Chapter 785: Black Weasel City

Right at this moment, a burst of peculiar silver light suddenly appeared beside Han Li, and a silver talisman flew out of Shi Chuankong's glabella before exploding violently.

The silver light instantly swept over both of them, and they vanished from the spot.

A resounding boom rang out as the green jade flying carriage was pulverized by the Golden Rhinoceros King's almighty stomp, but at this point, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were already nowhere to be seen.

The Golden Rhinoceros King let loose a furious roar upon seeing this, and he cast his gaze far into the distance as he prepared to continue in his pursuit.

However, his expression then suddenly changed slightly as he abruptly stopped cold in his tracks.

An incredibly dense dark cloud had suddenly appeared on the horizon in that direction.

After staring at the dark cloud with a hesitant expression for some time, the Golden Rhinoceros King ultimately decided to turn back, returning to his golden carriage before returning the same way he had come from.

……

Close to a hundred thousand kilometers away.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong suddenly emerged from the soil on a lush hill.

At this moment, both of them were looking a little disheveled. In particular, there was still some blood trailing down from the corner of Shi Chuankong's lips, and he didn't have time to wipe it away yet.

"The Golden Rhinoceros King didn't come after us?" Han Li asked.

"We've already entered the Black Weasel King's territory. That final stomp was most likely a last-ditch attempt to kill us, but he doesn't dare to venture any deeper into the Black Weasel King's territory. Otherwise, if the Black Weasel King comes out to confront him, it won't be so easy for him to get away," Shi Chuankong replied while panting heavily.

"What was that talisman that just flew out of your glabella? It really saved us back there," Han Li asked.

"That was one of the few life-saving talismans that my father gave to me, and it can only be used once," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

"In the instant before we were teleported away, I sensed an aura that was just as powerful as the Golden Rhinoceros King's, but I didn't get a chance to examine it further before the talisman took effect. We haven't just jumped out of the frying pan and into the fire, have we?" Han Li asked with furrowed brows.

"That was most likely the aura of the Black Weasel King that you detected. The reason why I decided that we should flee into the Black Weasel King's territory isn't just because he's a sworn enemy of the Golden Rhinoceros King. In addition to that, he's also somewhat different from the other Ten Hazards," Shi Chuankong said.

"How so?" Han Li asked.

"The Black Weasel King's true form is also that of a demon beast, but I've heard that his cultivation catalyst was quite unique. Instead of using a cultivation art of our Holy Realm, he's using a daoist cultivation art from your Immortal Realm, so he's not as bloodthirsty as the other Ten Hazards.

“Instead, he's a very refined and tasteful man who likes to read literary classics, and I've heard that he's even traveled to some mortal empires in the past while posing as a scholar," Shi Chuankong explained with a hint of mockery in his eyes.

"A well-learned demon beast? That's certainly a first," Han Li mused as he raised an eyebrow.

"Ultimately, he's still nothing more than an untamed beast under a refined guise. I heard that he previously took part in a mortal nation's imperial examination, but he failed on all three attempts, and in a fit of fury, he ate that nation's emperor and six other important officials," Shi Chuankong scoffed with a derisive sneer.

"It sounds like we can't rely on his good graces then. In that case, we should try and get out of here as soon as possible," Han Li said.

"There's no need for that. Over the years, the Black Weasel King has always been on friendly terms with Night Sun City, and it's clear that he's intentionally trying to distance himself from the title of the Ten Hazards. Hence, as long as we don't start any trouble, we shouldn't be under any risk in his territory. On top of that, I also want to pay a visit to Black Weasel City," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"Black Weasel City?"

"Even though the Ten Hazards Mountain Range is a primordial land, it produces a special type of spirit material known as Purple Sun Warm Jade. It's an extremely rare spirit material that can improve the harmony between a body and a nascent soul, thereby significantly shortening the amount of time required for a nascent soul to possess a new body.

“This is an item sought after by one of my subordinates, the one by the name of Feng Lin that you met back in the True Mantra Sect ruins. On top of that, this material can also nourish the soul, so perhaps it can cure Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul's current condition," Shi Chuankong explained.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then asked, "But I'm not a devilish being, won't that be a problem?"

"If I'm not mistaken, you also possess a devilish cultivation art, right? All you need to do is release the aura of your cultivation art, and even if you don't take on a devilish form, that should suffice," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Han Li channeled his Provenance True Devil Arts upon hearing this, and a layer of golden scales appeared over parts of his exposed skin.

"That's more than enough," Shi Chuankong assured with a nod. "Let's go. We're still quite far from Black Weasel City, and your flying carriage was just destroyed, so let's use my one from here, and you can take this time to have a rest."

Shi Chuankong swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, summoning a black flying carriage that was riddled with black devilish patterns, and it didn't appear to be inferior to the green jade flying carriage at all.

"In that case, I'll be in your care," Han Li said with a smile, then hopped onto the flying carriage.

Shi Chuankong flew onto the carriage as well before making a hand seal, and the carriage set off toward the northwest as a black shadow.

Over a month passed by in a flash, and there were no further pursuers during this time, but Han Li and Shi Chuankong still kept their guards up.

Finally, they arrived at their destination.

The territory of the Black Weasel King was already very close to the edge of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and there were far fewer demon beasts here than in the Golden Rhinoceros King's territory. Hence, their journey was far smoother, and they didn't come under many attacks.

"We're finally here," Han Li remarked as he hovered in mid-air, looking out at a vast lake several kilometers up ahead.

The water of the lake was dark purple in color, giving it a very peculiar appearance.

Despite its strange coloration, the water didn't appear to be harmful at all, and the lake was teeming with life.

"This lake is called Purple Fen Lake, and it derives its name from a type of fen jade that's produced here. There's a huge fen jade ore vein on the lakebed, and the energy seeping out from it is what's given the lake its purple color. Fen jade is a concomitant spirit material of Purple Sun Warm Jade, so when collecting fen jade, one would occasionally be able to dig up a chunk of Purple Sun Warm Jade or two.

“Fen jade ore veins are extremely rare, even in the context of the entire Holy Realm, and to my knowledge, this is the only one that can give rise to Purple Sun Warm Jade," Shi Chuankong explained.

"In that case, let's go," Han Li said in an eager manner upon hearing this.

Weeping Soul was still unconscious, and her aura was still gradually diminishing. He had no way to cure her condition for now, so he could only hope that the Purple Sun Warm Jade would have some effect.

"Hold on a second, Brother Li. Right now, our appearances are a little eye-catching, so we should adopt some disguises," Shi Chuankong said, then began to chant an incantation, and a layer of rippling black light washed over his body.

After the black light faded, Shi Chuankong was revealed to have transformed into a muscular man with strands of black fur all over his arms and legs, giving him the appearance of a being from the wolf tribe of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range.

Han Li also adopted a disguise upon seeing this, transforming into a horned young man with purple hair and green eyes.

This disguise of his was extremely intricate, and it incorporated both his Mantra Domain and his Provenance True Devil Arts, so even a Great Encompassment being wasn't necessarily going to be able to see through it.

After adopting this disguise, Han Li immediately flew toward the lake, while Shi Chuankong followed along.

Before long, the two of them had flown hundreds of thousands of kilometers, and right at this moment, a black island that was several hundred kilometers in radius appeared up ahead.

There was a giant city on the island that took up the entire landmass, and its walls were over a thousand feet tall and entirely paved with a type of black crystalline material, presenting a majestic sight to behold.

The city walls were also etched with some purple patterns that seemed to be for fortification purposes, and they were emanating a faint purple glow that enshrouded the city in an air of mystery.

This was Black Weasel City, the home of the Black Weasel King.

From here, Han Li and Shi Chuankong began to slow down as they were no longer the only ones in the area, and more streaks of light had begun to appear nearby.

A series of giant ships had also appeared on the surface of the lake down below, traveling toward the city.

The closer they drew to Black Weasel City, the more ships and streaks of light they encountered, all of which were converging toward the city.

The two of them didn't want to attract any attention, so they suppressed their auras to the True Immortal Stage.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the giant ships, upon which a surprised look appeared on his face.

"What's wrong, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"On the way here, all of the demon beasts that we encountered were still in their beastly forms, and only upon reaching a certain cultivation base could they adopt human forms. However, none of the beastly cultivators on those ships possess particularly lofty cultivation bases, yet they've already attained human forms," Han Li mused.

"Almost all beastly cultivators can attain human forms upon reaching a certain cultivation base, but the timing differs depending on their bloodlines. Generally speaking, the easier it is for a beastly cultivator to attain a human form, the lowlier their bloodline will be. All of the beastly cultivators on those ships are considered to be low-grade beings, and the same principle applies to all of the beings in our Holy Realm," Shi Chuankong explained.

Chapter 786: A Longing for Mortal Virtues

"I see. It sounds like bloodlines are taken very seriously in the Devil Realm," Han Li mused.

"Power championed above all else in our Holy Realm, and weaker tribes are generally all enslaved and oppressed by more powerful ones, so the bloodline hierarchy is indeed taken very seriously, and that's even more so in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range.

“Out of the Ten Hazards, only the Black Weasel King is more lenient in this regard, and that's why many of the low-grade tribes have moved here," Shi Chuankong sighed, seemingly not very pleased with the state of affairs.

Han Li offered no response to this.

At this point, the two of them had already arrived on the edge of Black Weasel City.

Up close, the city was even more majestic, and its tall city walls bordered the coastline.

There were city gates at set intervals along the city walls, and every single city gate was lined with ports where giant ships were docked, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

"This is quite a nice city. Even though it was built by a demon beast, it looks no different from a city in the Immortal Realm," Han Li remarked.

"Among the Ten Hazards, the Black Weasel King is closest with the mortal world, and he encourages business and trade, so even though there aren't many high-grade tribes residing in his territory, their overall power is still nothing to be scoffed at," Shi Chuankong said.

"It sounds like the Black Weasel King can be referred to as a wise ruler among the Ten Hazards then," Han Li said.

"I suppose you can say that to a certain extent," Shi Chuankong replied with a peculiar look on his face.

Han Li was rather intrigued by Shi Chuankong's reaction, but he didn't ask any questions.

"Let's go," Shi Chuankong said, and the two of them flew toward the nearest city gate, where there were some soldiers clad in black armor, examining those who were entering the city.

However, the checks weren't very stringent, and Shi Chuankong approached the guards at the city gates for a brief conversation, then handed over a few black crystals, and the two of them were granted entry into the city.

Han Li made his way through the city gate, then inspected his surroundings momentarily before nodding in approval at what he saw.

The streets and buildings in the city were quite clean and well-maintained, and in particular, the streets were over a hundred feet wide and paved with very uniform and even black bricks.

There were many carriages parked on either side of the street, drawn by a type of dark green beast that had horse-like bodies, but wyrm-like heads.

The owner of one of the carriages immediately approached Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

He was a short young man with dark red scales all over his hands and feet, and he was only at the Nascent Soul Stage.

The young man had a pair of bright and intelligent eyes, and he said in an enthusiastic voice, "Is this your first time visiting Black Weasel City? Please consider hiring my carriage, it'll only cost one top-grade devil stone a day. My name is Lu Xie, and I grew up my entire life in this city, so I'm very familiar with its layout."

"Why does everyone have to travel by carriage? Is flight prohibited in the city?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Indeed, flight is prohibited in the city by the Black Weasel King, and there are flight restrictions in the sky, so people in the city can only travel on foot or by carriage," Lu Xie replied.

Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with Han Li, then nodded as he said, "This is indeed our first time in Black Weasel City, and we're here to buy some things. If you do a good job, I can give you two top-grade devil stones a day."

Lu Xie was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly replied, "You can count on me, Senior!"

With that, Han Li and Shi Chuankong got into the carriage, and they set off from there.

The green horse-like creatures were quite fast, and the surrounding scenery was flying past in a blur.

"Are there any prohibitions in Black Weasel City, Lu Xie?" Han Li asked while inspecting his surroundings.

"There are. The most strictly enforced one is that fighting is prohibited, regardless for what reason. Anyone who breaks this rule will be captured and stripped of their cultivation base. There's also a nightly curfew in the city, and whenever night arrives, one has to either leave the city or find an inn to stay in. Anyone who's discovered wandering the city at night will be captured and also punished very severely," Lu Xie replied.

"Why is there a nightly curfew?" Han Li asked.

Flight and battle restrictions made sense to him, but a nightly curfew was rather unexpected. For cultivators, night or day made no difference, and given how developed the business sector in Black Weasel City appeared, all of the shops had to be quite busy. The nightly curfew essentially cut operating hours by half, and that had to have quite a heavy impact.

"The Black Weasel King mandated the nightly curfew. He says that people should go home at night, and that it's unbecoming and indecent to be wandering around at night," Lu Xie explained with a slightly awkward expression.

Han Li was a little speechless upon hearing this.

He had thought that the Black Weasel King had to have some special reason for enforcing a nightly curfew, but this was completely unexpected, and his impression of the Black Weasel King changed a little upon hearing this.

It was no wonder that Shi Chuankong had displayed such a peculiar expression when talking about the Black Weasel King earlier.

"Tell us about the city, Lu Xie," Shi Chuankong interjected.

Lu Xie was clearly very relieved that the conversation had diverged away from the Black Weasel King, and he said, "Black Weasel City is split up into nine areas, of which the three central areas are inhabited by the Black Weasel King and the Black Weasel Army directly under his command. Out of the six remaining areas, three are normal residential areas, and they're quite large, but they're inhabited solely by low-grade tribes, so there's not much to see there.

“Two of the remaining three areas are also residential areas, but reserved for high-grade tribes and powerful beings like yourselves, while the final area is the business area, where almost all of the city's best shops can be found. Almost all of the city's premium materials and devilish treasures are sold there, and a small fee is required to enter the area, but I'm sure that won't be an issue for cultivators of your caliber."

"We came to Black Weasel City on this occasion to buy some Purple Sun Warm Jade. Do you know where this material is sold?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Purple Sun Warm Jade is a very rare resource produced in our city, and demand has always outweighed supply. On top of that, someone like me is not privy to information concerning the current market circumstances for Purple Sun Warm Jade. All I can do is take you to the best shops in the city and hope that you can find what you're looking for there," Lu Xie replied in a an apologetic fashion.

"That's fine, take us there," Shi Chuankong replied.

It wasn't like he had expected to find out anything from Lu Xie anyway, and Lu Xie hurriedly gave an affirmative response.

An hour later, the carriage drew to a halt in front of a giant city gate deep in the city.

The areas in the city were separated by some shorter city walls, and looking in through the city gate up ahead, one could catch a glimpse of a series of tall and opulent shops and throngs of people coming and going, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

This was the city's trading area, and the carriage was stopped by some guards clad in black armor stationed at the city gate.

"Each person needs to issue one high-grade devil stone to enter the trading area, so that'll be three high-grade devil stones for the three of you," one of the guards declared.

Lu Xie turned to Han Li and Shi Chuankong with a slightly awkward expression upon hearing this.

Generally speaking, this fee was always issued by the passenger, but Han Li and Shi Chuankong had only just arrived in Black Weasel City, so they were perhaps unaware of this unspoken rule, and Lu Xie hadn't informed them of this in advance.

Thankfully for Lu Xie, neither of them made a fuss, and Shi Chuankong tossed three high-grade devil stones at the armored guard, earning them entry into the trading area.

"Thank you, Senior," Lu Xie said with a grateful expression, and the carriage began to trundle its way down the street into the trading area.

Shortly thereafter, the carriage drew to a halt in front of a five-story pavilion, one that appeared rather unremarkable, but there were many customers entering and exiting the building.

Hanging above the entrance of the pavilion was a plaque that read "Floating Gold Pavilion".

"This is one of the largest shops in the city," Lu Xie introduced. "It doesn't look like it's anything special, but it's already been in operation for over ten thousand years and possesses tremendous resources. Please feel free to take a look inside, I'll wait out here for you."

Han Li and Shi Chuankong stepped off the carriage before entering the shop, and as they did so, Han Li made a point to take a subtle glance at his surroundings to ensure that there wasn't anything amiss.

As soon as they stepped through the entrance of the shop, a burst of faint devilish qi fluctuations swept over their bodies, and their vision blurred momentarily, following which they suddenly found themselves in a giant hall that was thousands of feet in size.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this. Sure enough, there was more to the building than met the eye, and its interior was far larger than the exterior suggested.

On top of that, he had detected a sensory aura within that burst of devilish qi fluctuations just now, and that was most likely to examine their cultivation bases.

However, both he and Shi Chuankong had concealed their true cultivation bases, and an examination of this degree wasn't going to be enough to see through their guises.

The hall was lined with a series of giant display cabinets that were filled with merchandise. The cabinets on the left contained all types of raw materials, while the ones on the right contained finished products such as pills and devilish treasures.

These cabinets were arranged in a very orderly and uniform fashion, making it very easy for customers to quickly track down the items that they were looking for.

Behind each cabinet was a green-robed employee, all of whom were serving customers with warm smiles on their faces.

All of these employees were in humanoid forms, and barely any inhuman features could be seen in them.

A beautiful green-robed female employee approached Han Li and Shi Chuankong, then said in a respectful manner, "Welcome to our Floating Gold Pavilion, seniors. We aren't qualified to serve esteemed guests at the True Immortal Stage, so please allow me to take you to an administrator."

Chapter 787: Shopping Spree

"Lead the way," Shi Chuankong said in a casual manner.

The green-robed woman did as she was told, leading Han Li and Shi Chuankong to an individual booth, where various types of fruits, snacks, and tea were offered to them.

"These Dark Fruits and Spring Mist Tea are specialty local products of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, feel free to give them a try, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong suggested.

Han Li raised a cup of steaming tea, then took a small sip before giving a slight nod.

Right at this moment, the door of the booth was opened, and a young woman in a pink dress stepped inside. She had also taken on a humanoid form, and there were no visible inhuman features on her at all.

"Sorry to keep you waiting. I am Mei Lan, an administrator of the Floating Gold Pavilion," the young woman introduced.

Bouquets of pink flowers were emerging in the air around her as she walked, giving off a fragrant aroma.

Han Li raised an eyebrow at the sight of the young woman, who was at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage. It appeared that she was most likely a tree demon, and whatever cultivation arts she was using seemed to be quite remarkable as well.

It was quite strange to Han Li that someone of her cultivation base was serving as a mere administrator in this Floating Gold Pavilion, but he quickly realized that this was most likely a business tactic of the pavilion.

By sending out an administrator of a far superior cultivation base to the customer, the Floating Gold Pavilion would be able to exert subtle pressure on the customer, thereby gaining the initiative.

However, such a tactic naturally wasn't effective on Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and the two of them continued to sit and drink tea with their expressions completely unchanged.

Mei Lan was slightly taken aback by the composure displayed by Han Li's duo, but her expression also remained unchanged as she sat down across from the two of them and asked, "What can I help you with today, esteemed guests?"

Shi Chuankong casually set down the teacup in his hand, then flipped a hand over to produce a storage bracelet, which he tossed at Mei Lan as he said, "We heard that the Floating Gold Pavilion is one of the largest shops in Black Weasel City, and we wanted to discuss some business with your shop. Here's the deposit."

A hint of surprise flashed through Mei Lan's eyes upon hearing this, but she still caught the bracelet, and after inspecting its contents with her spiritual sense, an astonished look instantly appeared on her face.

Inside the storage bracelet were five hundred thousand Devilish Origin Stones stacked in neat piles, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Upon realizing her own loss of composure, Mei Lan hurriedly composed herself, then set down the storage bracelet in her hand as she said, "It is a great honor for our Floating Gold Pavilion that you've chosen us. May I ask how I can help you today?"

A hint of amusement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

Mei Lan had intended to intimidate the two of them with her vastly superior cultivation base, but Shi Chuankong had employed the same tactic against her, claiming the upper hand by presenting such an enormous sum of wealth.

An unspoken contest was taking place here, and Shi Chuankong had gained the upper hand, as expected of such an integral figure in the Vast Origin House.

"We're looking to buy a batch of high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade," Shi Chuankong declared in a straightforward manner.

Mei Lan's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she offered no response.

"Are you not interested in making such a deal?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Please don't misunderstand. We're naturally very much willing to do business with you, but Purple Sun Warm Jade has always been in very short supply, and we don't even have any mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, let alone high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade," Mei Lan explained with an awkward expression.

"I know Purple Sun Warm Jade is always in short supply. How about this? We're willing to pay you an additional 30% over the market price, but the product that you supply has to be good," Shi Chuankong offered.

"You misunderstand my intentions, esteemed customer, I'm not trying to increase the price. Instead, I'm merely telling the truth. I'm guessing that the two of you aren't from Black Weasel City, right? This may come across as a little rude, but you don't seem to have much of a grasp on the market for Purple Sun Warm Jade.

“While it's true that this city produces Purple Sun Warm Jade, the quantity produced is extremely low to begin with, and most of it falls under the control of the Black Weasel King. Even though we're one of the biggest shops in Black Weasel City, we only have a very small supply of Purple Sun Warm Jade, and it's all of the low-grade variety," Mei Lan explained with a wry smile.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions darkened slightly upon hearing this.

"So you're saying that you can't help us?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"If you're looking for anything else, then I'd be happy to help, but I'm truly powerless to help when it comes to Purple Sun Warm Jade. Please accept my sincerest apologies," Mei Lan sighed.

"In that case, I won't try to force the matter," Shi Chuankong said as he retrieved his storage bracelet, while Mei Lan looked on with a wistful expression.

"You just mentioned that you have a supply of low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, right? I'd like to take a look at that if possible," Han Li suddenly said.

A hint of elation flashed through Mei Lan's eyes upon hearing this, and she immediately replied, "Alright, please wait for a moment."

Following Mei Lan's departure, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to cast a restriction in the room, then asked, "Do you think she was telling the truth just now, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"While she was speaking, I used a secret technique that can verify the truth of one's words to a certain extent, and the secret technique tells me that she didn't appear to be lying," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In that case, it really does look like it'll be quite difficult for us to get our hands on some high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade," Han Li said with furrowed brows.

"We'll just have to do our best, and if it doesn't work out, then so be it. There's quite a large disparity in the efficacy of Purple Sun Warm Jade of different grades, and low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade has a rather mediocre soul nurturing effect, so it won't do us much good," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In any case, if it can help Weeping Soul's condition, then we can't afford to pass up on it," Han Li said.

Shi Chuankong merely smiled and offered no response, following which both of them became absorbed in their own thoughts.

A short while later, the sound of footsteps rang out from outside, and Han Li dispelled the restriction in the room, following which the door was opened.

Mei Lan stepped into the room with a purple jade box in her hands, and she set the box down in front of Han Li as she said, "Sorry to keep you waiting. This is all of the Purple Sun Warm Jade that our shop currently has."

Han Li opened the jade box to reveal around two to three dozen fist-sized purple crystals that were giving off a faint purple glow.

However, there were some flaws and blemishes on these crystals that were rather eye-catching, and they also somewhat dulled the purple light emanating from the crystals.

He picked up one of the purple crystals, and it was warm to the touch. Furthermore, it was releasing a burst of warmth into his mind to envelop his soul, making it feel as if it were basking in a warm spring breeze.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon sensing this. It seemed that this Purple Sun Warm Jade was indeed going to be beneficial to Weeping Soul's condition.

"These are all low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, but they're still nothing to be looked down on. What do you think, esteemed customer?" Mei Lan asked.

"How much are you selling this Purple Sun Warm Jade for?" Han Li asked as he placed the purple crystal in his hand back into the jade box.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Mei Lan stated a price that was 10% over the market price.

The price was within the realm of Han Li's expectations, and he couldn't be bothered to barter, so he nodded in agreement.

Having claimed the storage tools of Tie Yu and Tong Yu, he currently had quite a large supply of Devilish Origin Stones, so this was not a significant sum to him.

He stowed the purple jade box away, then summoned a storage ring that he handed over to Mei Lan.

"Thank you for your patronage," Mei Lan said with a smile after briefly inspecting the contents of the storage ring.

After the deal was complete, Han Li and Shi Chuankong promptly departed, and Mei Lan accompanied them all the way to the entrance of the Floating Gold Pavilion.

Lu Xie had been waiting for them this entire time, and he immediately approached them as they exited the shop.

"How did it go, seniors?"

"Don't ask unnecessary questions. Just do your job and take us to the next shop," Shi Chuankong replied in a cold voice.

Lu Xie shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly gave an affirmative response.

A short while later, the carriage drew to a halt in front of a tall pagoda, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong entered the shop before re-emerging close to an hour later.

"Take us to the next one," Han Li instructed.

All in all, the two of them visited six or seven large shops before night fell, clearing out all of their supplies of Purple Sun Warm Jade.

That night, they chose an inn to stay in.

Inside his room, Han Li made a hand seal before releasing a flurry of array flags out of his sleeves, and the flags descended all around the room, setting up several light barriers.

After that, he conjured up a door of silver light before stepping into the Flower Branch domain.

Inside the bamboo pavilion, Weeping Soul remained unconscious as she laid on the bed.

Her complexion was so pale that her cheeks almost appeared translucent, and small plumes of black qi were rising up out of her body before dissipating into nothingness.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Weeping Soul's condition had worsened significantly since he last checked on her several days ago, and the rate at which her essential energy was dissipating had also sped up drastically.

After taking a deep breath to compose himself, he swept a sleeve toward the nearby table, and five or six jade boxes appeared on the table amid a flash of azure light, containing a total of over two hundred pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade, all of which were of the low-grade variety.

Even though he hadn't managed to purchase even a single piece of mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, he was hoping that such a large quantity of low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade would be able to help Weeping Soul's condition.

The only concern was that buying up so much Purple Sun Warm Jade had most likely already attracted him a great deal of attention from those who were in the know in Black Weasel City.

Thankfully, Black Weasel City was a thriving business hub with many merchants coming through from outside, so their activities weren't particularly suspicious.

However, after some discussion with Shi Chuankong, the two of them had already decided that they were going to stay for one more day to purchase more Purple Sun Warm Jade before leaving the city to avoid unnecessary trouble.

Chapter 788: Unexpected Deal

After drawing three pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade into his hand, Han Li carefully placed them over Weeping Soul's forehead, heart, and lower abdomen in accordance with the method taught to him by Shi Chuankong.

The purple light emanating from the three crystals instantly brightened slightly, only to then return to normal again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he sat down onto the ground with his legs crossed to observe Weeping Soul.

Several minutes passed by with neither the pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade nor Weeping Soul displaying any changes, and Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

Even though this Purple Sun Warm Jade was only of the low-grade variety, he had thought that it would have some positive effect on Weeping Soul, even if it couldn't completely cure her condition.

Having said that, he was already prepared for such an outcome, and he immediately rose to his feet before setting up a hexagonal array that was around ten feet in size on the ground.

At the center of the array was a circular area, while there were sixteen slots littered throughout the array.

Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings to ensure that the array had been set up correctly, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that picked up Weeping Soul's body before gently setting her down at the center of the array.

After that, he placed sixteen pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade into the slots in the array before casting an incantation seal into the center of the array.

The hexagonal array immediately lit up, as did the sixteen pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade, which released bursts of purple light that flowed along the lines of the array before converging around Weeping Soul's body.

A layer of purple light instantly appeared around her, and her aura was immediately stabilized, while her rate of essential energy dissipation was slowed down significantly, but wasn't stopped altogether.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

The energy contained in Purple Sun Warm Jade was very special and difficult to harness. This array appeared to be quite simple, but it was actually extremely profound, and it was one that he had created after painstakingly altering a spiritual energy gathering array. Through the use of the array, he was able to elevate the low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade placed within them to around the mid-grade level, but it appeared that this still wasn't enough.

This meant that if he wanted to enhance the effect that the array had on Weeping Soul, he would have to replace all of the low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade in the array with mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, something that was completely beyond his means at the moment.

With that in mind, Han Li could only heave a long sigh.

It seemed that his only hope right now was to accompany Shi Chuankong to Night Sun City and seek out that grand priest.

Thankfully, Weeping Soul's rate of essential energy dissipation had already slowed down significantly, and that should be enough for her to last until they reached Night Sun City.

However, he only had just over two hundred pieces of low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, and he didn't know how long that was going to last, so he would have to purchase some more.

"I promise that I'll save you, Weeping Soul," Han Li vowed in a solemn manner, then left the Flower Branch space to return to his room.

An uneventful night passed by, the next morning, Han Li and Shi Chuankong paid for their rooms before leaving the inn.

"Seeing as we're only going to stay here for one more day, we don't have much time, so I think we should split up. What do you think, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li suggested.

"That sounds like a good idea. That way, we'll be able to visit more shops, but make sure to be on your guard and maintain constant contact," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Of course. Also, low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade may not be worth much to you, but they're very useful to me, so if you happen to find any, please purchase it for me, and I'll compensate you after the event," Han Li said.

"There's no need for you to compensate me. If it wasn't for Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul, I would've perished back in the infernal prison in Asura City. Seeing as this Purple Sun Warm Jade is for her, it's the least I can do to repay her for saving my life," Shi Chuankong said.

"You have my thanks," Han Li said.

The two of them emerged from the inn, and Lu Xie was already waiting for them by the entrance with a wide smile on his face.

"You can take Lu Xie's carriage, Fellow Daoist Li. I'll go hail another one," Shi Chuankong said before turning to depart.

Lu Xie turned to Han Li with an inquisitive look upon seeing this, and Han Li waved a dismissive hand as he explained, "Don't mind him, he has some other matters to attend to. Keep taking me to the shops in the city."

Lu Xie asked no further questions and did as he was told.

……

Half a day flew by in a flash.

With Lu Xie acting as his guide, Han Li visited five or six more shops, but progress was much slower than it had been the day before, and he had only managed to purchase fewer than a hundred pieces of low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade.

He emerged from a shop with tightly furrowed brows, then beckoned to Lu Xie, instructing him to move onto the next shop.

Lu Xie approached him with an uneasy expression, holding a black voice transmission talisman in his hand, then said, "Senior Li, someone approached me not long after you entered that shop and asked me to pass this onto you."

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he accepted the talisman before injecting his spiritual sense into it, following which his pupils instantly contracted slightly.

"Where's the person that gave you this talisman?" he immediately asked as he scoured his surroundings, but didn't spot anyone worthy of note.

Lu Xie became even more uneasy at the sight of Han Li's reaction, and he hurriedly replied, "He immediately left after giving me this voice transmission talisman, and he told me that if you want to meet him, then you can go to the Plum Forest Teahouse up ahead."

"It's alright, there's no need for you to feel anxious. Take me to the Plum Forest Teahouse," Han Li instructed.

Lu Xie did as he was told, while Han Li sat in the carriage, looking at the voice transmission talisman in his hand with a contemplative expression.

The talisman contained a very concise message: "I have information pertaining to Purple Sun Warm Jade."

A short while later, a resolute look appeared in his eyes as he stowed the talisman away, then summoned a purple jade plate and spoke into it briefly before stowing it away as well.

Before long, the carriage arrived in front of a teahouse.

"Wait for me outside," Han Li instructed before making his way into the teahouse.

Business appeared to be quite slow, and there were only four or five customers inside the teahouse.

Han Li was approached by a waiter, but he paid no heed to the waiter as he cast his gaze toward the customers in the teahouse.

Right at this moment, a black-robed young man rose to his feet before giving Han Li a nod.

"Thank you for coming, Fellow Daoist. Please come with me to the second floor where we'll have a bit more privacy," the black-robed young man said through voice transmission, then turned and began to make his way up the stairs.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li followed along, and the two of them entered a booth before sitting down.

"Were you the one who left this voice transmission talisman for me?" Han Li asked as he fished out the black talisman.

"That's right. My name is Hei Lang. This is quite an important matter, and that's why I employed such a roundabout method to invite you to come and see me," the black-robed young man replied as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing several small black flags that released a black light barrier to encompass the entire booth.

Through this gesture, Han Li was immediately able to determine that Hei Lang was a True Immortal cultivator. On top of that, he was from the devil race, just like Shi Chuankong.

Han Li wasn't all that surprised by this. During his time in the city, he had seen quite a few devilish beings, and there were even some mortal devilish beings among them.

According to Shi Chuankong, the devil race and the demon beasts in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range were sworn enemies, but Black Weasel City was a safe haven where all beings could coexist in harmony.

As a result, Black Weasel City was a massive melting pot of beings of all descriptions, and it was clear that this was exactly what the Black Weasel King wanted.

"It's fine. Do you truly have information on Purple Sun Warm Jade?" Han Li asked in a direct and straightforward manner.

"Of course. Otherwise, I wouldn't have invited you here," Hei Lang replied with a smile.

A hint of elation welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, but his expression remained completely unchanged as he asked, "How much Purple Sun Warm Jade do you have? If it's only a small quantity, then I'm not interested."

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist, my Purple Sun Warm Jade will definitely be of satisfactory quantity and quality to you. Here's a list of my stock. If you're interested, then we can discuss this matter further," Hei Lang replied as he pulled out a jade slip before handing it to Han Li.

Han Li took a meaningful glance at Hei Lang, then accepted the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it, following which a surprised look immediately appeared on his face.

Sure enough, the jade slip contained an extensive catalog of Purple Sun Warm Jade, consisting of over five hundred of the low-grade variety, forty to fifty of the mid-grade variety, and even two pieces of high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade.

"According to my knowledge, Purple Sun Warm Jade is extremely rare, and even the best shops in the city can only supply the low-grade variety. Do you really have so much Purple Sun Warm Jade to offer?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not someone with so little to do with my time that I would go around pranking people over such matters. Rest assured, you have my word," Hei Lang replied in a confident manner.

"Alright, in that case, how much are you planning to charge for your Purple Sun Warm Jade?" Han Li asked.

Hei Lang considered the question momentarily before stating a price.

Much to Han Li's surprise, the price that he had stated was not steep at all. In fact, it was even a little cheaper than the market price.

It seemed that there were some hidden circumstances involved. For example, perhaps Hei Lang had obtained his Purple Sun Warm Jade through illegitimate means, thereby making it difficult for him to sell them, and that could perhaps be why he was willing to offer such low prices.

Having said that, none of that mattered to Han Li. If he could go through with this deal, then he would immediately leave Black Weasel City after obtaining the Purple Sun Warm Jade, so the aftermath hardly mattered.

"Alright, I'll take everything you have. Do you have the Purple Sun Warm Jade with you right now? If so, then I'm willing to complete the transaction now," Han Li said.

"Before we discuss that, there's something else that I have to tell you," Hei Lang said.

Sure enough, there was a twist in the tale, and Han Li prompted, "Go ahead."

Chapter 789: True Appearance

"I can supply the Purple Sun Warm Jade that you want. However..."

A hesitant look appeared on Hei Lang's face as he spoke.

"What's the problem?" Han Li asked.

"The problem is that the batch of Purple Sun Warm Jade is currently in someone else's possession, and..."

"So you're negotiating a deal with me with someone else's stock?" Han Li interjected with a displeased expression. "On top of that, it sounds like they're not even aware of what we're discussing here, so it's yet to be seen whether they'd be willing to go through with this deal."

A hint of fury surfaced in Hei Lang's eyes upon hearing this, and he slammed his fist down onto the table as he snapped, "That's not true! I have a share in the Purple Sun Warm Jade as well!"

All of the teacups on the table were knocked over, spilling tea everywhere.

"My apologies for losing my composure," Hei Lang said as he suppressed the fury in his eyes.

"It's fine, just tell me what's going on," Han Li replied.

"I can assure you that I can convince that person to agree to the price I stated and complete this deal with you. However, I'm going to require your help. If you agree to help me, then we can continue this discussion, but if not, then let's end things here," Hei Lang said.

"Of course I'm interested in such a favorable deal, but how exactly do you need me to help you? Surely you can't expect me to take a risk without knowing any of the circumstances involved," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"There's no risk involved, all we need to do is use some negotiation tactics to force that person to agree to this deal. Just follow my lead, and I can assure you that there won't be any danger in the process," Hei Lang promised.

Han Li contemplated the offer for a moment, then replied, "I can help you, but under one condition."

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist," Hei Lang prompted.

"I'm sure that you're already aware that I'm not acting alone. I have a companion who isn't with me right now, and if you want me to help you, you have to bring him along as well," Han Li said.

"If that's your condition, then that won't be a problem. As long as it's someone you deem to be trustworthy, the more people we have on our side, the better," Hei Lang replied without any hesitation.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

As long as he and Shi Chuankong were together, he was confident that they would be able to get themselves out of any sticky situation, as long as there weren't any Great Encompassment cultivators involved, and it was worth taking some risk for the Purple Sun Warm Jade.

"In that case, let's go," Hei Lang said as he rose to his feet with an eager expression.

Han Li didn't want to delay this matter, either, and the two of them promptly exited the teahouse to find Shi Chuankong already waiting for them outside.

"Why did you call me here in such a hurry, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked as he took a glance at Hei Lang.

Han Li gave Shi Chuankong a brief recount of his discussion with Hei Lang through voice transmission, and an elated look immediately flashed through Shi Chuankong's eyes as he said, "That sounds like a great deal for us! Please lead the way, Fellow Daoist Hei Lang."

"Please come with me, fellow daoists," Hei Lang replied with a nod, then began to make his way down the street without hailing a carriage.

Shi Chuankong followed along behind him while scouring his surroundings, seemingly worried that Hei Lang could be up to no good.

Han Li was just about to follow along as well when a thought sprang into his mind, and he beckoned to the nearby Lu Xie, then handed him eight top-grade devil stones as he said, "Thank you for your hard work these past two days."

Lu Xie was ecstatic to see so many top-grade devil stones, and he immediately replied in a grateful voice, "Thank you, Senior!"

Han Li waved a dismissive hand, then quickly caught up to Shi Chuankong and Hei Lang.

The three of them rounded a series of corners and made their way through several streets before arriving at a rather shabby-looking shop.

The shop was situated in a rather secluded location, but it was quite large and appeared a little out of place.

At the moment, business appeared to be rather slow in the shop, and there wasn't a single customer inside. There was only a thin middle-aged man seated behind the counter, looking down at something, and a young employee that was organizing the stock on the shelves.

The thin shopkeeper looked up at the sound of Han Li's trio entering the shop, then put on a smile as he greeted, "Welcome, esteemed customers. How can I help you today?"

Hei Lang paid no heed to the shopkeeper as he made his way toward the shelves in the shop.

Han Li also began looking around the shop to find that despite its unremarkable appearance, there were some decent items being sold.

Even though he had just been flatly ignored, the shopkeeper remained unbothered, and he emerged from behind the counter as he introduced, "Our shop specializes in selling materials. We're not exactly a top-tier shop in Black Weasel City, but we have an extensive catalog that I'm sure will be satisfactory to you."

The shopkeeper was discreetly observing Han Li as he spoke, and Han Li was also watching him.

After walking through the shop for some time, Hei Lang stopped in a corner, then asked in a quiet voice, "Does your shop also purchase materials?"

"Of course, but we don't purchase everything that comes our way. It depends on what you have to sell," the shopkeeper replied.

Hei Lang slowly pulled out a black jade box, then opened it up just a sliver to reveal a length of black tree branch that was giving off astonishing devilish qi fluctuations.

The thin shopkeeper's eyes immediately lit up, but before he could get a closer look, Hei Lang had already closed the box, then took a glance outside, indicating that this wasn't the place to be talking.

"Come with me to the back, Fellow Daoist. As for these two fellow daoists, I'll have to get them to wait outside for a moment," the thin shopkeeper said.

"These two friends of mine have things that they wish to sell as well," Hei Lang said.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a wooden box upon hearing this, and Shi Chuankong did the same.

Even though the wooden boxes, one could sense formidable aura fluctuations coming from inside.

"In that case, all three of you can come with me," the shopkeeper said with a smile before leading the trio deeper into the shop.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other before following along, and the three of them soon arrived in an isolated room that was around seventy to eighty feet in size.

The thin shopkeeper made a hand seal, and an azure light barrier instantly appeared over the walls of the room, completely cutting it off from the outside world.

"Even a High Zenith cultivator wouldn't be able to eavesdrop on us through this restriction, so we can talk here without any qualms," the shopkeeper assured as he gestured for Han Li's trio to sit down.

Instead of sitting down, Han Li looked directly at the shopkeeper and said with a faint smile, "The restriction here is indeed quite remarkable, but before we begin, how about you present your true self to us? I don't have a habit of communicating with puppets."

Shi Chuankong and Hei Lang's expressions both changed slightly upon hearing this, and after a brief silence, the door of the room was opened once again, following which a thin middle-aged man emerged.

"You have a sharp eye, Fellow Daoist. I'm even more looking forward to seeing what you have to offer now."

At the same time, a dazed look appeared on the face of the shopkeeper in the room, and it made its way out of the room in a mechanical fashion.

"Your soul control technique is quite profound. If it isn't for the fact that I've cultivated a similar secret technique in the past, I wouldn't have been able to see through it," Han Li explained with a faint smile.

He could sense that the shopkeeper was at the Golden Immortal Stage, but he was carrying some type of aura concealment treasure that allowed him to display only a True Immortal Stage cultivation base.

This came as quite a relief to Han Li. If he was only dealing with a Golden Immortal, then there was no real danger here.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. Please take a seat," the shopkeeper said as he also sat down himself.

Both Han Li and Shi Chuankong also sat down, but Hei Lang remained standing.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist?" the shopkeeper asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"It sure was quite an ordeal just to secure an audience with you," Hei Lang said as a smile appeared on his face.

"What do you mean by that?" the shopkeeper asked in a bewildered manner.

"Long time no see, Brother Guan," Hei Lang said as he made a hand seal, and a series of writhing black feelers suddenly emerged over his body.

At the same time, his expression began to change rapidly, and he transformed into a dark-skinned young man who was looking exceptionally emaciated.

Simultaneously, his voice had also changed to become very sharp and raspy.

Both Han Li and Shi Chuankong had already noticed that Hei Lang was in disguise, so they weren't surprised to see this.

"Hei Lang? You're still alive?" the shopkeeper exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

"Of course I'm still alive. I must say, you possess commendable courage for continuing to stay in Black Weasel City, Brother Guan. The Black Weasel Army is searching for us outside, yet you're hiding in the city. The most dangerous place really can be the safest place sometimes," Hei Lang said with a smile.

A hint of killing intent flashed through the shopkeeper's eyes upon hearing this.

"I suggest you don't get any funny ideas, Brother Guan. Prior to coming here, I've already made preparations for a series of different outcomes, and if I don't walk out of this shop in two hours, someone will report all of your crimes to the Black Weasel Army. On top of that, with these fellow daoists here, you may want to think extra hard before you do anything," Hei Lang said as he casually sat down onto a chair.

The shopkeeper took a glance at Han Li and Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, and the killing intent in his eyes faded as he asked, "Why have you come to see me?"

Chapter 790: The Oriole Lurking Behind

"Why are you being so cold, Brother Guan? We're close acquaintances, are we not? As for why I came to see you, it's actually these two fellow daoists who wanted to see you. They want to buy some Purple Sun Warm Jade in Black Weasel City, so I introduced them to come here," Hei Lang replied as he gestured to Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"How could a small shop like mine possibly have stock of something as precious as Purple Sun Warm Jade? If you're looking for Purple Sun Warm Jade, I suggest you go to the larger shops in the city," the shopkeeper said with a cold expression.

Han Li offered no response, merely turning to Hei Lang to see what he had to say.

"Let's not waste any time here, Brother Guan. All of us risked our lives to secure that batch of Purple Sun Warm Jade. In fact, Ri Xi and Ri Xie even lost their lives in the process. Perhaps you can proclaim that you went into hiding in order to keep yourself safe, but don't even think about claiming all of the Purple Sun Warm Jade for yourself!" Hei Lang said in a cold voice.

"How could you say that, Hei Lang? Am I that kind of person in your eyes? I thought that the three of you had perished, but now you've come to me alive and well, I'm naturally not going to claim all of the Purple Sun Warm Jade for myself. Having said that, how could you divulge this matter to outsiders? Have you forgotten the vow that we swore together?" the shopkeeper accused as a furious look appeared on his face.

"We did indeed swear a vow together, but you know better than anyone how Ri Xi and Ri Xie died. You betrayed us first, so don't go bringing up the vow when it suits you!" Hei Lang sneered.

"Fine. Let's not dwell on the past, Hei Lang. Just tell me what you want," the shopkeeper said as the enraged look on his face faded away.

"I'm assuming that you've chosen to remain in Black Weasel City for two reasons, the first of which is to hide from the Black Weasel Army, while the second is to try and find a suitable buyer for the Purple Sun Warm Jade. These two fellow daoists aren't from the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and they possess a great deal of wealth.

“Both of them have come to Black Weasel City on this occasion to purchase large amounts of Purple Sun Warm Jade, so they're the perfect buyers. I've already negotiated a deal with them for this price, and I'm willing to let bygones be bygones as long as you split half of the Devilish Origin Stones with me," Hei Lang said as he pulled out a jade slip before tossing it at the shopkeeper.

The shopkeeper caught the jade slip, then injected his spiritual sense into it, following which a contemplative look appeared on his face.

After a brief silence, he said, "I have no objections to this deal, but I have a condition."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"The two of you need to swear a vow on your inner demons to leave Black Weasel City right away after our deal is complete, and to never tell anyone about what you saw and heard here," the shopkeeper said.

"That's fine. We're only here for the Purple Sun Warm Jade and have no interest in anything else," Han Li replied with a nod after exchanging a glance with Shi Chuankong.

With that, the two of them promptly swore their inner demon vows in accordance with the shopkeeper's request.

The shopkeeper's expression instantly eased significantly upon seeing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce a purple storage bracelet before placing it on the table as he said, "You've shown me a great deal of sincerity, so I won't waste any more of your time. This is what you're looking for."

Han Li flipped a hand over to summon two storage rings before placing them onto the table, then picked up the storage bracelet before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The shopkeeper and Hei Lang also each picked up one of the storage rings before examining their contents, and it was quickly confirmed that no one had attempted any trickery.

"Now that the deal is complete, I won't keep you any longer," the shopkeeper said.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong had no intention of staying, and they immediately stood up to depart.

Hei Lang seemed to be even more eager to leave than Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and he quickly made his way out of the room without a word.

However, right at this moment, a streak of golden sword qi suddenly appeared above his head without any warning before swooping down upon him.

The streak of sword qi had appeared without any warning, and it was incredibly fast, slicing Hei Lang's body cleanly into two before he even had a chance to raise his head.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, and they immediately drifted back into the room.

A horrified look appeared on the shopkeeper's face as he made a hand seal to try and activate the restriction in the room again, but the entire room was sliced into two with another flash of golden swordlight.

Immediately thereafter, around a dozen armorclad figures appeared to surround Han Li's trio.

These were none other than troops from the Black Weasel Army, and they were all at the Golden Immortal Stage.

Immediately thereafter, two figures appeared in mid-air before drifting down from above.

One of them was a handsome white-robed young man who appeared to be in his twenties, and he was holding a white folding fan.

He was accompanied by a beautiful azure-robed woman whose eyes were closed, seemingly indicating that she was blind, and she was holding a golden longsword that was giving off rays of dreamy golden light, making it impossible to make out the appearance of the sword.

Both of them were giving off tremendous High Zenith Stage auras, and the shopkeeper immediately let loose a cry of panic at the sight of the two of them while sweeping a sleeve through the air.

A ball of black flames swept over his body, then transformed into a giant fiery black devil that had three heads and six arms and was over a hundred feet tall.

Despite the black flames burning all over its body, the giant devil wasn't giving off any heat. Instead, a glacial aura was emanating from its body.

All of a sudden, it began swinging its six fists through the air, releasing a flurry of millstone-sized fiery black fist projections that rained down upon the dozen or so armorclad figures.

At the same time, it opened its three mouths to release three balls of black flames toward the two figures hovering in mid-air.

After doing all of that, a burst of yellow light flashed over the shopkeeper's body as he began sinking into the ground.

A cold sneer appeared on the white-robed young man's face, but he didn't do anything.

Meanwhile, the azure-robed woman's arm moved ever so slightly, and another streak of golden sword qi was released at an astonishing speed.

The three balls of black flames drew to an abrupt halt several dozen feet in front of them, and they were all sliced in half before glancing past them.

At this point, only the lower half of the shopkeeper's body had sunk into the ground, and his upper body suddenly fell to the side, having been severed in an instant.

The shopkeeper turned to the two figures with a frantic expression as he yelled, "Please forgive me, Your Highness! I let my greed get to my head in a momentary lapse in judgment! I'm willing to return all of the Purple Sun Warm Jade that I stole, and I'm also willing to sign a servant contract with you..."

The white-robed young man flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of crimson light that pierced into the shopkeeper's glabella in a flash like a dagger.

The shopkeeper's voice instantly cut off, while the light in his eyes faded away.

The white-robed young man made a beckoning motion, and the crimson light flew out of the shopkeeper's glabella with his nascent soul trapped inside.

The nascent soul was struggling with all its might, but to no avail.

"You certainly weren't easy to track down! Even my father was made aware of this incident, and he severely reprimanded me, yet here you are, hoping that I would spare you? I'm going to torment your soul for ten thousand years to make sure you learn your lesson!" the white-robed young man sneered before swallowing the black nascent soul.

After that, he turned to Han Li and Shi Chuankong with a slightly wary look in his eyes.

The two of them had been standing right in between him and the shopkeeper, yet they had been completely unaffected by the battle that had just taken place.

"Who are you, and how are you related to Guan Sheng and Hei Lang?" the white-robed young man asked as he descended to the ground.

"We're just customers visiting this shop, and we have no relation to those two at all. We'll be taking our leave now," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a parting salute, then turned to depart with Shi Chuankong.

A furious look flashed through the white-robed young man's eyes upon hearing this.

One of the armorclad figures immediately stepped into Han Li's path and yelled, "How dare you! Do you know who our young master is? How dare you speak to him with such blatant insolence?!"

"Get out of the way," Han Li said in an expressionless manner.

"You're a fool!" the armorclad man scoffed. "If you surrender now, perhaps you'll be spared."

He found it downright laughable that a pair of True Immortal Stage ants dared to be so insolent, but he didn't dare to attack without receiving any orders from the white-robed young man.

"Young Master, these two must be somehow associated with Guan Sheng and Hei Lang, so we should capture them right away!" another armorclad figure yelled.

"That's right! We don't know how many people snuck into the mine, and these two are most likely their accomplices! The Black Weasel King doesn't permit us to capture people in the city for no good reason, but we certainly can't just spare these people after committing such a severe crime!" a third armorclad figure chimed in.

Chapter 791: Subduing the Enemy with Ease

After a brief moment of contemplation, the white-robed young man gave a slight nod to the armorclad man, and a hint of bloodlust and excitement instantly appeared in the latter's eyes as he reached out with both hands to make a grabbing motion.

A pair of giant black claws appeared on either side of Han Li and Shi Chuankong, then converged toward them with tremendous force.

The claw projections swept through the air, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong were instantly torn to pieces, but their bodies then abruptly vanished from the spot, revealing them to be nothing more than afterimages.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li and Shi Chuankong appeared outside the encirclement of armorclad men amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then continued to make their way out of the shop, completely unaffected by the attack.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, and the azure-robed woman's brows furrowed slightly as she murmured to herself, "He's using spatial law powers..."

A hint of bewilderment flashed through the armorclad man's eyes upon seeing this, and after taking a glance at the white-robed young man, his body instantly swelled to several times its original height, while a layer of coarse fur emerged over his skin. He had taken on a half-demonic form, and his aura was also drastically elevated as a result.

Immediately thereafter, he let loose a thunderous roar, then sprang up into the air before lashing out at Han Li and Shi Chuankong from behind.

Han Li didn't even bother to turn around as he casually thrust a palm behind him to meet the armorclad man's fist, and a resounding boom rang out alongside the sound of cracking bones.

The armorclad man was instantly sent flying back as if he had been dealt a heavy blow, and he plowed straight through a nearby building, raising a huge cloud of dust.

Before he even had a chance to cry out, he had already fallen unconscious.

All of the Black Weasel Army cultivators were astonished to see this.

The armorclad man's forte was his physical prowess, yet he had been completely outmatched in that department, and that was a feat that was surely beyond the powers of even a High Zenith Stage demon beast.

At this point, it had become abundantly clear to them that Han Li and Shi Chuankong were clearly concealing their auras, and they all turned to the white-robed young man for further instructions.

After knocking his assailant unconscious, Han Li continued to walk along at a leisurely pace beside Shi Chuankong, but this time, no one attempted to stop them.

The white-robed young man seemed to be pondering what was the best course of action to take when he was approached by a short armorclad man, who whispered something into his ear.

The white-robed young man's expression remained unchanged upon hearing what the armorclad man had to say, but he abruptly vanished from the spot without any warning.

The white-robed young man then reappeared in front of Han Li and Shi Chuankong and said, "Please wait a moment."

At the same time, plumes of crimson mist began to surge out of his body, instantly forming a dense crimson cloud that was giving off some type of formidable law power fluctuations.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other, following which the latter asked with furrowed brows, "Do you still need something from us? We haven't broken any laws, and we're in a hurry right now, so we don't have any time to waste here."

"The two of you aren't from our Ten Hazards Mountain Range. I won't ask for what purpose you're visiting our city on this occasion, but please hand over the Purple Sun Warm Jade that you obtained from Guan Sheng and Hei Lang," the white-robed young man said.

"What Purple Sun Warm Jade? We were only doing some shopping here, but we didn't even get a chance to buy anything before you rushed in and killed those two!" Shi Chuankong replied with an oblivious expression.

The white-robed young man's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "In that case, please hand over your storage tools for me to examine. If there's no Purple Sun Warm Jade inside, then you two are free to leave."

"I already told you that we're in a hurry, so stop wasting our time!" Shi Chuankong objected in a cold voice.

"I can tell that both of you are quite powerful, but don't forget that this is Black Weasel City. Don't make this any harder on yourself than it has to be," the white-robed young man threatened, and all of the armorclad men immediately converged to surround Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"What a joke! I've always heard that free trade is encouraged by the Black Weasel King, but it appears that was nothing more than a lie. How disappointing," Han Li chuckled coldly.

"What did you say? How dare you slander my father!" the white-robed young man accused in a furious voice.

"How is this slander? We haven't broken any rules, yet we're being robbed here in broad daylight by the Black Weasel Army!" Han Li countered.

"I have no intentions of robbing anyone, my objective is merely to recover the stolen Purple Sun Warm Jade. If I can verify that it's not in your possession, then I'm willing to apologize," the white-robed young man harrumphed coldly, and the crimson cloud around him began to spread in all directions, encompassing both Han Li and Shi Chuankong within it.

In response, Han Li opened his mouth to release a streak of golden light, which shot forth through the air to reach the white-robed young man in a flash.

The white-robed young man was slightly taken aback by the speed of the streak of golden light, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of crimson light that caught the golden light in the blink of an eye.

The crimson light contained a crimson veil that was as thin as a cicada's wing, and it appeared to be quite a powerful treasure.

However, right at this moment, the streak of golden light suddenly transformed into twelve miniature golden swords that were several inches in length, and tiny arcs of golden lightning were flashing incessantly over them.

Before the white-robed young man had a chance to do anything, the twelve miniature swords released a burst of devastating lightning law powers that instantly tore the crimson veil into shreds before piercing directly toward the white-robed young man.

"Spare his life, Brother Li!" Shi Chuankong hurriedly yelled.

A panicked look finally appeared on the white-robed young man's face as the cloud of crimson mist quickly converged around him, attempting to keep the golden flying swords at bay while he tried to summon more treasures.

However, before he had a chance to do that, the twelve Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had already pierced through the cloud of crimson mist with ease before running straight through his body.

Twelve holes were instantly punched into his limbs, and he fell to the ground with an agonized cry and a horrified look in his eyes, while the crimson cloud around him quickly disintegrated.

Han Li paid no further heed to the white-robed young man as he swiveled around like lightning while flicking a finger through the air, releasing a miniature azure sword.

All of a sudden, a streak of golden swordlight appeared without any warning before hurtling directly toward him, only to be stopped cold in its tracks by the miniature azure sword.

A resounding metallic clang rang out, and the space near the two swords trembled warped as the pair of swords grated against each other, with neither able to get the better of the other.

A stunned look appeared on the azure-robed woman's face, while Han Li harrumphed coldly, "Your sword is not bad, but the wielder is too weak!"

Before the azure-robed woman had a chance to do anything, a burst of sharp pain suddenly speared through her mind, as if a red hot poker had been plunged into her head, and she gave a muffled groan, while her entire body involuntarily stiffened.

Han Li pounced on this opportunity to rush over to the azure-robed woman before placing a finger against her glabella before releasing an arc of golden lightning.

The azure-robed woman let loose an agonized howl as her entire body was instantly charred black, and she fell to the ground in an unconscious state.

Her golden sword also fell to the ground with a loud clang, and the radiant golden light emanating from it faded away.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li had subdued two High Zenith cultivators, and all of the Black Weasel Army cultivators could only look on in astonishment.

Right at this moment, Han Li turned his gaze to the Black Weasel Army cultivators before giving another cold harrumph, and all of them immediately threw their hands over their heads as they let loose agonized howls.

Han Li flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession, releasing around a dozen arcs of golden lightning that struck the Black Weasel Army cultivators with unerring accuracy, and their bodies were also charred black as they crumpled to the ground in an unconscious state.

Unleashing the Spirit Stun Thorn secret technique in succession had also been quite taxing on Han Li's spiritual sense, and his complexion had turned slightly pale, but he quickly recovered after taking a deep breath, then turned his gaze to the stunned white-robed young man.

The man opened his mouth to say something, but Han Li merely flicked a finger in his direction to release an arc of golden lightning that struck him on the forehead, instantly knocking him out as well.

"That was beyond impressive, Fellow Daoist Li, but it looks like we have no choice but to leave the city now," Shi Chuankong said with a wry smile.

"We've already achieved our objective, so there's no reason for us to stay anyway," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Chapter 792: Shifting Allegiance

Around fifteen minutes later.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were quickly making their way toward the northern city gate.

If it weren't for the fact that they didn't want to attract any attention to themselves, they would've already defied the flight prohibitions in the city and taken to the skies.

"It looks like we're going to have a rough journey from here onward," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

"Who could've anticipated that we would run into the Black Weasel Army? Then again, we never intended to stay here for long anyway, so I suppose it makes no difference," Shi Chuankong sighed.

All of a sudden, both of them stopped cold in their tracks before looking directly forward with apprehensive looks on their faces.

A refined young scholar was currently making his way toward them through the bustling crowd up ahead, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong could only exchange a wry smile at the sight of the young man.

Even though this was their first meeting, they were able to instantly identify the man as none other than the Black Weasel King.

The Black Weasel King was walking along at a leisurely pace with a placid look on his face, and he wasn't giving off even the slightest aura fluctuations, as if he were nothing more than a harmless mortal.

He was holding a book in one hand, and he extended a slight bow toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong as he said, "What an honor it is to have you in our city, Your Highness."

A warm smile appeared on Shi Chuankong's face, and he returned the bow as he said, "The honor is all mine, Senior."

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed, and he remained silent as he also extended a slight bow.

"It's hardly fitting for us to be talking in the middle of the street. How about we go and take a seat in my palace?" the Black Weasel King invited with an earnest smile.

Refusal clearly wasn't an option here, so Shi Chuankong replied, "Please pardon our intrusion."

The Black Weasel King made an inviting hand gesture, then swept a sleeve through the air, and a burst of black light appeared beneath the feet of all three of them.

In the next instant, they found themselves in an enormous garden that was filled with strange and exotic plants and rocks.

There was also a bamboo forest that was filled with birds and interspersed with many pavilions and pergolas, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

As they made their way deeper into the garden, the scenery began to change, and it felt as if they were making their way through the seasons, starting from the colorful vibrancy of spring before ending in the white snowscape of winter.

"I had always heard that there was an exceptionally beautiful garden in your palace that was home to scenery from all four seasons, and it's certainly lived up to its reputation, Senior Black Weasel," Shi Chuankong said.

"This is nothing compared with the scenery of Night Sun City," the Black Weasel King said in a modest manner, but the look in his eyes indicated that he was very pleased with Shi Chuankong's compliment.

Neither of them mentioned the conflict that had just taken place back at Guan Sheng's shop, and they continued to chat amicably with each other as they arrived in front of a red building.

"Your Highness, I would like to chat with you in private in the Bell Spirit Palace. Can we get Fellow Daoist Li to have some tea and wait for us in the Spring Water Palace in the meantime?" the Black Weasel King asked.

Han Li turned to Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, and the latter gave him a silent nod.

"We'll do as you say, Senior Black Weasel," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

With that, Han Li was led by a beautiful palace maiden to the Spring Water Palace, while Shi Chuankong accompanied the Black Weasel King to the Bell Spirit Palace.

Upon Han Li's arrival in the Spring Water Palace, some tea had already been prepared for him, and he sat down for a sip.

Meanwhile, in the Bell Spirit Palace.

Shi Chuankong and the Black Weasel King made their way into the palace together, and Shi Chuankong's expression remained calm and composed, but his palms were sweating profusely.

He looked around to discover that the interior of the palace resembled a study, and that around two thirds of the palace was taken up by large wooden bookshelves that were laden with hundreds of thousands of books.

A brief glance at the bookshelves told Shi Chuankong that most of the books were poem anthologies and other such works of mortal literature, and there were barely any cultivation arts among them.

On top of that, there were also some elegantly framed pieces of calligraphy hanging on the walls, most of which also consisted of ancient poem phrases and some Buddhist and Daoist mantras. As for the handwriting, it could only be referred to as stable and consistent, but there wasn't a lot of flair.

Shi Chuankong suppressed his apprehension as he praised, "Your calligraphy is just as refined as your taste for literature, Senior Black Weasel."

"There are far too few people who can appreciate good calligraphy in this primordial mountain range. What a breath of fresh air it is to have someone like you here," the Black Weasel King replied with a pleased expression.

"Regarding the conflict that we had with your son, I am truly..."

The Black Weasel King waved a hand to cut Shi Chuankong off before he had a chance to finish.

"It's fine, it was just a minor run-in. I certainly didn't invite you to my palace over such a petty matter," the Black Weasel King said with a meaningful expression.

"In that case, may I ask why you invited me here?" Shi Chuankong asked.

The Black Weasel King strode over to a bookshelf and set down the book that he was holding, then replied, "Right now, Night Sun City and even the entirety of the Holy Realm has been stirred up into a state of chaos over the matter of inheritance, and many powers are being forced to make choices. Our Ten Hazards Mountain Range has never been regarded with much importance, but when the time comes, we'll inevitably be affected as well, so I have no choice but to make plans early."

"I never had any intention of throwing my hat in the ring when it comes to the matter of inheritance, and I certainly didn't think that it would cause such a massive stir," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"A bright jewel will inevitably shine no matter where it is. Even if you hadn't returned to the Holy Realm, you still wouldn't have been able to escape scrutiny, Your Highness," the Black Weasel King said with a meaningful smile.

"What do you mean by that, Senior Black Weasel?" Shi Chuankong asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Everyone knows that among the Holy Monarch's thirteen sons, the eldest prince, Shi Zhanfeng, commands the most power, and that the only one who can contend with him is the third prince, Shi Pokong, the prince that possesses the greatest aptitude. You and the third prince share the same mother, so the two of you are extremely close, and everyone knows that you'll be sure to pledge your allegiance to him," the Black Weasel King said.

"I see, so you're planning to pledge your support to my brother through me, is that right, Senior Black Weasel?" Shi Chuankong asked with an enlightened expression.

"When I first received the eldest prince's orders to hunt you down, I was planning to bet on him. After all, the compensation that he promised me was too handsome to ignore. However, I began to change my mind after I learned that you and your servant slew both Tie Yu and Tong Yu," the Black Weasel King continued.

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he knew that the Black Weasel King had misinterpreted Han Li's status. At the same time, he suddenly recalled that Han Li had mentioned sensing another powerful aura as they were fleeing from the Golden Rhinoceros King, and he asked, "Senior Black Weasel, was it you who helped us escape from the Golden Rhinoceros King on the border?"

"That's right. I had already been keeping tabs on you prior to that, and my initial plan was to wait for the Golden Rhinoceros King to crush you before swooping in to claim the spoils. However, after seeing you escape from him on two separate occasions, I changed my mind and decided to save you so that I can throw my support behind the third prince. However, now..."

The Black Weasel King's voice suddenly trailed off here, and Shi Chuankong immediately tensed up, only to then relax again.

At this point, the situation really couldn't get much worse.

"Now that I've met you, I've decided to place my bets on you," the Black Weasel King chuckled.

Shi Chuankong was astonished to hear this, and he was stunned into silence for a moment before asking, "Why?"

"Would you believe me if I told you that I was doing it on a hunch?" the Black Weasel King asked.

Shi Chuankong immediately shook his head in response, and he was just about to say something when the Black Weasel King continued, "You possess immense potential, but it's still yet to show. On top of that, the fact that you have such a powerful servant by your side and the lengths that the eldest prince has gone to in order to hunt you down are also very telling signs."

"Your courage is very admirable, Senior Black Weasel," Shi Chuankong praised with a smile.

"Now that I've made my intentions clear, let's discuss some more concrete matters," the Black Weasel King said.

……

Close to half a day passed by in a flash.

Han Li remained seated in the Spring Water Palace the entire time, and he was approached by no one with the exception of a few beautiful palace maidens, who refilled his cup whenever he finished the tea inside.

He appeared calm and collected on the surface, but internally, he was feeling very concerned.

Right as he was about to run out of patience and break out of the palace, Shi Chuankong and the Black Weasel King made their way into the palace, looking like a pair of old friends.

"It's not every day that our Black Weasel City gets to entertain such esteemed guests, so why don't you stay for a while so I can show some hospitality? I'll make the arrangements for you to leave the Ten Hazards Mountain Range safely," the Black Weasel King said with a smile.

"We'll be in your care then, Senior Black Weasel," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile of his own, and he and Han Li were arranged a place to stay in the palace.

Chapter 793: Passing By the Vast Origin House

Han Li naturally had his reservations about the Black Weasel King, but he didn't ask any questions.

Initially, he had thought that it was his breakthrough that had attracted the attention of the Ten Hazards, but he had since realized that things weren't so simple, and that it seemed like Shi Chuankong was the one actually being targeted.

Shi Chuankong's status was most likely the reason why the Black Weasel King was being so polite and amicable to him, but Shi Chuankong seemed to have no intention of explaining himself, and Han Li didn't feel it appropriate to ask.

In any case, his best option was to follow Shi Chuankong's lead in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and everything else could wait until they were out of the mountain range.

Three days later, Han Li set off for the city north of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, Preeminent City, along a secret trade route established between Black Weasel City and Preeminent City.

Several months later.

In the southern region of the Devil Realm was an extremely steep and long mountain range that stood between the Ten Hazards Mountain Range and the Vast Seal Plains, and at the center of the mountain range was a col where a massive city wall had been constructed.

The wall was constructed from giant black stone blocks that were etched with complex patterns, and it was enshrouded within a layer of faint thin gray mist. Hanging on top of the wall was a huge plaque that read "Preeminent City", and below the plaque was a massive archway, as well as two smaller gates on either side.

The main gate and the one on the left were both shut, leaving only the right one open, and there were some armorclad guards standing on lookout duty there.

There were very few pedestrians near the gate, and at this moment, there were two people slowly approaching the city together.

One of them had an imposing physique, with dark skin and a set of rough facial features. There was a single black horn on his forehead, and he was clad in a suit of leather armor. His companion was much more similar to a human in appearance, except there were some golden scales on his cheeks.

"Brother Shi, why did we part ways with the merchant convoy the Black Weasel King arranged for us instead of entering the city with them?" the man with the golden scales on his face asked.

"There have always been business dealings between Preeminent City and the Black Weasel King, but it's all done in secret under the table, and given our sensitive identities, it would be best for us to not get involved in all of that," the imposing man replied.

These two were none other than Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and before long, they arrived at the city gate, where they were stopped by the armorclad guards.

"Show us your passage tokens," one of the armorclad guards demanded as he reached out a hand.

Shi Chuankong flipped a hand over to produce a pair of palm-sized black jade badges before handing them over.

The armorclad guard accepted the badges, and after giving them a close examination, he said, "These are passage tokens issued by the Serene Mountain Marquis Manor. Why have you come all this way to Preeminent City?"

"We're here to run some errands for our masters, so we don't really have a choice in the matter, do we?" Shi Chuankong sighed.

"Alright, you can go in," the armorclad guard said as he returned the jade badges to Shi Chuankong.

Upon entering through the city gate, Shi Chuankong handed one of the jade badges to Han Li as he said, "We'll be using these things a lot in Preeminent City, so you should carry one too."

"What's this Serene Mountain Marquis Manor?" Han Li asked as he accepted the jade badge.

"Our Holy Realm is different from the Immortal Realm in that it's primarily ruled over by my father, and there are many nobles under him who rule over different areas, one of whom is the Serene Mountain Marquis," Shi Chuankong explained.

"Seeing as you're the son of the Devilish Monarch, you must have a very high noble title, right?" Han Li asked.

"Bloodline is very important in our Holy Realm, but power is championed above all else, so in order to attain the highest noble titles, one has to at least be at the Great Encompassment Stage and have a certain amount of accolades or backing. At the moment, I have no territory of my own, nor any official title, but I'm able to draw upon a great deal of the Vast Origin House's resources," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

The city wall was far thicker than Han Li imagined, and even the passageway leading into the city from the gate was over a thousand feet in length.

Upon emerging from the passageway, the natural light immediately returned, making them feel as if they had stepped out in a whole new world.

However, as soon as Han Li set foot in the city, his brows immediately furrowed slightly.

The devilish qi in Preeminent City was several times more abundant than it was outside the city.

Han Li had noticed that the further north they traveled, the more abundant the devilish qi in the environment had become, but he still wasn't prepared for such a drastic change just from crossing a single city wall.

"Back when Preeminent City was first constructed, array masters were hired to bolster its walls in order to keep in as much devilish qi as possible. Hence, once we leave the city and go further northward, the devilish qi will actually be less abundant," Shi Chuankong assured, looking rather amused at Han Li's discomfort.

"In contrast with Preeminent City, the Ten Hazards Mountain Range really is a primordial area with sparse devilish qi," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Are you feeling alright? If the discomfort becomes too severe, I have a Qi Locking Pill that can lock away the devilish qi that you absorb into your body," Shi Chuankong said.

"It's still fine for now," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"I suppose this amount of devilish qi won't be much of a bother for a High Zenith cultivator like yourself," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

Beyond the city gate was a spacious plaza, branching off from which was a paved stone road that led to the center of the city. The road was lined with buildings constructed in an orderly fashion, and the closer one drew to the center of the city, the taller the buildings became.

The construction style of Preeminent City was quite unique, with most of the buildings constructed out of giant black stone blocks, and the roofs were primarily domed or conical in shape. On top of that, there were many intricate decorative statues on the walls and roofs of the buildings, the most prevalent of which were statues of different strange and exotic beasts, presenting some spectacular sights to behold.

There were very few shops lining the streets near the city gate, and most of them were small trading houses where business appeared to be very slow. However, as one made their way deeper into the city, they'd discover that the streets would gradually become more lively and bustling.

"Are we going straight to the city lord's manor to use the teleportation arrays from here?" Han Li asked.

"There's no hurry. There's a Vast Origin House branch in Preeminent City, let's go there first," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response, and the two of them hailed a beast-drawn carriage, which promptly set off northward.

Along the way, Han Li spotted a large cluster of tall buildings within a lush garden, and he asked, "Is that the city lord's manor?"

"That's right, and the current city lord is the Heavenly Ax Marquis," Shi Chuankong replied.

"A marquis is serving as the city lord?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Normally, the role of city lord would be undertaken by a baron at most. However, Preeminent City is different in that it's responsible for keeping the threat of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range at bay, which is quite a heavy responsibility, and that's why a marquis is serving as the city lord. On top of Preeminent City, a large area to the north of the city is also under his jurisdiction," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

After passing by the city lord's manor, the carriage continued northward, making its way onto a very wide and opulent street.

The street was lined with shops that were selling all types of different wares, and it was far more crowded here than elsewhere in the city, so the carriage was forced to slow down.

The coach driver began introducing to his two passengers some of the shops on the streets with the intention of recommending them to the shops that paid him a commission, but he quickly discovered that one of his passengers was already extremely familiar with the city, so he wisely chose not to put in any recommendations.

Along the way, Shi Chuankong gave Han Li an introduction to many of the shops that he passed by, further demonstrating his knowledge of the city.

"How are you so familiar with Preeminent City, Brother Shi?" Han Li asked.

"Back when I first got involved with the Vast Origin House, Preeminent City was where I started, and that's why I know so much about the Ten Hazards Mountain Range," Shi Chuankong explained through voice transmission.

"I see, so this is a starting point for you," Han Li replied with a nod.

"You could say that," Shi Chuankong agreed with a smile.

As the two of them were conversing with each other, a seven-story building with a conical roof appeared up ahead. The building was adorned with elegant carvings and all types of complex patterns, and there was a plaque outside that read "Vast Origin House".

However, to Han Li's surprise, Shi Chuankong only took a glance at the entrance of the Vast Origin House, then cast his gaze forward once again and instructed the coach driver to continue onward.

"Why aren't we going in?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

A hesitant look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

"Brother Shi, I may have agreed to accompany you to Night Sun City, but that's not the only option available to me. If you're intentionally keeping secrets from me, then I'm afraid that we'll have to part ways here," Han Li warned.

"Please don't jump to conclusions, Brother Li. I'll explain everything to you once we've found a place to settle down in," Shi Chuankong sighed.

Han Li offered no reply, merely nodding silently in response.

Chapter 794: Allaying Suspicions

The two of them remained silent as the carriage made its way to the end of the street before turning into an alley.

At the entrance of the alley, Shi Chuankong instructed the coach driver to stop, then asked Han Li to wait for him for a moment before stepping off the carriage himself and making his way toward an extremely small shop at the end of the alley.

The shop had no visible signage with the exception of a cloth banner that read "Traveler House", and after a few minutes, Shi Chuankong emerged from the shop before returning to the carriage.

From there, the carriage traveled eastward before arriving at an inn called the Cloud Mountain Inn.

The inn was situated in a rather secluded location in the eastern region of the city, and it was surrounded by lush forest. There were more trees than buildings in the area, and the inn itself had a rather antiquated appearance.

After paying the carriage fare, Shi Chuankong pushed open a wooden door with peeling paint and led Han Li into the courtyard.

Upon entering the courtyard, Han Li felt the surrounding space ripple slightly, following which he suddenly found himself standing in a spacious garden.

There was a flowing creek nearby, as well as an elegant covered bridge arching over a small lake, presenting a beautiful sight to behold.

A seductive woman who looked no different from a normal human emerged from the inn before asking, "How can I help you?"

"Are the Serene Lotus Courtyard and the Wicker Comb Courtyard still vacant?" Shi Chuankong.

The woman faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "The Serene Lotus Courtyard is still vacant, but the Wicker Comb Courtyard is currently occupied by a permanent resident. As an alternative, may I suggest the Green Sorrow Courtyard?"

Only after hearing the woman's response did Shi Chuankong recall that the Wicker Comb Courtyard was permanently reserved for him, and he slapped a hand to his own forehead as he chuckled, "Oh, I forgot about that. In that case, we'll take the two vacant courtyards."

With that, Shi Chuankong dismissed the woman, then led Han Li over the covered bridge before making their way deeper into the inn. Along the way, they could see a series of well-constructed courtyards that were encompassed within arrays.

Shi Chuankong accompanied Han Li through a bamboo forest, and the two of them arrived at Green Sorrow Courtyard, which contained a two-story building.

Using the token given to him by the woman, Han Li opened the restriction around the courtyard before stepping inside.

The first floor of the building was a guest hall, attached to which was an inner room and an outer room, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong sat down at a round table in the inner room.

Han Li made a hand seal to conjure up a light barrier around the room, then said, "Alright, now we can talk."

"Brother Li, I... I'm honestly not sure where to start," Shi Chuankong said after a brief silence.

"Then start from when the Golden Rhinoceros King began coming after us. Initially, I thought that my breakthrough had attracted his attention, but judging from the events that transpired after that, I presume things aren't that simple, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"You're correct, Brother Li. The Golden Rhinoceros King's target was me, and he was hunting me under orders from my brother, the eldest prince," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"Why is your brother trying to kill you?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'm afraid I can't reveal all of the details to you. All I can tell you is that it concerns an inheritance that is of the utmost importance to our Holy Race. My brother is most likely under the impression that I pose a threat to his claim over the inheritance, and that's why he colluded with the Golden Rhinoceros King to hunt me down," Shi Chuankong replied.

"You're related by blood, are you not? Why is he going so far?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Countless brothers have been pitted against each other throughout history in the face of significant inheritances. On top of that, we only share the same father, but have different mothers. This isn't the first time that something like this has happened, but in the past, I've never been targeted. After all, a mere Golden Immortal like myself poses no real threat to him," Shi Chuankong replied with a self-deprecating smile.

"Clearly, something must've happened to convince him that you do pose a threat to him now, is that right?" Han Li said in a meaningful voice.

Shi Chuankong already knew the answer to this question, and he replied, "It's most likely because I recovered the Virata Lute, and it certainly didn't help that my father was willing to save me from the Gray Realm at the expense of a vast amount of resources."

"I presume the latter had more of an impact than the former," Han Li mused.

"Perhaps. Even when my brothers and sisters have encountered severe peril in the past, my father has rarely ever intervened. Perhaps this incident convinced my brother that our father is considering me as the recipient of the inheritance," Shi Chuankong said.

"I don't think he's the only one who thinks that. I've been wondering why the Black Weasel King was willing to help us even after the trouble that we caused in his city. He must be placing his bets on you, right?" Han Li asked.

"You truly possess a keen eye like no other, Brother Li. That is indeed what the Black Weasel King told me," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Now that your brother has decided to come after you, I'm sure there will only be more trouble to come. Why didn't we return to Night Sun City right away using the teleportation array in the city? Surely we'd be safer once we return to Night Sun City. Could it be that you don't trust the Heavenly Ax Marquis?" Han Li asked.

"Back when I was last at Preeminent City, the Heavenly Ax Marquis still wasn't the city lord. Instead, he only took over the role during my absence. I paid a visit to the Vast Origin House branch earlier to see if the circumstances in Preeminent City have changed, and sure enough, there was a secret warning symbol outside the building.

“All of my trusted subordinates have already been cleansed from the branch, and that tells me that the city lord's manor is no longer a safe haven for me," Shi Chuankong explained.

"In that case, why are we staying here instead of leaving right away?" Han Li asked.

"My brother previously contacted the Black Weasel King, instructing him to intercept us. However, now that the Black Weasel King has chosen to help me, he'll be issuing a false report to my brother, claiming that we're still on the run in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, so Preeminent City is still safe for now," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"I presume that's not the only reason you decided to stay in Preeminent City, right? Did you visit that shop in the alley earlier to request reinforcements?" Han Li asked.

"I went there to send a message to another brother of mine, the third prince. He'll be sending reinforcements to us, and in the meantime, we'll stay here in this inn," Shi Chuankong confirmed with a nod.

"Is this brother of yours trustworthy?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"You can rest assured of that, Brother Li. My third brother and I share the same mother, and I once saved his life. If I can't trust him, then there's no one I can trust in the entire Holy Realm," Shi Chuankong replied in a confident manner.

Han Li nodded in response.

"I'll admit that I was at fault for keeping this from you, but there were some very sensitive circumstances at play, so I had to be careful, I hope you can understand. Even though we haven't known each other for long, we've been through a lot together, and I have a great deal of trust in you," Shi Chuankong said as he rose to his feet before extending a solemn salute toward Han Li.

"Truth be told, I really don't want to get involved in your family matters. However, our lives are intertwined on this journey back to Night Sun City, so I'll do everything in my power to protect you. Having said that, please don't keep any more secrets from me," Han Li said in a serious voice.

"Rest assured, Brother Li, I've already told you everything, and I'll be sure to do everything in my power to fulfill the request that you made to me once we arrive at Night Sun City," Shi Chuankong promised.

After that, the two of them chatted for a while longer before Shi Chuankong departed, and after sitting in silence for a moment, Han Li made his way up to the second floor of the building.

There, he set up a restriction in a silent cultivation chamber before conjuring up a door of silver light and stepping into the bamboo building in the Flower Branch domain.

The second floor of the bamboo building was where Mo Guang had previously stayed, but at this moment, the room was occupied by Weeping Soul.

She was laying on the bed with pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade hovering above her, giving off gentle energy fluctuations.

At this moment, her expression was very peaceful, and her breathing was slow and even. Her entire body was enshrouded in a layer of faint purple light, and it looked as if she were merely sleeping, but she showed no signs of waking up.

After replacing the low-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade in the array with ones of the mid-grade variety, Weeping Soul's condition had somewhat improved, but it wasn't enough to replenish her lost essential energy, so she still remained unconscious.

Han Li had given Shi Chuankong most of the mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade that they had obtained, and he had kept both of the pieces of high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade for himself.

However, he knew that this didn't address the problem at its roots, so even high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade wouldn't be enough to cure Weeping Soul's condition.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie's voice suddenly rang out from outside the bamboo building.

"Can I come in, Fellow Daoist Li?"

Han Li immediately made his way down to the first floor upon hearing this, then invited Daoist Xie into the room, and the two of them sat down at a bamboo eight immortal table.

As soon as Daoist Xie sat down at the table, Han Li immediately noticed that there was a hesitant look on his face, in contrast with his normal perpetually neutral expression.

"Is something wrong, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Recently, a certain name has been frequently popping up in my mind, and I feel like it may have something to do with my former owner," Daoist Xie replied.

"What's the name?" Han Li asked.

"Scalptia Spatial Domain," Daoist Xie replied.

The name didn't ring any bells for Han Li, and he asked, "What's that?"

"I'm not sure myself, but the phrase has been frequently appearing in my mind of late," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

"It sounds like some type of secret area... How is this place related to your former owner?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Chapter 795: Time is Ever-present

"Ever since we arrived in the Devil Realm, memories pertaining to my former owner have begun appearing in my mind. It seems like my former owner came from the Devil Realm, and this Scalptia Spatial Domain seems to be somehow related to him, but I'm not sure exactly what the nature of the correlation is," Daoist Xie replied.

"Are you saying that your former owner was a devilish being?" Han Li asked.

This made sense, considering he first met Daoist Xie in the Devilish Origin Sea, which was the equivalent of the Devil Realm, but as a lower realm. [1]

"That's right. However, at some point in his life, he traveled to the Immortal Realm for some reason, and he once served as a puppet refinement master in the Hundred Creation Mountain," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

"I'll try to do some digging into this Scaptia Spatial Domain. Seeing as the term only began appearing in your mind after our arrival in the Devil Realm, it most likely has something to do with the Devil Realm. If you recover any other memories, make sure to tell me. I agreed to fulfill the dying wishes of your former owner, and I fully intend to keep that promise," Han Li said.

Daoist Xie nodded in response before departing, leaving Han Li to sit in the bamboo building on his own with a contemplative look on his face.

Ever since he set foot into the True Mantra Sect ruins, things had become very hectic for him, and it seemed like he was being swept from place to place without any control over his own fate.

Back in the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, he had broken through a bottleneck in the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, but he never had a chance to consolidate on the breakthrough, so he still hadn't achieved full mastery of the fifth level.

As for the five time-attribute cultivation arts from the True Mantra Sect, his progress in them was still rather lackluster with the exception of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

Even back in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, he had sensed that there was some type of connection between the Mantra Axis Scripture, the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, and the Water Divination Time Arts.

After that, he had obtained the Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture and the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome, and he was confident that these two cultivation arts also had to be connected to the aforementioned three.

If I'm going to be staying here for some time anyway, I may as well take this time to work on these cultivation arts and consolidate my cultivation base.

With that in mind, Han Li closed his eyes and sat down to meditate.

The Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome left to him by Immortal Lord Hot Flame surfaced in his mind, and this was the first time that he was going to truly closely examine the cultivation art.

Just like the other time-attribute cultivation arts, the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome also had nine levels, and it was most similar to the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

Similar to the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture's Illusory Dawn Sand Domain, the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome had a Time Severing Fire Domain, within which all time would come to a standstill.

As opposed to a time-slowing effect, the flow of time within the domain was brought to a complete halt. However, its effective area of influence was rather limited, but the area could be gradually expanded as one progressed through the levels of the cultivation art.

After some contemplation, Han Li decided against pursuing the cultivation art right away.

Instead, the Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture surfaced in his mind.

Back when he first obtained the cultivation art, he had only roughly examined it, and he didn't get a chance to go through it in detail.

After some close examination, Han Li discovered that this cultivation art was quite different from the other ones. Even though it was also a time-attribute cultivation art, it wasn't on with much offensive application in battle. Instead, the objective was to manifest an Eastern Divine Tree.

The seasonal changes within a certain area around the location where the tree was planted would be entirely under the control of the cultivator, and it was also very potent in suppressing the powers of plant spirits.

However, Han Li wasn't very interested in its suppressive effects. After all, his Essence Fire Raven was already the natural bane of all plant spirits. Hence, he was much more interested in the cultivation art's primary effect.

If he could control the passage of the four seasons within a certain area, then didn't that mean that he would be able to accelerate the passage of the four seasons, thereby speeding up the growth of spirit plants?

If that were the case, then if he could plant an Eastern Divine Tree in his spirit medicine garden, then he would be able to mature all of the spirit plants in a large area. The effect definitely wouldn't be as pronounced as that of the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, but the effective area would be much larger.

All of a sudden, Han Li recalled that there was one part of the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture that had perpetually stumped him, despite his best efforts. After carefully reading through the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome, he discovered that there was a section of the cultivation art that seemed to offer a solution to the bottleneck that he was facing in the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

With that in mind, he hurriedly put his theory to the test, and several hours later, his eyes sprang open as an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

Sure enough, he was right!

At the same time, a hint of befuddlement welled up in his heart. These five cultivation arts were all time-attribute cultivation arts, yet they specialized in different areas, and each of them also corresponded with the five elements. Could it be that the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra was a combination of all five cultivation arts?

As soon as this thought sprang into his mind, he immediately closed his eyes again and began examining the five cultivation arts one by one, starting from the Mantra Axis Scripture, which was the one that he was most familiar with.

Time slowly passed by, and day transitioned into night before turning into day once again.

Han Li had remained seated in meditation the entire night, and right at this moment, he slowly opened his eyes as a wry smile appeared on his face.

None of the five cultivation arts were easy to understand, and trying to connect them was like trying to connect loose ends in a tangled ball of yarn. Seeing as he wasn't able to make any progress in this endeavor, he decided to set it aside for now and turn his attention to cultivating the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome and the Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture in the hope that this would yield some positive outcomes.

After making up his mind, Han Li didn't hesitate any longer, and he promptly took a pill before channeling the mantra of the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome, upon which layers of red ripples instantly began to spread from his body.

……

Over three months flew by in a flash.

Inside the bamboo building in the Flower Branch domain, Han Li had already awakened from his state of cultivation, and he was pacing back and forth with his hands clasped behind his back.

Moments later, he emerged from the bamboo building with tightly furrowed brows and stepped out into the courtyard outside.

The courtyard was teeming with spiritual qi, striking him with a sense of blissful comfort, and he made his way onto the bridge before resting a hand on the railing and looking out at the lotus leaves on the surface of the pond in an absentminded manner.

Over the past three months, he had made some initial forays into both the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome and the Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture, only to find that he was having a much harder time making progress in the two cultivation arts compared with the Water Divination Time Arts.

This wasn't because his mastery over the laws of time was insufficient. Instead, what he had noticed was that while the five cultivation arts were connected in many ways, there were also many conflicting elements to them as well.

In particular, the immortal spiritual power circulation method that complied with the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture conflicted with that of the Water Divination Time Arts, and similarly, what worked for the Mantra Axis Scripture and the Water Divination Time Arts came in direct conflict with the Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture.

In summary, if he couldn't find some type of balance, then there would be no way to pursue all five cultivation arts at once.

Han Li was feeling rather frustrated, like he had walked into a dead-end, and he was wondering if he should abandon his current pursuit. If worse came to worst, he would just have to pursue the five cultivation arts independently, and at the very least, he wanted to achieve full mastery of the Mantra Axis Scripture first.

With that in mind, he suddenly recalled that the bamboo slip that contained the nine levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture also included a very strange text titled "Sumeru Insights".

"How could I have forgotten about that?" Han Li exclaimed as he slapped a hand to his own forehead.

He then immediately flipped a hand over to summon a bamboo slip, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he hurriedly made his way back into the bamboo building before closing the door.

……

Several more months passed by in seclusion, and during this time, Shi Chuankong had come to visit him once, but departed after learning that Han Li was in seclusion.

However, prior to his departure, he had requested Daoist Xie to inform Han Li to come and see him as soon as he came out of seclusion.

Han Li had been staying in the bamboo building over the entire duration of his time his seclusion, and on this day, he finally emerged.

This time, he was looking in far higher spirits than last time, and he performed some stretches as a faint smile appeared on his face.

He had spent most of the past few months examining Sumeru Insights, and even though it was only a text that consisted of several thousand characters, it had stumped him for quite some time.

Thankfully, his persistence had paid off, and he was finally able to glean some of the text's secrets two months ago.

Sumeru Insights was initially so difficult to understand because he had gone into it with the wrong mindset, thinking that it had to have something to do with the laws of time or time-attribute cultivation arts.

As it turned out, it was actually more like a general outline, and it was not something to be cultivated. Instead, it laid out the sequence in which one should pursue the five time-attribute cultivation arts.

Of course, it didn't just lay out a simple order for the cultivation arts. Instead, it subtly displayed the relationship between the five cultivation arts, and that was the basis upon which the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra was to be cultivated.

The five cultivation arts required one to glean the laws of time from the perspective of the five elements. After all, time affected everything in this world, and as one of the three paramount laws, the influence of the laws of time was ever-present in all things.

However, this also made the laws of time very abstract and difficult to grasp, thereby making it one of the most difficult law powers to understand and cultivate.

However, it was possible to glean the secrets of the laws of time by observing the cycle of birth and destruction of the five elements.

[1]. For more information on the Devilish Origin Sea, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2086: Devilish Origin Sea.

[Back]

Chapter 796: Waiting for the Enemy

Initially, Han Li couldn't understand why Patriarch Miro had gone to such great lengths to split the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra into five parts, but it later became apparent to him that he was most likely trying to leave behind an alternative inheritance of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra in addition to the full cultivation art recorded on the dhvaja.

If it weren't for this precautionary measure, the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra would've already been completely lost, and Han Li couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh at this sobering thought.

Over the past two months, he had arranged the five cultivation arts in accordance with Sumeru Insights to compile a brand new Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, which consisted of nine levels.

There were still many finer details that had to be smoothed over, but overall, his work was mostly complete.

Having already made some progress in some of the time-attribute cultivation arts, he was currently roughly at the third level of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and once he gained the ability to manifest the complete set comprising the Mantra Treasured Axis, the Clear Time Vial, Illusory Dawn Sand, Time Severing Flowing Fire, and the Eastern Divine Tree, he would be able to jump straight to the sixth level.

By then, his cultivation base would also have reached the mid-High Zenith Stage.

Due to the fact that he had recompiled this cultivation art using Sumeru Insights, he didn't know how this new cultivation art was going to diverge from the original one.

However, he was definitely going to be encountering many more problems along the way than if he had access to the original Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. He was going to have to constantly switch back and forth between the five cultivation arts, and that was undoubtedly going to drastically raise the level of difficulty.

Even so, this was still an extremely alluring prospect, and he wanted nothing more than to find a quiet and peaceful location where he could cultivate in seclusion, but that was clearly not going to be possible under the current circumstances.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, and he stepped through the doorway into the pavilion in the Green Sorrow Courtyard, where Daoist Xie just so happened to be meditating.

He slowly opened his eyes and rose to his feet, then declared, "Fellow Daoist Shi came to visit a while ago, asking you to pay him a visit once you come out of seclusion."

Han Li nodded in response, then asked, "Have you recovered any more memories pertaining to your former owner's unfulfilled wish?"

"No, it's still just the phrase of Scalptia Spatial Domain that's occasionally appearing in my mind," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

"Thank you for your hard work," Han Li said as he extended a salute, and Daoist Xie returned the salute before stepping into the door of silver light.

After closing the Flower Branch domain, Han Li emerged from the pavilion before making his way toward the Serene Lotus Courtyard.

The Serene Lotus Courtyard was situated on a small island at the center of a small lake, and the surface of the lake was filled with lotus leaves.

Han Li made his way over the covered bridge toward the small island, and even before he arrived, Shi Chuankong had already come out to meet him.

"You're finally here, Brother Li," Shi Chuankong said.

"Have you rented the entire island, Brother Shi? I'm assuming you must've set up a sensory array in the lake, considering you were able to detect my arrival as soon as I stepped onto the bridge," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

"I've only set up some arrays on the island, but I've released dozens of Wave Observing Fish into the lake that detected your aura as soon as you arrived on the bridge," Shi Chuankong explained.

"Why are you suddenly being so cautious? Has something happened?" Han Li asked as he scoured the surroundings.

The entire island was concealed within a lush forest, and the greenery should've been teeming with the sound of birdsong, but the island was completely silent, clearly indicating that all of the birds had been scared away by all of the arrays that had been set up.

"I recently paid a visit to the Traveler House and received a message from my third brother," Shi Chuankong replied with tightly furrowed brows.

"What did the message say?" Han Li asked.

"It contained some good news and some bad news. The good news is that he's already sent someone to fetch us, but the bad news is that my eldest brother has most likely also been made aware of the situation," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

"If the Black Weasel King had been covering for us this entire time, then he should've been able to keep your eldest brother in the dark for about five or six months, and that much time has already elapsed. Seeing as your eldest brother has already been tipped off, then there's a very good chance that our location has been exposed, so it's just a matter of waiting to see whether the reinforcements or the enemy arrive first," Han Li said.

"Precisely, and that's why I was in such a hurry to meet you to discuss how we should proceed from here," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"Judging from the scale of this Cloud Mountain Inn, there should be people stationed here to quell potential trouble, right? As guests staying in this inn, we should be entitled to their protection," Han Li said.

"That's true, but the only concern is that the enemy could be too formidable for even the Cloud Mountain Inn to deal with. However, leaving this place would put us in even more danger, so I think it's better to stay here and wait for the enemy," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"I agree, but we should also take some additional safety precautions," Han Li said.

"What do you suggest, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

The two of them talked until dusk before Han Li finally returned to the Green Sorrow Courtyard.

Over the next few days, Shi Chuankong traveled back and forth between the inn and the shops in the city, while Han Li spent most of his time on the small island where the Serene Lotus Courtyard was situated with the exception of his nightly cultivation.

……

Half a month passed by in a flash.

One night, Han Li was meditating in the pavilion in the Green Sorrow Courtyard when he suddenly flew up into the air, hovering above the bamboo forest as he cast his gaze toward the small island.

At the same time, two streaks of light, one azure and one purple, shot forth from afar. As they approached the island, they suddenly parted ways, with the streak of azure light descending toward the island, while the streak of purple light flew directly at Han Li.

The streak of purple light arrived before Han Li in the blink of an eye, then faded to reveal a breathtakingly beautiful woman in a purple dress that perfectly hugged her delicate curves.

As the woman's gaze fell upon Han Li, a hint of disgust flashed through her eyes, but she hid it extremely well, and Han Li wouldn't have been able to catch that flash of emotion if it weren't for his exceptional abilities of observation.

"May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist?" the woman asked with a warm smile as she extended a curtsey toward Han Li.

"I was expecting a battle, so I don't really know how to react now," Han Li mused with a faint smile.

"My master's only target is the one on the island, and he has no conflict with you. As long as you're willing to stand by and watch while Sister Qing Ling takes care of business over there, my master will be sure to reward you handsomely," the woman replied.

"Well, it sounds like I'm truly blessed to be in this situation then," Han Li said as his smile widened a little.

"Once everything is said and done here, why don't you return with us to Night Sun City? My master..."

All of a sudden, the woman's voice trailed off here as a resounding boom rang out nearby.

At the same time, a silver array that was over ten thousand feet tall rose up from the island at the center of the lake, and it encompassed the entire island and the lake while giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, a string of loud explosions rang out, and the lake rumbled and churned violently as large plumes of white mist were hurled up into the air. The ground beneath Han Li's feet also began to tremble along with the entire bamboo forest.

At the same time, the entire island sank to the bottom of the lake along with the silver array.

The woman immediately turned her gaze back to Han Li with a furious look on her face, yet before she had a chance to do anything, Han Li was already rushing directly at her with his Mantra Treasured Axis revolving behind him.

The golden ripples released by the axis slowed down everything that they came into contact with, and the woman instantly felt the flow of time around her slow down significantly, while her own spiritual sense also became very dull and sluggish.

Han Li immediately pounced on the opportunity as several translucent chains shot out of his glabella, then pierced straight into the woman's head.

In the next instant, the chains wove themselves into a cage in her consciousness, and trapped inside was a tiny purple figure that was struggling with all its might to break free, but in complete futility.

With the Spiritual Sense Cage in place, the woman had become immobilized, and Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis upon seeing this, then conjured up a door of silver light.

Shi Chuankong stepped out of the Flower Branch domain, and a hint of surprise appeared on his face at the sight of the woman as he remarked, "I didn't think that my brother would send his most prized concubines after me. If it wasn't for your help, I would've definitely fallen to my demise here."

"It sounds like you're quite wary of these two," Han Li remarked.

"If they hadn't decided to split up, there's no way we would've been able to divide and conquer them so easily. In any case, let's take care of her first," Shi Chuankong replied with tightly furrowed brows.

"Her soul has been trapped by me, so she's unable to resist. You can do anything that you please," Han Li replied with a nod.

Shi Chuankong was just about to make a move upon hearing this when things took an unexpected turn...

Chapter 797: Two Souls in One Body

All of a sudden, an unsettling smile appeared on the woman's face, and an azure nascent soul emerged from her shoulder before giving Han Li a resentful glare, then vanished into the woman's body.

A burst of azure light flashed over the woman's body, and one half of her head of black hair instantly turned azure in color, while the other turned purple, and the same had happened to her pupils as well.

Han Li felt a burst of tremendous spiritual sense sweep through the woman's consciousness, and his Spiritual Sense Cage was instantly eradicated without being able to pose any resistance.

"She has two souls occupying the same body!" Han Li exclaimed as he flew back in retreat.

"In the past, I only knew that these two were twin sisters who were extremely powerful with their bodies combined, even killing a Great Encompassment cultivator together, but I never knew that they had a shared body! In that case, what was it that was destroyed just now with the island?" Shi Chuankong asked with a bewildered expression.

"That was most likely some type of avatar. Given that they share the same body, their collective soul is most likely comparable in power to that of a Great Encompassment cultivator in their combined state, so make sure you don't..."

Before Han Li had a chance to finish, he was cut off by a shrill shriek.

The shriek was extremely high-pitched, and it pierced straight into his and Shi Chuankong's consciousnesses like a sharp spear, throwing their spiritual sense into disarray. At the same time, their immortal spiritual power circulation had gone completely awry, and they began to involuntarily fall out of the sky.

Han Li fought through the excruciating pain in his consciousness as he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and a burst of invisible force instantly appeared in his consciousness to ward off the sound-based attack.

As for Shi Chuankong, he had been caught completely off guard, and he plummeted straight into the bamboo forest below, seemingly having fallen unconscious.

The woman's shriek died down, and she said, "Our master wanted to spare you out of the kindness of his own heart, and that's why Sister Zi He was trying to extend you an olive branch, but you've sealed your own fate now!"

Her voice had suddenly become a little more coarse, and it was clear that it was Qing Ling who was speaking.

Han Li took a moment to compose himself, and he offered no response as he summoned eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, with all of their tips turned toward the woman.

A cold sneer appeared on the woman's face upon seeing this, and she chanted an incantation, upon which Han Li felt as if the entire world around him had been instantly plunged into darkness.

He slowly raised his head to look up, and he was greeted by the sight of two giant eyeballs, one azure and one purple, hovering up above, both of which were giving off bursts of rippling light.

As the rippling light swept over his body, he wasn't struck by any discomfort. Instead, it was a very soothing sensation, like basking in a warm spring breeze.

Enshrouded in the layers of ripples, Han Li's entire body was filled with warmth, and before he knew it, he had fallen into a very relaxed and lazy state of lethargy.

However, at this moment, restrictive bands of azure and purple light were currently appearing in rapid succession around his soul deep in his consciousness, and despite its best efforts to break free, its struggles proved to be in futility.

However, Han Li was no ordinary High Zenith cultivator, and he possessed far more willpower and spiritual sense than the woman anticipated.

Even within the ripples of light, he was still constantly shaking his head from side to side, trying to snap himself out of his stupor, and the woman was very surprised to see this.

In the past, no one below the mid-High Zenith Stage had managed to retain even a shred of mental clarity in the face of such a powerful spiritual attack, and the woman said to herself, "If we can devour his soul, our cultivation base will definitely be enhanced."

This time, it was Zi He's voice that had spoken, and Qing Ling replied in a cautious manner, "Don't get complacent. His soul is far more powerful than that of the average Jade Immortal, so we have to be on our guard here and ensure that we claim his and Shi Chuankong's head for our master. Otherwise, we'll surely be punished for losing such an important avatar."

"I'll follow your lead then, Sister," Zi He said as the woman turned her gaze to Han Li.

At this point, Han Li had already recovered from the spiritual attack, and he had restabilized himself in mid-air as he cast a wary gaze toward the woman.

"I didn't think he would be able to snap out of it on his own," Zi He remarked in a surprised manner.

After shaking off the effects of the spiritual attack, Han Li immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, launching himself at the woman at an astonishing speed, while his eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were flying ahead of him.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords reached the woman in the blink of an eye, but they were kept at bay by some type of invisible force around a hundred feet away, unable to make any further progress.

Han Li immediately activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes upon seeing this, and it was revealed to him that his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been stopped cold in their tracks by eighteen translucent spiritual sense threads that were as thin as strands of hair.

The spiritual sense threads were extending out of the woman's body, and they were wrapped tightly around the flying swords, locking them firmly into place.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at his behest, instantly snapping all of the spiritual sense threads wrapped around them.

Immediately thereafter, the eighteen flying swords continued to hurtle directly toward the woman, who remained completely unfazed as she brought her hands together in front of herself to make a strange hand seal.

A semi-transparent spirit domain instantly erupted out of her body, encompassing all of the oncoming Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

In the instant that the flying swords flew into the spirit domain, a sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart, and sure enough, in the next instant, his spiritual connection with the swords was severed.

The lightning and sword qi emanating from the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly faded, and they were left hovering in mid-air in a completely still manner.

Despite Han Li's best efforts to reestablish a spiritual connection, the eighteen swords displayed no reaction whatsoever.

The spirit domain only encompassed an area no more than several dozen kilometers in radius, yet all other spiritual sense seemed to be inhibited in this space. Not only had Han Li's spiritual connection with his flying swords been severed, his spiritual sense had also been somewhat affected.

Despite this, his expression remained unchanged as he summoned another Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, then swung it through the air to release an arc of golden lightning.

Looks like I can still control my flying swords as long as it's not with my spiritual sense.

This observation came as quite a relief to Han Li, but at the same time, he was feeling a little frustrated with himself. If he had focused on cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique, perhaps he would've already reached full mastery of the fifth level by now, and that would undoubtedly make him much better equipped to face this opponent.

However, there was no point in thinking about that now.

"Don't get distracted now," Zi He suddenly sneered in a mocking voice, and Han Li looked up to see a strange colored glass lantern flying directly toward him.

The lantern was rather antiquated in appearance, with an engraving of a peculiar-looking beast perched on each of its four corners, facing away from each other while raising their hands to the sky to support a lotus flower oil lamp up above.

There didn't appear to be any oil in the lamp, but it held a green flame that was flickering slightly.

As soon as Han Li's gaze fell upon the flame, his entire body instantly stiffened, and his attention was completely drawn to the tiny flame, as if it had some type of transfixing property.

At the same time, a giant oil lamp projection appeared in his mind, and green light flashed through the eyes of the four strange beasts below the lamp as all of them opened their mouths in unison.

Han Li shuddered internally, and he could feel his own spiritual sense rapidly seeping out before flowing into the mouths of the four peculiar beasts like wisps of smoke.

As his spiritual sense quickly faded away, the flame on the oil lamp only burned brighter and brighter, as if it were feeding on his spiritual sense as a fuel source.

"Now that the Soul Devouring Lamp has been lit in his consciousness, his spiritual sense will be completely exhausted soon, and by then, his soul will be ours to devour. In the meantime, let's go and kill Shi Chuankong," Qing Ling said.

"We'll do as you say," Zi He replied.

Even though their voices were clearly different, it still looked like a single person talking to herself while role-playing as two different people, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

With that, the woman began to descend toward Shi Chuankong in the bamboo forest below.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong remained completely still on the ground in a prone position. It seemed like he was still unconscious, and his spiritual sense fluctuations had become very feeble.

The woman raised a hand from several hundred feet away, releasing a purple and azure metal chain that shot forth through the air before piercing straight into the back of Shi Chuankong's head, pulverizing it like a ripe watermelon.

An elated smile appeared on one half of the woman's face upon seeing this, but a perplexed look appeared on the other half of her face, and Qing Ling said in a wary voice, "Something's not right... Why hasn't his nascent soul tried to escape?"

Chapter 798: My Territory

The elation on Zi He's half of the woman's face also faded upon hearing this, and before the woman had a chance to do anything, two pillars of silver light suddenly erupted out of the ground below to encompass her, instantly immobilizing her.

Countless silver runes surged out of the pillars of silver light, forming a simple array in the blink of an eye, embedded at the center of which were two antiquated silver mirrors.

Bursts of formidable spatial fluctuations were rippling over the surface of the mirror, and the silver light that was emanating from it was also imbued with tremendous law power fluctuations that completely immobilized the woman in mid-air.

Right at this moment, Shi Chuankong's body was suddenly flipped over, following which another Shi Chuankong emerged from the ground beneath the body.

At this moment, his complexion was very pale, his eyes were out of focus, and he appeared to be rather unsteady on his feet.

He had truly sustained tremendous spiritual damage earlier, knocking him unconscious, but he woke up not long after he fell to the ground thanks to a protective treasure in his possession.

However, instead of immediately reentering the battle, he had hatched a plan, leaving a false body on the ground with a fragment of his soul deposited within it, while his true body sank into the ground using a spatial secret technique before setting up this array.

Only after shaking his head vigorously was the fog in his mind somewhat lifted, and he made a strange hand seal, then pointed a finger up at the sky, releasing a streak of silver light to strike the glass lantern in the sky.

With the woman trapped within the silver array, the lantern was completely defenseless, and it shuddered violently upon being struck by the streak of silver light before careening toward the ground in an unsteady fashion.

At the same time, the lantern projection in Han Li's mind also faded, and after being released from the clutches of the lantern, Han Li involuntarily plummeted out of the sky before crashing heavily to the ground, creating a huge crater.

However, he then immediately crawled out of the crater with a deathly pale complexion and his robes drenched in sweat, looking as if he had just gone through severe overexertion.

Shi Chuankong cast his gaze toward him, and the two of them exchanged a wry smile from afar.

"Why didn't you bring out this treasure earlier, Brother Shi? That was way too close for comfort," Han Li sighed.

"I'm afraid it's not so simple, Brother Li. These Twin Heavenly Silver Mirrors are a prized treasure of my third brothers, and they only arrived at the Traveler House a few days ago via teleportation array. I'm unable to refine the mirrors, so I can only channel their power with the help of this array," Shi Chuankong explained.

"Alright, let's focus on taking care of these two first. If they manage to break free again, then we'll truly be doomed," Han Li said.

Trapped in the silver array, the woman wasn't able to move her lips, so she could only threaten through voice transmission, "Shi Chuankong, if you dare to kill us, our master will be sure to torment you for all of eternity!"

"Don't flatter yourself, you're nothing more than a plaything for my brother! Besides, will Shi Zhanfeng be willing to spare me if I let you go?" Shi Chuankong sneered.

Before the woman had a chance to say anything else, Shi Chuankong made a hand seal before pointing a finger at the array on the ground, and the two mirrors in the array swapped positions amid a flash of silver light.

The two pillars of silver light shining out of them also twisted in mid-air, and Zi He and Qing Ling let loose a collective agonized cry as their body was reduced to a pile of mincemeat by the twisting space.

The nascent souls inside the body were instantly eradicated as well, and after the pillars of silver light faded, the pulverized remains of the woman's body spilled down onto the ground.

At the same time, specks of azure and purple light began to seep out from within before dissipating in all directions.

"I don't think I've ever seen a soul as formidable as this one. Even in such terrible condition, it's still able to somewhat hold itself together," Han Li remarked in amazement as he drew the specks of azure and purple light to himself with a sweep of his sleeve.

He then made a beckoning motion to recover all of his flying swords before making his way into the bamboo forest in the distance to pick up the glass lantern as well.

The lantern had already been snuffed out at this point, and he examined it momentarily before tipping the remains of the woman's soul into it.

The runes on the glass lantern instantly lit up, releasing a burst of faint radiance that enveloped all of the specks of light.

However, shortly thereafter, the light within the lantern faded again, and all that remained were the soul remnants sealed within the lantern.

He didn't know what had just happened, so he casually stowed the lantern away.

By the time he returned to Shi Chuankong, the latter had just fished a purple storage bracelet out of the woman's remains.

After wiping away the blood and filth on the storage bracelet, he refined it before opening it to find many treasures inside, all of which required devilish qi to wield, and there were also many pills and spirit medicines that were beneficial for the soul.

"These treasures won't be of much use to you, but these pills and spirit medicines are perfect for you, Brother Li," Shi Chuankong remarked.

"Both of us have sustained severe spiritual damage during this battle, so let's split the pils and spirit medicines evenly among us. I won't take any of the treasures in the storage bracelet, but I would like that little book. Is that alright?" Han Li asked as he pointed at a thin book with a green cover.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at the cover of the book to find the words "Soul Devouring Refinement Technique" inscribed upon it, and after a brief hesitation, he nodded in response.

"I don't know what type of cultivation method this is, but seeing as it's caught your eye, you can have it."

"Thank you, Brother Shi," Han Li said with a smile as he grabbed the book for himself.

After that, the two of them split the pills, then each took some before resting for a moment.

"Not even a single guest elder from the Cloud Mountain Inn came to check on us during the course of that entire battle. In fact, the area seems eerily quiet. It looks like they've already been notified in advance," Han Li mused.

"My eldest brother has always possessed the most power and influence out of all of us, so it's no surprise that the inn would bend to his will. However, there's one more problem. Perhaps the Heavenly Ax Marquis could've pretended to be oblivious to our presence in the city prior to this, but in the wake of this massive commotion, he'll be forced to take a side," Shi Chuankong replied with tightly furrowed brows.

"Does that mean we have to leave Preeminent City?" Han Li asked.

"That's right, we have to get out of here as soon as possible," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"But isn't your third brother sending reinforcements?" Han Li asked.

"We have no choice in the matter. I'll just have to leave behind a message for him," Shi Chuankong sighed.

……

Several minutes later, two figures arrived in a secluded alley in the northern region of Preeminent City.

Both of them were dressed in scholar's robes, and they walked briskly into the alley. One of them appeared to be quite advanced in age, while the other was a young man, and they were none other than Han Li and Shi Chuankong in disguise.

At the end of the alley was a tiny shop with its door slightly ajar, revealing a dimly lit interior.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other, then rushed into the shop in unison.

All of the shelves in the shop were rather crooked and ill-maintained, with some of their contents spilling onto the ground.

Shi Chuankong paid no heed to this as he made his way straight to the back of the shop, then pressed a hand against a certain unremarkable-looking brick on the wall.

A faint crack rang out as the brick wall slowly rolled back to reveal a hidden doorway, and Shi Chuankong stepped into it first, followed immediately by Han Li.

The secret chamber behind the brick wall turned out to be just as cluttered and chaotic as the state of the shop. There was a small array inside that had already been completely destroyed, and laying beside it was a young man who appeared to have been an employee of the shop.

There were no injuries on his body, and his eyes were wide open, but they were completely devoid of light.

"His soul is completely gone. Those sisters must've gotten to him," Han Li concluded after a brief examination.

"In that case, it looks like there's no point in leaving a message here," Shi Chuankong replied in a grim voice.

"Where should we go after we leave Preeminent City?" Han Li asked.

"We'll go to Grain Mountain City. I've been there even longer than I have Preeminent City, and it's technically my territory, so it should be a little safer. On top of that, there's also a teleportation array there," Shi Chuankong replied.

"If it's your territory, then why didn't we go there right away instead of coming here?" Han Li asked.

"Everyone knows about my history in Grain Mountain City, so I thought that going straight there would've been too predictable, and I was worried that we would run into an ambush on the way. However, at this point, it hardly matters," Shi Chuankong explained with a wry smile.

"Seeing as your eldest brother has already been tipped off and sent people to Preeminent City, it should indeed be a little safer for us in Grain Mountain City," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I certainly hope so. Time is of the essence, so let's go right now," Shi Chuankong said before making his way out of the shop, and before long, the two of them had left Preeminent City through the northern city gate.

Shi Chuankong swept a sleeve through the air to summon his flying carriage, and after the two of them had flown onto the carriage, it sped away into the distance as a ball of black light at Shi Chuankong's behest.

Chapter 799: Fleeing from the Enemy

In a certain mountain range in the True Immortal Region.

The rocks in the mountain range were golden in color, and they gleamed brightly under the light of the sun, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

A streak of white light was flying over the golden mountain range at an incredible speed that was far faster than the average High Zenith cultivator, and within the streak of white light was a giant white beast that was over a hundred feet in length.

The beast's entire body looked as if it had been carved out of flawless white jade, and there were some silver markings on the top of its head.

Straddled atop the white beast's back was a golden-robed young woman who appeared to be seventeen or eighteen years of age. Her breathtaking features were framed between a head of shoulder-length golden hair, but her expression was extremely cold and forbidding.

Despite her delicate-looking frame, she was holding a giant golden scythe that was even taller than herself.

The scythe was riddled with countless squiggly golden lines that were flashing incessantly while giving off an incredibly formidable aura, as if nothing could stand in the way of this almighty weapon.

The scythe should've appeared very much out of place in the young woman's arms, but instead, they seemed to complement each other perfectly.

These two were none other than Jin Tong and the Pixiu, and both of them were far more formidable than back when they left Han Li.

Jin Tong had already reached the mid-High Zenith Stage, while the Pixiu had also reached the High Zenith Stage.

However, at the moment, both of them were looking very apprehensive. In particular, there was a clear look of fear in the Pixiu's eyes as it flew onward as quickly as it could.

Hundreds of thousands of kilometers behind them was an enormous red cloud that was flying along in hot pursuit.

The red cloud was constantly changing forms, and there projections of countless soldiers and horses could be made out within it, giving one the impression that the cloud contained a formidable army.

Deep within the cloud was a huge crimson stone platform with countless fiery spirit patterns engraved upon it, and a red-robed middle-aged man was seated atop the platform.

The man was very tall and imposing, and there was a golden crown on his head and a golden dragon embroidered onto his red robes, giving him the appearance of an emperor from a mortal empire.

At this moment, he was glowering straight ahead with a furious look on his face, and all of a sudden, he swept a sleeve through the air, upon which a layer of crimson light emerged over the surface of the stone platform.

Countless runes surged out of the layer of crimson light in a frenzy, and the surrounding red cloud instantly sped up significantly. As a result, the distance between the red cloud and the Pixiu began to rapidly dwindle, quickly shrinking down to less than a hundred thousand kilometers.

"Go faster!" Jin Tong urged with tightly furrowed brows as she swung her golden scythe viciously down onto the Pixiu's back with a resounding metallic clang.

The Pixiu yelped in pain as a layer of golden light surfaced over its body, and a pair of giant white wings that were riddled with countless spirit patterns emerged on either side of its body.

As the Pixiu flapped its wings, bursts of white air currents emerged, swirling around its body, and it also sped up significantly, but it was still far slower than the red cloud behind it.

Before, the distance between them had shrunk down to only around thirty thousand kilometers, and a cold look flashed through the red-robed man's eyes as he made a rapid string of hand seals, then pointed a finger up at the heavens.

In an astonishing turn of events, the sun in the sky instantly swelled to dozens of times its original size, and it was as if he were a deity capable of controlling the celestial bodies.

The nearby air temperature climbed drastically, and it seemed that even the very space was about to be set alight, while trees down below were all set alight, and the golden mountain range was also beginning to melt.

"Xiao Bai!" Jin Tong called out in an urgent voice, and the Pixiu immediately reacted.

The silver lines on its head began to glow radiantly, and at the same time, its opened its mouth up wide.

A burst of silver light surged out of its mouth, and the space within a radius of hundreds of kilometers up ahead immediately began to cave in violently before being sucked into its mouth, upon which its abdomen began to rapidly expand.

The collapse of the space up ahead instantly caused a massive disturbance in the space even further away, and a giant black vortex began to emerge.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of the vortex, and the Pixiu immediately shot forward at over ten times its original speed.

Right as it was about to fly out of the area within the scope of the scorching sun, the red-robed man let loose a loud roar before pointing a finger up at the sun in the sky, and countless rays of scorching white light instantly rained down upon Jin Tong and the Pixiu.

The nearby space was instantly set alight by a burst of sweltering heat, and as a result, the Pixiu was immediately slowed down significantly.

Jin Tong's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and she stomped a foot down into the air, upon which countless streaks of invisible sword qi shot out of her body.

Immediately thereafter, she opened her mouth to release a burst of blinding golden light, which fused into the streaks of sword qi in a flash, forming a vast expanse of golden light that swept through the air to clash against the scorching white light.

Golden and white light intertwined as a string of resounding explosions rang out incessantly, causing the entire nearby area to tremble and quake violently.

The golden light was clearly struggling to hold its own against the opposing white light, but it was able to put up some resistance for now.

The red-robed man gave a cold harrumph as he switched to a different hand seal before making a grabbing motion with one hand, and the sun in the sky swelled even further in size before crashing down upon Jin Tong and Xiao Bai like a gargantuan asteroid.

Even before the sun had fully descended, a burst of tremendous force had already crashed down from above, causing the nearby space to tremble and fracture.

Most of the white light around Xiao Bai's body instantly faded, while it's wings were also snapped, and it began to plummet toward the mountain range down below like a kite with its string snapped.

A cold look flashed through Jin Tong's eyes as a burst of bright golden light erupted out of her body, then formed a giant golden humanoid projection that was several hundred feet tall behind her.

The projection's facial features were rather unclear, but it was also wielding a giant scythe.

At the same time, the golden scythe in Jin Tong's had begun to glow with blinding golden radiance, while countless golden runes also surged out of it.

A dull thump rang out as all of the world's origin qi in the nearby area began to ripple violently, following which it began to funnel into the golden scythe in a frenzy.

The scythe instantly swelled even further in size, while lines of golden runes emerged on its surface.

Right at this moment, the golden projection behind Jin Tong suddenly flew forward as a streak of golden light before fusing into her golden scythe, and the golden light radiating from the scythe instantly became so bright that it was impossible to look at.

The scythe's aura has also become countless times more fearsome than before, and Jin Tong raised it before slashing it gently at the sun that was still descending out of the sky.

A streak of crescent-shaped golden light erupted out of the scythe, then struck the rapidly descending sun head-on, and the sun was instantly sliced into two, with the two halves just barely glancing past Jin Tong and Xiao Bai.

The red-robed man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, while the two halves of the sun crashed down onto the mountain range below before exploding violently.

The entire mountain range trembled as waves of white flames erupted in all directions, eradicating everything in their path.

Xiao Bai was sent flying by the shockwaves, but now that the white sun had been sliced apart, the pressure in the nearby area also faded, so it was able to stabilize itself in mid-air again.

All of a sudden, it began flying in a different direction before exhaling violently, and an enormous spatial storm erupted out of its mouth, while its bloated body quickly returned to normal.

At the same time, it was flying back at an incredible speed, even faster than when it was sucking in space earlier, and it vanished into the distance in the blink of an eye.

The spatial storm swept over the pursuing red-robed man, causing the red cloud around him to churn violently.

The red-robed man's expression darkened even further upon seeing this, and it clenched its hand into a tight fist before throwing a punch forward, unleashing a giant crimson fist projection that was several acres in size to strike the spatial storm up ahead, instantly scattering it with ease.

After that, the red-robed man swept a sleeve through the air, and the fiery cloud around him continued onward.

At this point, Jin Tong and Xiao Bai were already countless kilometers away, and the propulsion force generated by the spatial storm that had erupted out of Xiao Bai's mouth was finally completely exhausted.

Sitting on Xiao Bai's back, Jin Tong's aura had diminished significantly after unleashing that almighty attack, and the golden light around her had also become far dimmer than before.

At this moment, she was seated with her legs crossed, and the golden scythe was laying across her lap as she summoned a steady stream of treasures before stuffing them into her mouth.

As a result, her aura began to rapidly recover, while the golden light emanating from her body also gradually grew brighter and brighter.

"We can't keep going like this, Boss. Sooner or later, that bastard from the Nine Origins Temple is going to catch up to us. We don't know where our master has gone recently, but at this point, he should be back to the True Immortal Realm. Our spiritual connection with him has already recovered, so we should try and contact him for help," Xiao Bai said.

"There's no need for that. I can handle this on my own without his help," Jin Tong replied in a cold voice.

Xiao Bai couldn't help but grumble something under its breath, and even though it had made sure to be very quiet, Jin Tong still grabbed onto the scruff of its neck as she asked, "What are you muttering to yourself there?"

"Nothing, I was just thinking about how we can escape from our pursuer," Xiao Bai hurriedly replied with a sheepish smile.

"At this point, he already knows all of our tricks, so it's only going to become more dangerous for us from here onward. You should go and seek out Uncle on your own," Jin Tong said.

"I'm not leaving you, Boss. If it wasn't for your help, there's no way I would've been able to reach the High Zenith Stage so quickly. I'll admit that I'm a coward, but I definitely won't abandon you in your time of need," Xiao Bai said in a solemn voice.

Jin Tong took a surprised glance at Xiao Bai, then nodded in response and spoke no further on the subject.

"He's catching up to us again!" Xiao Bai said in an urgent voice as a pair of white wings reappeared on its back.

Chapter 800: Thriving Business Hub

Several months later.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong had arrived at a highland with black soil stretching as far as the eyes could see.

It was a very dry and arid place, and the occasional gust of wind would sweep through, raising up huge clouds of black dust.

Upon reaching this place, Shi Chuankong was clearly looking a lot more relaxed, and Han Li was also feeling quite relieved upon seeing this.

After departing from Preeminent City, the two of them had been constantly on the move. Thankfully, Shi Chuankong was quite familiar with this area, and the two of them had changed directions several times on the way here while also avoiding the usage of teleportation arrays for fear of being intercepted.

Their cautious approach appeared to be paying off, and the journey thus far proved to be quite smooth. They hadn't encountered any more of Shi Zhanfeng's forces, but nor had they received any further news from Shi Pokong.

Around two more months passed by, and on this day, two enormous mountains appeared on the horizon up ahead. Nestled between the two mountains was a black city, and Han Li could tell that it was quite a large one.

They were already deep in the highlands at this point, and the environment here had become even more unforgiving, with gusts of ferocious black wind sweeping through the air in all directions, sweeping up pieces of debris as large as small mountains. Anyone below the Nascent Soul Stage would undoubtedly be killed in this hostile environment, but of course, a storm of this degree could simply be ignored by Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

In contrast, the area in a radius of hundreds of kilometers around the city nestled between the pair of mountains was very serene and peaceful, and it seemed that the storm raging outside was being kept out by some type of restriction.

"We're finally here," Shi Chuankong declared with an elated expression.

"This is Grain Mountain City? The climate here is terrible, and the devilish qi isn't very abundant, nor are there any favorable geographic features in the area like ore mines. Why did you decide to construct a city here?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"I didn't construct Grain Mountain City, it was once inhabited by the Sand Clump Tribe. Tens of thousands of years ago, they moved away from the city, and I purchased it. It took a great deal of effort to mold it into its current form. The environment here is indeed quite hostile, but it also serves as a natural barrier of sorts, does it not?" Shi Chuankong countered with a smile.

"I don't think that's the key factor that influenced your decision. According to the map of the Devil Realm that you gave me, Grain Mountain City is situated at a point where the routes leading to several major cities meet, and it's also not far away from the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, so it's an ideal business location," Han Li analyzed.

"You truly know me better than anyone else, Brother Li!" Shi Chuankong chuckled.

"Are we just going in like this? This city may be your territory, but you've been away for a long time, so there's no guarantee that things are still the same compared with when you left it," Han Li said.

"It'll be fine. I've already contacted my trusted subordinates in the city, and they've assured me that the city is still untouched for now," Shi Chuankong replied with a confident smile.

"Alright, I'll follow your lead then," Han Li said with a nod.

As they approached the city, it began to rapidly expand in their field of view, and even though the city was made to look rather diminutive compared with the two mountains on either side of it, it was still quite an enormous and majestic city.

The walls of the city were thousands of feet tall, and streaks of light were frequently entering and exiting the city, containing different types of flying boats.

Some giant carriages had also begun appearing on the ground, and to Han Li's surprise, it appeared far more lively and bustling here than even Black Weasel City.

As Shi Chuankong gazed upon the giant city up ahead, a hint of excitement and pride began to surface in his eyes.

In order to avoid attracting attention, Shi Chuankong intentionally slowed down his flying carriage, so it took them a while to reach the edge of the city.

Looking in from the outside, the city was filled with tall buildings and orderly streets that were teeming with activity, far more so than in Black Weasel City and Preeminent City.

There were also around a dozen giant jade pillars hovering in the air above the city, and all of the pillars were etched with countless black runes, giving them the appearance of some type of array tool.

Around the pillars was an enormous black light barrier that encompassed the entire city, as well as a large area outside of it, keeping the ferocious storms at bay.

The city had eight gates situated in the east, west, south, north, southeast, southwest, northeast, and northwest. At this moment, all eight gates were open, and there were long lines of flying boats and flying carriages waiting at the gates to enter the city.

"It looks like even eight gates is still not enough. I'll have to construct a few more city gates so that people can enter and exit the city faster," Shi Chuankong murmured to himself upon seeing this.

Instead of descending onto the ground to join the line, the flying carriage flew straight toward the interior of the city at Shi Chuankong's behest.

There were many guards clad in suits of gray armor patrolling the city, and as soon as they spotted the approaching flying carriage, a group of guards immediately sprang into action, with their leader yelling, "Who goes there?"

Shi Chuankong stowed the flying carriage away, then flipped a hand over to summon a purple badge that was giving off a hazy purple glow.

The expression on the patrol commander's face instantly changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly extended a respectful bow as he said, "Please forgive me, esteemed guest."

He then pulled out a black flag and chanted a quick incantation before waving it through the air, releasing a streak of black light that vanished into the black light barrier up ahead.

An opening that was several dozen feet in size then appeared on the light barrier, and Shi Chuankong gave the patrolling guards a slight nod before flying into the city with Han Li.

There were no flight restrictions in the city, so there were many streaks of light whizzing through the air, and Shi Chuankong and Han Li mingled themselves into the crowd before flying toward the center of the city.

Shortly thereafter, the two of them arrived in front of a large manor.

This area was far away from the bustling streets, so it was very quiet, and there were no guards stationed at the entrance, only an elderly man in a long azure robe.

"It's so good to finally see you again," the azure-robed elderly man said in an emotional voice as he approached Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"Long time no see, Elder Qi," Shi Chuankong replied with a faint smile, then made a hand seal to revert back to his original appearance.

"Fellow Daoist Li, this is Elder Qi. He used to serve my mother, and he's been looking after me since I was a child, so he's most definitely trustworthy. Elder Qi, this is Fellow Daoist Li, the friend I was telling you about," Shi Chuankong introduced.

Han Li refrained from removing his disguise, and he cupped his fist in a salute toward the elderly man as he said, "It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Qi."

Even though Elder Qi was doing his best to conceal his own aura, Han Li could sense that he was at the High Zenith Stage.

However, what was even more surprising to Han Li was that even though there was devilish qi emanating from the elderly man's body, the devilish qi originated from immortal spiritual power, so the two of them were in a rather similar situation.

"Thank you for protecting our young master over the course of your journey together," Elder Qi replied in a solemn manner as he returned the salute.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Qi," Han Li said with a smile.

"There's no need for such formalities, Elder Qi, you're making Fellow Daoist Li uncomfortable. Let's go in, Brother Li," Shi Chuankong said, and the two of them were led into the manor by Elder Qi.

"Your Highness!"

"You're finally back, Your Highness!"

"Did your journey go smoothly, Your Highness?"

All of the servants in the manor immediately converged around Shi Chuankong to ask him questions, and Shi Chuankong replied to all of them with a warm smile, displaying none of the detached haughtiness one would expect to see in a prince.

"That's enough! His Highness has only just returned, and there are still many things that he needs to do, so give him some space," Elder Qi said in a stern voice.

He seemed to be a very authoritative figure here, and everyone immediately dispersed.

"Sorry about that, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said with a slightly embarrassed smile.

"What is there to apologize for? It's clear that you're very welcome and admired here," Han Li replied with a smile.

The three of them continued onward, and they arrived in a hall before taking a seat.

"Elder Qi, thank you for looking after Grain Mountain City during all the years that I've been away. I can see that the city is in far better condition than when I left it, and it's all thanks to you," Shi Chuankong said.

"You're far too kind, Young Master, I merely executed the plan that you had already devised prior to your departure. The number of shops in the city and the population have increased, but they're not all welcome, and there’s no lack of spies among them. I've been doing my best to weed them out, but the effects have been rather lackluster.

“On the surface, the city appears to be thriving, but there is already some unrest beginning to brew beneath the facade. Overall, it's nowhere near as orderly as back when you were in command, Young Master," Elder Qi replied with a sullen expression.

"If we're unable to suppress them, then let's take the opposite approach and invite them in. The entirety of the city is under my control, and if they insist on sending offerings right to my doorstep, it would be rude of me to refuse, would it not? There's no need to be concerned, Elder Qi, I'll make sure to have this taken care of," Shi Chuankong chuckled, and the sullen look on Elder Qi's face instantly faded away at the sight of Shi Chuankong's confident expression.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this. It seemed that Shi Chuankong excelled far more in business than he did in battle.

"By the way, has there been any news from my third brother?" Shi Chuankong asked.

Chapter 801: Absent

"His Highness has already informed me that reinforcements are on their way, and that they'll arrive in half a month," Elder Qi replied.

"Do you know who it was that my brother sent?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"His Highness never specified, so I'm afraid not," Elder Qi replied with a shake of his head.

Shi Chuankong was a little disappointed to hear this, but a confident look then appeared in his eyes as he said, "Regardless of who it is that my brother sent, I'm sure things will be easier for us from here onward."

Han Li was also feeling slightly more reassured upon hearing this.

"Seeing as it'll take some time for the reinforcements to arrive, let's stay here in the meantime and take care of some of the issues in the city. Fellow Daoist Li, you can take this opportunity to have a rest," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li nodded in response as he rose to his feet, and Elder Qi called over a young maidservant to take Han Li to his resting quarters.

Han Li knew that Shi Chuankong had some things to discuss with Elder Qi, so he was going to give them some privacy.

"Young Master, is this Fellow Daoist Li truly trustworthy?" Elder Qi asked as soon as Han Li departed.

"Rest assured, Elder Qi, Fellow Daoist Li is a good friend that I first encountered in the Immortal Realm, and during the time that we've been together, he's saved my life on multiple occasions, so he's definitely someone we can trust," Shi Chuankong replied.

Elder Qi's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, but he then said, "That's good to hear, but he's a little too weak at only the early-High Zenith Stage. I'll arrange a few more guards for you to ensure your safety."

"That's even less of a concern, Elder Qi. We have many powerful cultivators under our command, but I can assure you that no one would be a match for him in battle. Fellow Daoist Li and the reinforcements sent by my brother will be enough to keep me safe. Having too many people around me could work to my detriment," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Elder Qi's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but before he had a chance to protest, Shi Chuankong declared, "Alright, that's enough on that, tell me about the spies you mentioned earlier."

Elder Qi could only heave a resigned sigh before delivering his report.

Meanwhile, Han Li was led to a courtyard at the back of the manor. The place wasn't very large, nor was it very opulent, but it was very quaint and peaceful.

"This is where you'll be staying, Senior. Please call upon me if you need anything, I'll be just outside the courtyard," the maidservant said.

Han Li was very happy with the courtyard, and he suddenly turned to the maidservant with a mesmerizing gleam in his eyes as he asked, "What's your name?"

The maidservant seemed to be transfixed as she looked into Han Li's eyes, and she replied in a slightly dazed voice, "My name is Lian'er."

"What kind of person is Shi Chuankong?" Han Li asked.

"His Highness is someone who has no interest in fighting for power, but he's an avid businessman. He left Night Sun City at a very young age, and he's very good to his servants. He's not arrogant like the other princes, and everyone in Grain Mountain City admires him," the maidservant replied in a slightly jumbled fashion.

Han Li asked her a few more questions before the light in his eyes faded, and the maidservant's expression instantly returned to normal.

"Alright, you can go now," Han Li instructed, and the maidservant promptly departed, none the wiser to the interrogation that she had just been put through.

Han Li watched as the maidservant departed with a contemplative look on his face.

The maidservant's description of Shi Chuankong fit perfectly with how Shi Chuankong normally behaved, so it seemed that he had been overly cautious.

After carefully inspecting the entire courtyard with his spiritual sense, he released a string of array flags throughout the courtyard, quickly conjuring up an azure light barrier.

Only after doing all of that did he enter his bedroom, where he sat down with his legs crossed to cultivate his recompiled version of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

At the same time, he also channeled his spiritual sense to continue cultivating the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

There had been multiple close calls during the past few attacks, and he was determined to make full use of what time he had to enhance his own powers.

Around half a month passed by in the blink of an eye, and on this day, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open as a hint of elation appeared on his face.

Perhaps he was more able to tap into his own latent potential under such a dangerous and stressful environment, but this past half-month of cultivation had yielded exceptional results.

In particular, following that breakthrough that he had made back in the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, his progress in the Spirit Refinement Technique had become incredibly smooth.

After withdrawing the restrictions in the courtyard, Han Li made his way outside, and the maidservant who was waiting there hurriedly extended a curtsey as she declared, "His Highness would like to see you, Senior."

"Take me to him," Han Li replied with a nod, and before long, the two of them arrived in the same hall from before.

Shi Chuankong and Elder Qi were both there, and there were also three more people in the room, two male and one female, all three of whom were at the High Zenith Stage.

The one at the center of the trio was a dark-skinned elderly man clad in a suit of azure devilish armor, while to his left was an extremely tall and rotund middle-aged man who resembled a mountain of meat.

As for the woman, she appeared to be around thirty years of age, and she would've been quite good-looking had it not been for her huge red dress and the excessively ostentatious red flower on her head, both of which gave her a rather comical appearance.

"Please take a seat, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said with a smile as he rose to his feet.

Han Li gave a slight nod as he sat down onto a chair, and Shi Chuankong introduced, "These three are Fellow Daoist Mo, Fellow Daoist Lu, and Fellow Daoist Hua. All three of them are guest elders of this city and also trusted subordinates of mine."

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance. My name is Li Feiyu," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute, and the trio returned the salute in a polite fashion.

Han Li then cast his gaze toward Shi Chuankong, wanting to ask him about the reinforcements sent by Shi Pokong, but he didn't know if it was appropriate with these three guest elders present.

Shi Chuankong could tell what Han Li was thinking, and he assured, "There's no need to be apprehensive of anyone in this room, Fellow Daoist Li. My brother has always been very punctual, and if he says that the reinforcements will arrive in half a month, then they'll definitely be here on time, so they should be here today."

Han Li nodded in response upon hearing this.

"I've invited all of you here today as I want everyone to get to know each other. I'll be relying on all of you from here onward, so let's have a chat over some wine while we wait for reinforcements to arrive," Shi Chuankong said with a smile as he pulled out a red wine jar.

Even with the seal still intact, a delectable aroma was already seeping out of the jar.

"It's our honor to be able to serve you, Your Highness," the dark-skinned elderly man said with a faint smile.

"Indeed. You've always been very kind to us, so it's only right that we return the favor. If you need us to do anything for you, I, for one, am more than happy to make myself useful!" the rotund middle-aged man declared as he patted his own chest.

"It's almost a little hurtful that you're being so formal to us," the woman in the red dress chuckled.

"Thank you, fellow daoists."

Shi Chuankong's mood was lifted significantly by everyone's assurances, and he flipped a hand over to produce a few cups, then personally filled them for everyone.

"Fellow Daiost Li, I know you're quite an expert when it comes to wine, but I'm sure this wine of mine won't disappoint you," Shi Chuankong said to Han Li.

Han Li lifted his cup before taking a sip, and his eyes immediately lit up.

The flavor of this wine was very unique, and it was very different from all of the other immortal wines that he had tasted in the past.

What was even more remarkable was that the wine contained a burst of extremely pure devilish qi that was beneficial for nourishing his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"This is indeed an exceptional wine. What's it called?" Han Li asked.

"I knew you'd be interested in it. This wine is called Rainbow Mulberry Wine. Here's the recipe," Shi Chuankong said as he pulled out a jade slip before handing it to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the jade slip with gratitude, then injected his spiritual sense into it, upon which he discovered that there were around twenty to thirty ingredients required to brew the wine.

At the moment, he still wasn't very familiar with the ingredients of the Devil Realm, but his intuition told him that the devilish qi in the wine originated from an ingredient by the name of Red Mulberry Fruit.

"Where can I find this Red Mulberry Fruit?" Han Li asked.

"Red Mulberry Fruit is produced in the northernmost region of our Holy Realm. Do you intend to brew this Rainbow Mulberry Wine, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"I'm thinking about it. Would it be possible for you to use the power of the Vast Origin House to gather the ingredients required to brew this wine for me? I'll be sure to compensate you for the ingredients," Han Li replied.

"That's not a problem, but Red Mulberry Fruit is a very rare ingredient, so it may take some time to acquire," Shi Chuankong said.

This was no urgent matter for Han Li anyway, and he replied, "In that case, I'll be counting on you, Fellow Daoist Shi."

"You're a wine enthusiast as well, are you, Fellow Daoist Li? In that case, you and I will get along just fine. I don't have any hobbies, but I've always loved fine wine and food. Here's to you, Fellow Daoist Li!" the rotund middle-aged man said in a boisterous voice as he pressed a hand down onto Han Li's shoulder.

Han Li raised his cup with a faint smile, making no attempt to evade the man's hand.

Even though they had only just met, he could tell that the man was very straightforward and wasn't very scheming. If the dark-skinned elderly man had reached out to him, then he definitely wouldn't have let him touch any part of his body.

Only now did Shi Chuankong begin to truly relax, and he began to initiate conversations so everyone could become more familiar with one another.

As the wine began to flow, the atmosphere quickly began to liven up, and before long, everyone began discussing their cultivation insights and experiences.

Everyone present was at the High Zenith Stage, with the exception of Shi Chuankong, but he had also overcome his baleful tribulation, so he had one foot in the door.

The time quickly passed by, and close to an entire day flew by in the blink of an eye, but the reinforcements sent by Shi Pokong still hadn't showed up.

Chapter 802: Traitor?

Han Li took a quick glance at Shi Chuankong to discover that he was also looking slightly concerned, but he maintained a calm expression as he drank and chatted with the dark-skinned elderly man.

Han Li subtly withdrew his gaze, then resumed his discussion with the rotund middle-aged man.

The cultivation arts used by the rotund man were more geared toward body refinement, so they were rather similar to the Provenance True Devil Arts, and as a result, the two of them had much common ground to discuss.

Time continued to pass, and before long, it had already turned dark outside, but the reinforcements sent by Shi Pokong still hadn't shown up, and at this point, no one was in the mood to be chatting anymore.

"My brother's subordinates are extremely well-disciplined, so there's no way they would be intentionally tardy. Looks like something must've happened," Shi Chuankong said with furrowed brows.

Han Li turned his gaze to Shi Chuankong in silence.

"Could it be that something went wrong on their way here, Young Master?" Elder Qi asked with furrowed brows.

"Elder Qi, report this matter to my brother and ask him if he knows what's going on," Shi Chuankong instructed.

"The last time I attempted to contact His Highness, he seemed to have been busy with something, so he won't be able to get back to me until later," Elder Qi replied in a hesitant voice.

A hint of surprise appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this, and he said, "Is that right? In any case, you should still go and ask him."

"Yes, Young Master," Elder Qi replied before quickly departing.

Following Elder Qi's departure, Shi Chuankong leaned back against his chair and fell into deep thought with his brows tightly furrowed, and everyone fell silent.

Time began to slowly pass once again, and around fifteen minutes later, Elder Qi returned.

"How did it go?" Shi Chuankong immediately asked.

"There's still been no response," Elder Qi replied with a shake of his head.

Shi Chuankong's expression darkened a little further upon hearing this, and everyone in the room was looking at him, clearly waiting for him to make a decision.

"We'll wait for another half-day. If the reinforcements still haven't arrived, then we won't wait any longer," Shi Chuankong declared as he took a glance at Elder Qi, and the latter immediately departed once again.

Han Li took a glance at Elder Qi's parting figure, then lowered his gaze, and the room fell back into a tense silence.

As a result, time began to pass agonizingly slowly.

The three High Zenith cultivators were also beginning to grow a little uneasy, and they would exchange glances with each other from time to time, while Shi Chuankong and Han Li's expressions remained unchanged.

Half a day quickly passed by, yet there was still no further news.

Right at this moment, Shi Chuankong sprang to his feet, and Han Li and the others stood up as well.

"Please come with me, everyone," Shi Chuankong instructed before making his way out of the room, and everyone immediately followed along.

The group quickly arrived in a hall deep within the manor. The hall was cylindrical in shape, looking much like a round altar, and it was entirely black without any connective seams visible, as if it had been entirely carved out of a giant piece of black crystal.

The hall was around an acre in area and over a hundred feet tall, towering over all of the surrounding buildings.

At this moment, Elder Qi was standing at the closed entrance of the hall, and he immediately approached Shi Chuankong upon catching sight of him.

"Are the preparations complete?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Rest assured, Young Master, everything is ready to go," Elder Qi immediately replied with a nod, following which a streak of black light flew out of his hand before vanishing into the door of the hall.

A layer of black light emerged over the door, following which it parted down the center to reveal the hall inside.

It was a circular hall that was completely empty, making it appear particularly spacious.

Embedded onto the walls at set intervals were head-sized chunks of white jade that were giving off a bright white radiance, making the interior of the hall as bright as day.

On the ground at the very center of the hall was a silver teleportation array that was around seventy to eighty feet in diameter. It was entirely filled with silver array patterns, and there were also close to a hundred black crystals embedded into it, every single one of which was giving off formidable devilish qi.

At this moment, there were eight gray-robed devilish beings seated around the array, all of whom were at the Golden Immortal Stage, and they immediately stood up at the sight of Shi Chuankong before extending respectful bows.

"Where does this teleportation lead to, Fellow Daiost Shi?" Han Li asked.

"The array leads to Chuyu City hundreds of thousands of kilometers away. At the moment, it's safe to assume that the reinforcements sent by my brother have been held up somewhere, so continuing to wait here will only put us in an even more passive position," Shi Chuankong replied, and Han Li nodded in agreement.

"Activate the array, Elder Qi," Shi Chuankong instructed.

Elder Qi nodded in response, then took a step forward as he summoned a silver badge. However, right as he was about to use the badge, he suddenly stopped in his tracks.

"What's wrong, Elder Qi?" Shi Chuankong asked.

Han Li also turned his gaze to Elder Qi, who crouched down to pluck a black crystal out of the array on the ground, then examined it momentarily before stowing it away.

At the same time, another black crystal appeared in his other hand, and he deposited it into the vacant slot.

"I just noticed that one of the Devilish Origin Stones in the array was a little impure, so it's best to get it replaced," Elder Qi explained with a smile, then took a step back before making a hand seal, and the silver badge instantly rose up into the air while glowing radiantly.

The eight Golden Immortals nearby also each summoned a silver badge, and the silver light radiating from their badges connected together with that of Elder Qi's badge.

The array on the ground instantly also began to glow and buzz, and Shi Chuankong was just about to step into the teleportation array when a burst of black light suddenly flew out of Elder Qi's hand before striking Shi Chuankong on the back at an astonishing speed.

A bewildered look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as the black light pierced through the layer of protective light around him with ease, following which a purple jade pendant hanging from his waist abruptly exploded to form a light barrier that kept the streak of black light at bay.

Shi Chuankong immediately snapped back to his senses and let loose a furious roar as he dodged to the side.

A loud crack rang out as the purple light barrier was breached by the streak of black light before glancing past Shi Chuankong's body, slicing a deep gash into his waist that instantly began spewing blood.

Right as the streak of black light flew out of Elder Qi's hand, a giant golden claw, a thin pink sword, and a black wheel appeared around Han Li without any warning, then hurtled directly toward him, piercing into his body in unison.

Immediately thereafter, the dark-skinned elderly man, the rotund middle-aged man, and the woman in the red dress surrounded him in an instant with cold killing intent etched on their faces.

However, much to their surprise, Han Li's body suddenly dissipated, revealing it to have been nothing more than an afterimage.

On the other side, the gash on Shi Chuankong's waist was bleeding profusely, and the skin around the wound was quickly turning black while spreading over the rest of his body. His entire body quickly became numb, and as a result, his movements were inhibited.

"Die!" Elder Qi roared with a fierce look on his face as he made a grabbing motion with one hand.

Three azure vortexes instantly appeared above Shi Chuankong out of thin air, and countless streaks of incredibly sharp azure light came raining down upon him.

At the same time, the eight Golden Immortals around the array also pounced at him in unison, unleashing attacks of their own.

"Elder Qi, how could you?"

Shi Chuankong's face was distorted with fury and grief as a vast expanse of purple light surged out of his body, then transformed into a purple shield that was several dozen feet in size.

Layers of intricate patterns were etched onto the surface of the shield, and countless dazzling purple runes could also be seen interspersed among them.

The shield had only just taken shape when the barrage of oncoming attacks arrived, and an earth-shattering boom rang out alongside an eruption of blinding light as the shield shuddered violently.

Countless cracks instantly appeared on the shield's surface, following which it exploded violently, and Shi Chuankong was dashed to the ground as if he had just been dealt a heavy blow.

Before he had a chance to get up, he was overwhelmed by the barrage of fierce attacks, and he was completely powerless to resist.

Right at this moment, he abruptly vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden light.

All of the attacks directed at him struck the ground instead, and a string of resounding explosions rang out as a series of giant craters were smashed into the ground.

The shockwaves from the explosions erupted outward in all directions, causing the entire hall to tremble violently as cracks appeared over its walls, but a layer of bright black light had emerged from the walls, resiliently keeping the hall intact.

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light flashed through the air before piercing into one of the walls, running through the black restriction on the wall with ease, following which a large hole was blasted into the wall itself.

A blurry golden shadow then flew out from within, and at the same time, the black restriction in the entire hall lit up in an erratic fashion before collapsing violently.

Without the fortification provided by the restriction, the entire hall instantly collapsed as well, burying everyone within it.

Several thousand feet away from the hall, Han Li appeared in mid-air amid a flash of golden light with Shi Chuankong clutched in one hand, and a rapidly revolving golden wheel could just barely be seen in his body.

Chapter 803: Abnormalities

Han Li took a glance at the wreckage of the hall, then gently placed a hand onto Shi Chuankong's shoulder, and a burst of pure immortal spiritual power instantly swept through his body, suppressing the poison so that it didn't spread any further from his wound.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Li."

Shi Chuankong could feel the numb sensation in his body quickly fading, and he hurriedly rose to his feet, then took a blue pill.

A series of blue patterns instantly appeared over his entire body, and countless strands of muscle fibers emerged from the wound on his waist, then connected together to heal the wound, while the black coloration on the nearby skin also began to fade.

"Looks like all of your subordinates have already betrayed you. What do you want to do with them?" Han Li asked.

A conflicted look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, a string of loud explosions rang out, and the ruins of the hall erupted as Elder Qi and the others flew out into the open before pouncing at Han Li and Shi Chuankong again.

Han Li took a glance at Shi Chuankong, then made a grabbing motion with one hand, and three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly appeared before him.

With a flick of his wrist, the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords transformed into countless golden lightning threads that shot forth through the air, reaching the oncoming assailants in a flash.

Every single lightning thread was glowing radiantly, and they were giving off formidable lightning law power fluctuations.

Elder Qi's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he let loose a thunderous roar, upon which three azure vortexes reappeared in front of him, releasing waves of azure ripples that formed a dense azure light barrier in front of everyone.

The torrential barrage of golden lightning threads fell upon the azure light barrier, and a series of tiny vortexes appeared on its surface, attempting to devour the golden lightning threads.

However, the sword threads formed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were extremely formidable, and they were only stopped in their tracks for a split second before piercing through the azure light barrier with ease.

The azure light barrier instantly exploded violently, but it had bought everyone enough time to react.

The rotund middle-aged man clenched his hands into tight fists before ramming them against each other, and a metallic clang rang out as a series of golden ripples surged out of his body.

The golden lightning threads that were caught in the ripples instantly began trembling erratically, and a small portion of them exploded on the spot, while the rest were stopped cold in their tracks.

The rotund man then let loose a loud roar before making a grabbing motion with both hands, and all of the golden ripples instantly converged to form an extremely life-like golden lion projection that let loose a deafening roar.

In the face of the destructive soundwaves, all of the remaining lightning threads were also shattered before disintegrating into specks of golden light.

At the same time, two beams of black light shot out of the dark-skinned elderly man's eyes, while a vast black shadow erupted out of his body.

The shadow contained a burst of glacial law powers that caused the nearby space to warp and blur, as if it had been frozen solid.

The golden lightning threads were instantly stopped cold in their tracks by the black shadow, while the woman in the red dress opened her mouth to release a translucent white ring.

The ring swelled dramatically to over a hundred feet in size at her behest, encompassing her entire body within it, and it revolved around her briefly before exploding on its own to form a white cloud that was hundreds of feet in size.

The oncoming golden lightning threads were able to pierce into the white cloud with ease, but they were instantly slowed down as a result, as if they had pierced into a viscous swamp.

The woman took advantage of this window of respite to dodge to the side, allowing her to evade all of the golden lightning threads.

Meanwhile, Elder Qi flew back in retreat before appearing among the eight Golden Immortals in a flash.

The eight of them immediately formed an orderly circle around Elder Qi, and lights of different colors rose up from all nine of their bodies, then intertwined with one another before dancing through the air like a storm of flowers.

Elder Qi rubbed his hands together, and a torrential barrage of incantation seals instantly shrugged forth.

All of the flowers of light of different colors instantly fused into one, then formed a gray array that encompassed the nine of them.

The golden lightning threads struck the gray array before exploding into arcs of lighting, and the array instantly began trembling incessantly, but it showed no signs of breaking.

Even though everyone had managed to ward off the golden lightning threads, Han Li remained completely unfazed, and he turned to Shi Chuankong again as he urged, "You can't afford to be indecisive here, Fellow Daoist Shi!"

Shi Chuankong shuddered, and the indecision in his eyes faded as he replied, "My apologies, Fellow Daoist Li. If they're determined to kill us, then there's no need for you to hold back."

Han Li nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and all of the golden lightning threads up ahead also flew back before reverting back into three golden flying swords.

The twelve Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were all glowing radiantly as Han Li made a rapid string of hand seals, and streaks of golden sword qi descended out of the sky to form a massive sword array that was several acres in area.

It was none other than his Horned Dragon Sword Array, and as it descended from the heavens, it seemed to be bringing the nearby space along with it.

The dark-skinned elderly man and the woman in the red dress immediately darted away in opposite directions, just barely getting out of the way before the golden sword array fully descended.

The two of them had managed to escape, but the rotund man and Elder Qi and the eight Golden Immortals weren't so fortunate, and all of them were caught within the array.

A grim look appeared on the rotund man's face as he opened his mouth to release a burst of golden light that vanished into the golden lion projection in a flash, and the projection instantly swelled to several times its original size to encompass him within it.

Immediately thereafter, countless golden runes emerged over the golden lion projection's body, and it instantly took on a much more substantial form. At the same time, a series of golden spots had also appeared over its skin, resembling a suit of scale armor, giving it a very fearsome appearance.

The golden lion let loose a ferocious roar as it began to bound forward, trying to escape from the sword array.

At the same time, the gray array that Elder Qi was situated in began to glow brightly while releasing a series of threads of gray light that swept toward the surrounding sword array, attempting to break it open from the inside.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and countless streaks of formidable golden sword qi erupted out of the sword array at his behest, alongside twelve golden sword projections that resembled giant dragons, all of which struck the golden lion and the gray array.

The golden lion instantly crumpled, falling away into several pieces as if it were made from tofu.

As a result, the rotund man was revealed with an alarmed look on his face, and before he had a chance to do anything, two sword projections swept right through his body, slicing him into pieces.

At the same time, all of the threads of gray light released by the gray array also instantly shattered upon making contact with the opposing sword qi.

Several sword projections then struck the gray array, and it was barely able to put up any resistance before it was also destroyed.

A torrential barrage of sword qi instantly inundated Elder Qi and the eight Golden Immortals, and a chorus of agonized howls rang out.

"Gao Feng, you bastard! Stop!" the woman in the red dress screeched in a furious voice as she pounced at Han Li like lightning while flipping a hand over to summon a pink jade fan.

The fan was entirely pink in color with countless vibrant butterfly designs emblazoned upon it, and it was giving off a layer of pink flames.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong both faltered slightly upon hearing her enraged cry, but before they had a chance to do anything, the woman swept the fan vigorously through the air, releasing a burst of dense pink light that surged toward Han Li in a frenzy.

At the same time, the dark-skinned elderly man also transformed into a black shadow that pounced at Han Li, and as he did this, black shadows began to surge out of his body, forming a black cloud that was several hundred feet in size.

A low roar rang out from within the cloud, following which a giant black turtle the size of a house emerged.

The creature had six eyes and a series of giant ice spikes on its back, and its entire body was giving off a fearsome glacial aura.

As soon as the giant black turtle appeared, all six of its eyes instantly sprang open at once to release six pillars of black light, which covered a distance of several thousand feet in the blink of an eye to strike at Han Li.

In response, Han Li immediately made a hand seal, and arcs of thick golden lightning erupted out of his hands, forming two dense walls of golden lightning that stood in the path of the pink light and the pillars of black light.

Two dull thumps rang out as the walls of lightning shuddered violently, then instantly settled down once again, keeping the oncoming attacks at bay.

Even though the pink light and the pillars of black light had been stopped in their tracks, the law powers imbued within them were able to pass through the walls of lightning and into Han Li's body.

There was a burst of glacial law powers that had some effect on his body, but was kept out before it was able to infiltrate very deep. However, the other burst of law powers was as soft as cloud and mist, and it quickly began to burrow into his body upon contact.

Han Li caught a whiff of a peculiar aroma, and his bones shuddered while all of his pores opened up at once, and he was suddenly overcome by such an intense wave of feebleness that he almost fell to the ground.

He immediately realized that this burst of soft law powers was interspersed with some type of fragrant substance, and both had infiltrated his entire body.

The two of them had been combined together to perfection, and he was unable to tell them apart.

Chapter 804: Strange Powers

Han Li was slightly alarmed by this turn of events, but he didn't panic.

His Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and it released waves of golden ripples that washed over his body, eradicating the two bursts of external law powers that had infiltrated his body.

However, to his dismay, the fragrant substance remained in his body, completely unaffected by his time law powers, and he was still feeling extremely feeble.

"Well done, Fellow Daoist Hua! This is where you die, Gao Feng!" the dark-skinned elderly man yelled as he pointed a finger at Han Li, and five more giant black turtles emerged from the shadows around him before opening their eyes in unison.

Pillars of black light erupted out of the six turtles' collective thirty-six eyes, and they condensed into a series of thin black threads that hurtled directly toward Han Li.

These thin black threads were giving off a glacial aura that was almost on par with that of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and at the same time, all of the ice spikes on the backs of the giant black turtles detached themselves before hurtling directly toward Han Li.

In the face of the oncoming attacks, Han Li remained completely unfazed as he made a hand seal before opening his mouth to release a silver fireball that was around ten feet in diameter.

The silver fireball instantly expanded into a sea of silver flames that was around an acre in size, with Han Li at the very center.

Waves of fire that were dozens of feet tall rose up into the air, giving off a sweltering aura.

The Essence Fire Raven was dancing within the sea of flames, and as soon as the black threads and ice spikes pierced into the silver flames, they were instantly melted away into nothingness.

All of the pink sword projections in the air also vanished before reverting back into a pink flying sword, and the spiritual light emanating from it was rapidly fading in the face of the scorching flames.

The woman's expression changed drastically as she raised a hand to try and summon her flying sword back to herself, but right at this moment, the Essence Fire Raven swooped down onto the sword, catching it in its beak before tipping its head back to swallow the sword as if it were a little bug.

The woman's spiritual connection with the flying sword instantly vanished, and she gave a muffled groan as her complexion paled significantly.

A look of alarm and concern appeared on the dark-skinned elderly man's face upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, the Essence Fire Raven suddenly launched itself at him with astonishing speed.

Even before the fire raven had fully descended upon him, the heat radiating from its body was already enough to make the nearby space tremble incessantly, as if it were about to be set alight.

All of the black shadows around the elderly man were rapidly evaporating, and he hurriedly flew back in retreat, while a burst of black light erupted out of his body, quickly forming a black spirit domain that was around a hundred feet in size.

A burst of glacial law powers was churning incessantly within the black spirit domain, freezing everything within it.

At the same time, seven or eight treasures flew out of his body in rapid succession, forming a series of protective barriers around him.

A very humanized look of derision flashed through the Essence Fire Raven's eyes upon seeing this, and it abruptly swelled to around twice its original size, while roughly a dozen large specks of silver light appeared on its wings.

Bursts of silver flames erupted backward out of those specks of light, and the Essence Fire Raven instantly sped up dramatically, flying headfirst into the black spirit domain as a long streak of silver light.

The black spirit domain had no effect on the Essence Fire Raven at all, and it instantly tore through the spirit domain before crashing into the protective barriers in front of the elderly man.

The protective barriers weren't able to pose any resistance, either, and the Essence Fire Raven was barely slowed down at all as it tore through all of them in rapid succession before piercing straight through the dark-skinned elderly man's body.

The elderly man was instantly split into two at the waist, following which the two halves of his body erupted into scorching silver flames.

A fearful look finally appeared on the woman's face upon seeing this, and she gritted her teeth before fleeing into the distance as a streak of pink light.

However, she had only managed to fly for about a thousand feet before several translucent chains shot out of the nearby space without any warning, then wound themselves around her body like lightning.

At the same time, Han Li appeared directly before her, clearly having already recovered from the poison that he had inhaled.

The pink light emanating from the woman's body instantly brightened significantly before erupting outward to form a pink spirit domain, and around a dozen different fragrances appeared within the spirit domain, mixing with the law powers inside before converging toward Han Li.

In response, the golden light radiating from Han Li's body brightened significantly at his behest, releasing bursts of time law powers that kept all of the external law powers within the spirit domain at bay.

At the same time, he flicked a finger through the air, and several arcs of golden lightning shot out of his fingertip before striking the woman in several of her vital regions, including her glabella and her dantian.

A loud thunderclap rang out, and the woman's entire body was charred black, following which she convulsed violently for a moment before falling unconscious.

Immediately thereafter, the pink spirit domain vanished, and the fragrances in the air began to dissipate.

Han Li then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of green light that emitted tremendous suction force, sucking all of the fragrances up his sleeve.

Right at this moment, a dull thump suddenly rang out from the sword array in the distance, and a miniature azure figure flew out from within. It was Elder Qi's nascent soul, and it had somehow managed to escape from the Horned Dragon Sword Array.

As soon as the azure nascent soul emerged, it immediately fled into the distance as a streak of azure light, but right at this moment, Shi Chuankong appeared directly in front of it, then reached out with one hand, conjuring a huge purple hand projection that caught the nascent soul in a flash.

The nascent soul immediately began struggling with all its might, but strands of purple light were surging out of the hand projection, forming a dense net that prevented the nascent soul from getting away.

"Elder Qi, I've always seen you as family, and I've never wronged you in any way. Why have you betrayed me?" Shi Chuankong asked in a furious voice with his fists tightly clenched.

However, the nascent soul didn't appear to have heard him at all, and it yelled in a defiant voice, "I won't tell you anything about Young Master Shi!"

Immediately a look of resolve appeared on its face as blinding azure light began to radiate from its body.

"Stop him, Fellow Daoist Shi! He's about to self detonate!" Han Li yelled in alarm.

Shi Chuankong hurriedly sprang into action upon hearing this, and threads of purple light began to burrow their way into the azure nascent soul, but it was already too late.

In the next instant, the nascent soul exploded violently into a radiant azure sun.

Shi Chuankong hurriedly flew back in retreat, but he was too close to the azure sun, yet right as he was about to get swept up in the explosion, an arc of golden lightning fell out of the sky, forming a protective barrier in front of him, and two crossed golden flying swords could just barely be made out within the barrier.

The explosion of azure light raged ferociously against the lightning barrier, causing it to tremble incessantly, but it displayed no signs of breaking.

A few moments later, the azure sun rapidly dimmed before vanishing altogether.

Han Li appeared beside him in a flash, then made a hand seal, and the golden lightning barrier reverted back into a pair of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before flying back up his sleeve.

"What happened just now, Fellow Daoist Li? Who is this Gao Feng that they were speaking of?" Shi Chuankong asked as he turned to Han Li.

Han Li offered no response. Instead, he closed his eyes, and he seemed to be sensing something.

Right at this moment, a loud explosion rang out several thousand feet away, and a yellow figure stumbled out of thin air with another Han Li hot on their tail.

The other Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that hurtled directly toward the yellow figure, but the latter remained completely unfazed, releasing a streak of translucent light that contained a yellow copper mirror.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and the six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were sent flying back, but the streak of translucent light also exploded.

Meanwhile, the yellow figure vanished from the spot, then reappeared thousands of feet away to reveal male figure in a yellow robe, but his facial features were concealed behind a layer of yellow light.

"If I'm not mistaken, this man orchestrated everything that happened just now. I don't know how he did it, but he appeared to have somehow manipulated Elder Qi and the others into mistaking us for two other people, thereby turning them against us," Han Li said.

Shi Chuankong's expression instantly darkened significantly upon hearing this.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and the Han Li beside Shi Chuankong dissipated into specks of azure light, revealing it to have been nothing more than avatar.

The Horned Dragon Sword Array also reverted back to twelve Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that flew up his sleeve, and the bodies of the rotund man and the eight Golden Immortals fell to the ground.

Chapter 805: Tricked

"My apologies. The situation just now was very urgent, so even though I already noticed that something was amiss, I had no choice but to retaliate," Han Li said in an apologetic manner, then raised his hand to make a beckoning motion, and a ball of silver fire flew over to him, following which the body of the dark-skinned elderly man fell out of it.

The two halves of his body had already been reassembled, but his aura was extremely feeble.

It seemed that some type of restriction had been planted in his body, and this moment, he was laying on the ground in a completely immobilized manner, glowering up at Han Li and Shi Chuankong with burning resentment in his eyes.

As for the ball of silver flames, it reverted back into the Essence Fire Raven before vanishing into Han Li's body in a flash.

Shi Chuankong didn't seem to have heard Han Li at all, and he took a glance down at the dark-skinned elderly man with mixed emotions in his eyes, then cast a cold gaze toward the yellow-robed man.

"It's very impressive that you were able to find me on such scant leads," the yellow-robed man remarked as he sized up Han Li.

The yellow light concealing his face quickly faded away as he spoke, revealing him to be a young man who appeared to be around twenty-five to twenty-six years of age.

He was wearing half a silver mask that concealed the left half of his face, and the exposed skin on the right side of his face was very fair and smooth.

Upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that the man was wearing makeup, and his lips were bright red, giving him a very strange, gender-ambiguous appearance.

"Hua Jing!" Shi Chuankong yelled in a furious voice, and he seemed to be familiar with the man.

All of a sudden, his entire body began to tremble, and an agonized look appeared on his face as his aura began to fluctuate violently.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately flew over to Shi Chuankong's side, then released a burst of azure light into his body.

His aura instantly began to settle, while the pain on his face also began to ease.

"I understand you must feel terrible right now, but you can't afford to let your emotions get the better of you. This man is quite powerful, and his law powers are also very peculiar. You seem to be familiar with him, do you know what we should expect from him in battle?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

The masked man was a late-High Zenith cultivator, and he was clearly far more formidable than Elder Qi and the others.

During their brief clash, he had used six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, yet even that wasn't enough to gain him an upper hand.

Shi Chuankong took a deep breath to regain some composure, then replied through voice transmission, "His name is Hua Jing, and he's one of the subordinates of my fifth sister, Shi Jingyan. He's mastered some type of law powers related to hypnotism, and he's able to control one's senses. Elder Qi and the others must've fallen prey to him."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Back in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range and Preeminent City, it was Shi Zhanfeng, and now, it was Shi Jingyan. It seemed like barely any of Shi Chuankong's siblings wanted him to live!

"Jingyan sent you, didn't she? What does she want?" Shi Chuankong asked as he stepped forward with a cold expression.

"Why ask the question when you already know the answer, Your Highness? Her Highness instructed me to fetch your head along with the Virata Lute. Having said that, I don't have absolute confidence in my ability to defeat this subordinate of yours, so how about we make a compromise, and I'll let you live, but you have to hand over the Virata Lute," Hua Jing proposed with a faint smile.

Han Li remained silent upon hearing this, while Shi Chuankong spat through gritted teeth, "Is that supposed to be a joke? You turned so many of my subordinates against me, and you killed Elder Qi! You're not leaving this place alive!"

"Why are you getting so worked up over the deaths of an old servant and a few dogs? It's unbecoming of a prince like yourself to have such little composure," Hua Jing chuckled.

Shi Chuankong wasted no more time with words as he pounced forward, and his Virata Lute appeared in his grasp amid a flash of silver light.

As he strummed his fingers over the lute's strings, countless silver runes surged forth, then transformed into hundreds of silver blades of wind that hurtled directly toward Hua Jing.

Now only were these blades of wind extremely fast, there was an insubstantial, wraith-like quality to them, making them very difficult to evade.

Hua Jing's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of the Virata Lute, but instead of rushing in recklessly, he darted back in retreat.

Right at this moment, three golden flying swords appeared behind him without any warning, then transformed into countless golden sword projections to cut off his retreat.

Hua Jing was completely unfazed as he swept a sleeve through the air, and an intricate little yellow bell appeared above his head amid a flash of yellow light.

The bell chimed as it released a burst of yellow light, which formed a giant yellow bell projection that encompassed Hua Jing's entire body.

In the next instant, all of the golden sword projections and blades of silver wind struck the giant bell projection, causing it to tremble incessantly, but it was able to remain intact and keep all of the attacks at bay.

Shi Chuankong's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and in the next instant, all of the silver blades of wind began to circle around the giant bell projection like a flock of birds.

Immediately thereafter, Shi Chuankong strummed his fingers over the strings of the lute once again, and all of the hundreds of blades of wind instantly converged to form a pair of silver crescent moons, each of which was several dozen feet in size.

A burst of rumbling rang out from the pair of crescent moons, and they began to sweep toward the giant yellow bell.

Hua Jing's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately swept both sleeves through the air, upon which the yellow bell projection around him became around twice as thick as before.

At the same time, countless yellow runes appeared over its surface, giving off a burst of tremendous earth law powers.

In the next instant, the two crescent moons struck the giant bell projection, and they were able to phase straight through the projection, completely ignoring it and the earth law powers that it was releasing.

Hua Jing's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly flew back in retreat as a yellow shadow.

However, right at this moment, Han Li appeared behind him without any warning, then threw an almighty punch into the giant bell projection.

A resounding clang rang out, and even though the bell projection wasn't shattered, it was stopped cold in its tracks, thereby allowing the two silver crescent moon projections to catch up to it.

The two crescent moons struck Hua Jing in the blink of an eye, releasing bursts of sharp spatial law powers that instantly reduced his body to a pile of mincemeat.

Shi Chuankong's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and he sighed, "Rest in peace, Elder Qi. I've avenged you..."

"Hold on, something's not right!" Han Li suddenly yelled in a grim voice, and Shi Chuankong looked up just in time to see Hua Jing's mangled remains vanish into thin air, revealing it to have been nothing more than an illusion.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes while also releasing his tremendous spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area, and at the same time, Hua Jing reappeared several thousand feet away with a mocking sneer on his face.

"You thought that was enough to kill me, Your Highness? How hurtful that you think so little of me! If that was enough to kill me, then I would've already been dead and buried long ago."

A yellow copper mirror emerged above his head amid a flash of yellow light, and the mirror was around a foot in size, giving off rays of translucent light.

There were some squiggly lines engraved onto its frame, and at the center of the mirror was an extremely vibrant red flower.

Han Li's gaze was immediately drawn to the flower, which began to turn toward him, as if it had sprung to life.

Han Li instantly snapped back to his senses upon seeing this, and his tremendous spiritual sense began to sweep through his mind, where a series of red projections had appeared, wrapping themselves around his soul before attempting to burrow their way in.

However, Han Li was instantly able to eradicate these projections with his spiritual sense, thereby restoring his mental clarity, and he heaved a faint sigh of relief before turning his gaze back to Hua Jing with a wary expression.

A hint of surprise flashed through Hua Jing's eyes upon seeing this.

"Impressive! I didn't think your spiritual sense would be so powerful. Having said that..."

Right at this moment, two white shadows suddenly shot forth toward him like lightning from either side, and he immediately took evasive measures, darting away as a streak of golden light to just barely evade the oncoming attacks.

He then reappeared several thousand feet away, while Shi Chuankong appeared in the same spot where he had just been standing a moment ago.

At this moment, there was a look of murderous rage in Shi Chuankong's eyes, and he pounced at Han Li once again while strumming his Virata Lute, sending countless silver blades of wind sweeping toward Han Li.

At the same time, the two streaks of white light circled around in mid-air before also hurtling toward Han Li once again, and they were a pair of white jade rulers.

Shi Chuankong opened his mouth to release two balls of blood essence, which vanished into the pair of rulers in a flash, and countless white runes instantly surged out of the jade rulers, following which they transformed into a pair of massive balls of white light that rumbled toward Han Li with tremendous power.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning, then reappeared not far behind Shi Chuankong before urging in a thunderous voice, "Wake up, Fellow Daoist Shi!"

He was unleashing a lion's roar technique that was capable of shaking the soul and dispelling illusions, but it had no effect on Shi Chuankong, who swung around before taking a swipe at Han Li.

Five bursts of purple devilish qi shot out of his fingertips, each forming a fiery purple devilish claw that grabbed directly at Han Li's chest.

Chapter 806: Sealing Souls

Han Li made a hand seal upon seeing this, and several thick arcs of lightning sprang out of his flying swords before striking Shi Chuankong in his vital regions, including his glabella and his dantian.

Shi Chuankong shuddered violently, and his entire body was instantly charred black, but he didn't seem to be able to feel the pain at all as he shrugged off the golden lightning and continued charging forward.

At the same time, several streaks of black light descended out of the sky like bolts of black lightning before striking Han Li, while a sweet aroma wafted through the air from another direction, and a dragon formed by pink mist appeared without any warning before pouncing Han Li.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face as he shot back in retreat with golden lightning flashing over his body, while the dark-skinned elderly man and the woman in the red dress emerged from behind the black light and the mist dragon, respectively.

Both of them had ashy complexions and violently fluctuating auras, and they were in no condition to battle, but they were still charging at him without any recourse.

"Anyone who's fallen prey to my Flower Mirror ability will continue to fight to the death regardless of how severe their injuries are, unless I free them from the ability," Hua Jing chuckled.

Han Li's expression darkened even further upon hearing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to summon eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in a row.

The eighteen flying swords then flew toward Shi Chuankong's trio at his behest, releasing thick arcs of golden lightning that formed a wave of lightning that stretched for close to ten kilometers while giving off formidable lightning law power fluctuations.

Han Li flew into the wave of lightning, and it instantly began to glow even brighter while sweeping through the air, reaching Shi Chuankong's trio in the blink of an eye.

The three of them immediately lashed out without any hesitation, with Shi Chuankong strumming his fingers over the Virata Lute to release bursts of violent soundwaves interspersed with countless silver runes.

The silver runes split up into two before fusing into the blades of silver wind and the two balls of white light, and the blades of silver wind instantly converged to form a silver crescent moon that was twice the size of the ones directed at Hua Jing earlier.

As for the two balls of white light, they fused together to form a radiant white sun, and the silver moon and white sun sped toward the wave of golden lightning, leaving a flurry of spatial rifts in their wake.

Meanwhile, the dark-skinned elderly man opened his mouth to release a black inkstone, which instantly began to revolve rapidly at his behest, releasing a vast expanse of black mist that formed a huge black cloud in the blink of an eye.

The cloud was filled with immense glacial qi, and countless black ice crystals began to take shape, while the cloud of black mist itself transformed into a torrent of black water.

The previously insubstantial black cloud instantly transformed into a turbulent glacial river that rumbled through the air.

At the same time, the woman flipped a hand over to summon a white scroll, which was unfurled to release a flurry of white runes that converged to form eight extremely life-like crystalline white dragons.

The pink light emanating from the woman's body brightened significantly before surging into the white scroll, which instantly turned pink as well, as did the eight white dragon projections.

The crystalline dragons looked as if they had been carved out of pink ice, and they were giving off tremendous auras near the High Zenith Stage.

The woman's complexion had become deathly pale at this point, but she was still expending her devilish power without any reservation.

The attacks from all four combatants clashed amid a string of earth-shattering booms, and golden, silver, black, and pink light intertwined violently, resulting in a temporary impasse.

However, it was very apparent that the golden lightning had the upper hand, but Han Li didn't dare to go all-out for fear of killing his three already injured opponents.

Hua Jing burst into deranged laughter upon seeing this, and he began licking his fingers with an intoxicated expression.

He loved turning previously close friends against each other, and it was even better in scenarios where one person managed to remain conscious, and he was forced to fight against his friends, but didn't dare to go all-out for fear of hurting them.

Han Li could hear Hua Jing's deranged laughter, and he harrumphed coldly as he made a string of hand seals.

Eighteen thick streaks of swordlight instantly shot out of the wave of lightning at his behest, and at this point, it was already taking every last ounce of power just for Shi Chuankong's trio to keep the wave of golden lightning at bay, so they didn't have the spare capacity to defend themselves from any other attacks.

As a result, the golden flying swords were able to tear through the protective light barriers around them with ease, following which they were struck by the surrounding arcs of golden lightning.

All three of them were instantly sent flying with blood gushing out of their mouths, and thanks to the properties that it had inherited from the Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, the lightning in the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had a numbing effect that could deprive one of their control over their body and immortal spiritual power.

However, a burst of bright red light flashed in their minds in unison, and they were forced to overexert themselves without considering the costs incurred, forcibly fighting their way through the numbing effect.

Right at this moment, Han Li appeared in front of the three of them without any warning, then tapped a finger against their foreheads in rapid succession.

With each tap, several translucent chains flew out of his fingertip before vanishing into their glabellas in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, all three of them crumpled to the ground with dazed looks on their faces.

It had clearly taken a great deal of effort for Han Li to subdue the trio, as evidenced by his slightly pale complexion, and he took a deep breath to steady himself before sweeping a sleeve through the air, upon which the vast wave of golden lightning in the sky reverted back into eighteen golden flying swords that flew back up his sleeve.

Hua Jing's smile immediately stiffened upon seeing this, and he began making a string of hand seals, but Shi Chuankong's trio displayed no reaction.

"What did you do to them? How did you manage to seal their souls away?" he asked with a furious expression.

"You think I would tell you?" Han Li scoffed in a cold voice.

"You're not going to tell me? Fine! In that case, I'll just have to pluck your soul out of your body and see for myself! After such an intense battle, I'm sure you're already close to a spent force!" Hua Jing sneered.

"Are you trying to tell me that you can use that Flower Mirror ability of yours with minimal exertion? Surely you haven't been passively observing this entire time just to show off," Han Li countered.

Hua Jing's eyes instantly narrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"You've made me your plaything this entire time, it's about time that you get what's been coming to you now!" Han Li declared in a cold voice as he strode toward Hua Jing with cold killing intent in his eyes.

For some reason, a chill ran down Hua Jing's spine, and in order to disguise his fear, he yelled, "You sure talk big for a mere early-High Zenth cultivator!"

Immediately thereafter, a burst of bright yellow light surged out of his body, then took on the form of a strange beastly head that was over a thousand feet in size and seemed to be somewhere between a dragon and a tiger.

The beastly head opened its cavernous mouth to release a burst of yellow light, which crossed over a distance of tens of thousands of feet in the blink of an eye before descending upon Han Li.

In response, Han Li raised a hand before making a grabbing motion, and thick arcs of golden lightning appeared before him once again to form a thick lightning barrier that stood in the path of the yellow light.

The two clashed, and while one would've expected an earth-shattering boom, there was only a faint thud in reality.

The thick lightning barrier flashed erratically before it was torn apart by the burst of yellow light without being able to pose any resistance, and the burst of yellow light was barely slowed down at all as it pierced straight through Han Li's chest.

However, in the next instant, Han Li vanished into thin air, revealing himself to be nothing more than an afterimage.

Hua Jing's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but in the next instant, an alarmed look suddenly appeared on his face as his body split up into four or five yellow shadows that sprang away in all directions.

Before the yellow shadows were able to get very far, countless streaks of golden sword qi erupted out of the very spot where Hua Jing had been standing just a moment ago, and all of the yellow shadows were caught in the barrage.

A roar of pain and fury rang out from within the flurry of sword qi, and a streak of yellow light flew out before retreating to tens of thousands of feet away, where it was revealed to be Hua Jing.

At this moment, his robes were in tatters, and his arms and legs were bleeding profusely, but a suit of black inner armor had appeared beneath his robes, protecting his vital regions.

However, the mask that he was wearing had been torn away, revealing the other half of his face, which was gray and wizened, resembling the bark of an old tree.

Hua Jing's face instantly became twisted with fury as he roared, "My mask! How dare you! I'm going to kill you!"

The golden light emanating from his body brightened significantly as around a dozen of the same yellow beastly head projections appeared around him, and each of them opened their mouths to release a burst of yellow light that struck the oncoming golden sword qi.

The bursts of yellow light were extremely formidable, and just like how the first one was able to tear through the golden lightning barrier with ease, these bursts of yellow light were able to vanquish the streaks of golden sword qi just as easily.

Chapter 807: Vanquishing the Enemy

Han Li flew out of the mass of crumbling golden sword qi, and as soon as he emerged, a burst of golden light instantly erupted out of his body to form a golden spirit domain that was several dozen kilometers in size.

At the same time, eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot out of his body before vanishing into thin air.

Hua Jing could sense the flow of time slowing down around him, and he immediately unleashed his own spirit domain, which was filled with flashing lights and countless flower petals, presenting a dizzying sight to behold.

He then hurriedly made a hand seal, and a pillar of yellow light shot down from the copper mirror above his head to encompass his entire body.

At the same time, a giant yellow bell that was over a hundred feet tall appeared around his own body, and he had only just adopted these defensive measures when the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot out of thin air to strike the yellow bell around him.

The giant bell shuddered violently, and the yellow light radiating from it flashed erratically for a moment, but then quickly settled down again.

Hua Jing was rather taken aback to see this.

By his estimates, the eighteen flying swords may not have been able to break through the bell projection around him, but they definitely should've been more powerful than this.

Right at this moment, a giant fist that was covered in purplish-golden scales emerged above the giant bell amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then gently struck the bell.

A resounding clang rang out as the giant bell was instantly smashed into pieces like porcelain, following which Han Li emerged out of thin air, having already unleashed his Holy Nirvana Physique.

Bursts of strange power were constantly infiltrating his mind from the nearby spirit domain, attempting to disrupt his senses, but he was able to retain his mental clarity thanks to his tremendous spiritual sense, and his other five fists slammed into the pillar of yellow light around Hua Jing in unison.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the space within a radius of several thousand feet warped significantly, and all of the yellow beastly heads around Hua Jing instantly exploded, while the pillar of yellow light was also shattered.

Even though Hua Jing hadn't been directly struck by the oncoming fists, just the shockwaves alone were enough to send him flying like a leaf in a storm, and blood gushed out of his mouth as he fled into the distance with an alarmed and fearful look on his face.

However, despite his best efforts, he was still only able to move very slowly in Han Li's time spirit domain.

A look of resolve flashed through his eyes as he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the copper mirror above his head, and a layer of crimson light instantly emerged over its surface before descending into his body.

Immediately thereafter, his body swelled drastically in size, while his skin took on a bright red coloration. Veins began to bulge all over his body, and his speed was enhanced by roughly twofold.

At the same time, dozens of identical streaks of yellow light appeared in the nearby space before fleeing in all directions.

All of the streaks of light were giving off identical auras, making it impossible to tell which one was the real Hua Jing.

Han Li harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him before releasing waves of golden ripples that spread through the air to encompass all of the streaks of yellow light, instantly immobilizing them.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, but right at this moment, a tremendous aura erupted out of one of the streaks of light up ahead.

The aura excelled far beyond Hua Jing's, almost reaching the Great Encompassment Stage, and it was still steadily elevating.

All of the golden ripples near that streak of yellow light began to buzz and tremble, looking as if they were on the verge of giving out.

Han Li hurriedly made a hand seal upon seeing this, and the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly shot forth through the air before converging toward that streak of yellow light.

In the blink of an eye, Hua Jing's body was reduced to a pile of mincemeat, and the tremendous aura that he was giving off instantly faded, restoring the nearby golden ripples to normal.

Han Li heaved another faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, and he reverted back to his human form.

After that, he swallowed a couple of pills, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure light, which swept up Hua Jing's remains and the yellow copper mirror.

At this point, the crimson light on the mirror had already faded, restoring it to its original color.

Han Li picked up the mirror with an intrigued look in his eyes.

This mirror was most likely Hua Jing's bonded treasure, and it was what he used to hypnotize others. Not only was the mirror capable of hypnotizing us, he had even used it to hypnotize himself at the end, allowing him to fully tap into his own latent potential to attain power that was close to the Great Encompassment Stage.

If it weren't for the recent strides that Han Li had made in his Spirit Refinement Technique, he may not have been able to withstand Hua Jing's hypnotism.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a burst of green light shot out to sweep up the mirror before sucking it into the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

After that, Han Li flicked a finger through the air to release a streak of azure light into Hua Jing's remains, and it quickly re-emerged with a yellow nascent soul.

A hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes as he grabbed onto the nascent soul, and he was just about to crush it when he suddenly stopped what he was doing and turned to take a glance at Shi Chuankong.

After a brief hesitation, he opened his mouth to release a ball of silver flames, which quickly flew in a circle around the yellow nascent soul, forming a series of fiery silver runes that imprinted themselves to its body.

Han Li then swept a sleeve through the air to release another ball of flames, which quickly incinerated Hua Jing's remains into ashes, leaving behind only a suit of black inner armor, a yellow bracelet, and carving of a yellow beastly head.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he drew the carving into his grasp.

It was only around the size of a human hand, and it was extremely intricate and life-like.

This was most likely what had just unleashed those formidable bursts of yellow light.

Even though the carving had a jade-like appearance, it felt more like something that had been carved out of bone.

He played with it for a moment before stowing it away to be examined some other time.

Han Li then also stowed the suit of black inner armor and the storage bracelet away, and only after that did he withdraw his spirit domain and Mantra Treasured Axis.

As soon as the golden ripples vanished, a horrified look immediately appeared on the face of Hua Jing's nascent soul, and a burst of yellow light emerged over its body.

However, right at this moment, silver flames shot out of the silver runes emblazoned onto its body, incinerating the yellow light and leaving a scorch mark on its body.

The nascent soul let loose an agonized howl while trembling violently.

"I've set up a true flame restriction on your body. That was just a warning. If you try any more funny business, I'll kill you right now," Han Li warned in a cold voice.

Hua Jing's nascent soul shuddered as it instantly fell still.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to recover his eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, then flew over to Shi Chuankong and the others.

"Let's be civilized about this, Fellow Daoist. There's no bad blood between us, we only just so happen to be serving different masters in conflict with each other. I'm sure you're protecting Shi Chuankong in exchange for some form of compensation. Out of all of the Holy Monarch's children, Shi Chuankong is the least remarkable one.

“I'm serving Her Highness, Shi Jingyan, and she possesses a tremendous amount of connections and resources, far more so than Shi Chuankong. On top of that, she's always looking out for more capable subordinates, so why don't you defect to her camp instead? I'm willing to put in a recommendation for you, and with your powers, you'll surely flourish under Her Highness.

“Whatever compensation Shi Chuankong has given you, Her Highness can double it, no, triple it!" Hua Jing implored in an urgent voice, trying to convince Han Li into defecting.

Han Li completely ignored Hua Jing's offer as he ordered, "Undo your Flower Mirror ability."

"You don't seem to be from our devil race. Instead, it looks more like you're a cultivator from the True Immortal Realm using devilish cultivation arts, so I'm assuming you don't know much about the current state of our Holy Realm.

“Right now, there's a very important event taking place in Night Sun City, and all of the princes and princesses are locked in a battle that concerns the fate of the entire Holy Realm. For High Zenith cultivators like ourselves, joining the wrong camp will spell instant death, so you have to think carefully..."

The nascent soul's voice was becoming more and more urgent as it spoke.

"Undo your Flower Mirror ability," Han Li repeated in a cold voice. "Don't make me say it a third time. I'm sure killing you would automatically undo the ability anyway, right?"

Hua Jing's nascent soul looked up at Han Li with its mouth gaped open in panic and agitation, and it was at a loss for words.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face, and the silver fire runes on the nascent soul's body instantly began to light up.

Black scorch marks were beginning to appear on the nascent soul's body, and it hurriedly yelled, "Alright, alright, I'll undo the ability right away! Please spare me!"

Immediately thereafter, it made a hand seal, and a strange red symbol appeared on the foreheads of Shi Chuankong's trio before fading away.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, and the silver flame restriction on Hua Jing's nascent soul subsided at his behest, following which several translucent chains flew out of the glabellas of Shi Chuankong's trio before vanishing into his body.

Their eyelids fluttered slightly before they opened their eyes, and all of them were looking deathly pale.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release three balls of azure light that fused into their bodies, and their complexions instantly improved slightly as they sat up from the ground.

"What happened just now, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked with a dazed expression, seemingly having no recollection of what had just transpired.

The dark-skinned elderly man and the woman in the red dress were also looking very confused.

All of a sudden, a thought sprang into Shi Chuankong's mind, and he hurriedly asked, "Where's Hua Jing? Did he get away?"

Chapter 808: Leaving the City

"He's here. I thought you'd have some things to ask him, so I spared his nascent soul," Han Li said as he tossed Hua Jing's nascent soul at Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong faltered slightly upon hearing this, but still caught Hua Jing's nascent soul, and a look of burning fury and resentment appeared in his eyes.

Hua Jing's nascent soul immediately began bowing in apology as it hurriedly said, "Please forgive me, Your Highness, I'm only acting under the instructions of someone else. If you spare me, I'm willing to defect to your camp. On top of that, I know a huge secret pertaining to you..."

However, Shi Chuankong had no intention of listening to it, and bright silver light began to glow from his hand as he closed his fingers.

Hua Jing's nascent soul instantly began to warp, and it struggled in a panic as it screeched, "Wait, you can't kill me! My master is Daoist Master Bone Shine! If you dare to kill me, then he'll definitely avenge me!"

Shi Chuankong completely ignored the nascent soul's pleas he closed his hand into a tight fist, and the nascent soul only had a chance to let loose a despairing cry before it disintegrated into specks of yellow light.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything.

Given how close Shi Chuankong had been with Elder Qi, he had to have been furious that Elder Qi had been killed under such tragic circumstances.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Shi Chuankong cupped his fist in a grateful salute toward Han Li as he said, "I must thank you again for saving me, Fellow Daoist Li."

"You're welcome, Fellow Daoist Shi. However, I think it would be wise for us not to ignore what Hua Jing said at the end there. I'm assuming this Daoist Master Bone Shine is a Great Encompassment cultivator, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. It seems like the current situation is even worse than I anticipated. Grain Mountain City is no longer safe, so we should leave this place as soon as possible," Shi Chuankong replied before taking several pills in succession.

The recently concluded battle had caused quite a commotion, and even though no one had arrived on the scene yet to see what had happened, news of what had happened here was most likely going to spread in no more than half a day.

"What do we do with them?" Han Li asked as he turned his gaze to the dark--skinned elderly man and the woman in the red dress.

The injuries sustained by the two were far more severe than Shi Chuankong's, and even though they had already woken up, they were completely unable to move.

They had overexerted themselves to the point that they were completely spent, and even their cultivation foundations had been severely damaged, so it was difficult to say whether they would be able to make a full recovery.

"I'm the one being targeted here, so as long as I leave Grain Mountain City, there should be no further attacks here, and we can leave them here to recover from their injuries," Shi Chuankong replied.

Han Li nodded in response.

"Please wait here for me for a moment, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of purple light, which picked up the dark-skinned elderly man and the woman in the red dress, then also collected the bodies and belongings of Elder Qi and the others before carrying them away into the distance.

Meanwhile, Han Li sat down on the spot with his legs crossed for some quick recovery.

Shortly thereafter, Shi Chuankong returned, and Han Li rose to his feet.

"Let's go," Shi Chuankong said as he summoned his flying carriage, and before long, the two of them had vanished into the distance.

……

Shi Chuankong's flying carriage had only just made it out of Grain Mountain City when he and Han Li spotted a streak of red light flying toward them.

"Another one so soon?" Han Li mused in a grim voice.

Shi Chuankong's brows also became tightly furrowed as he immediately stopped the flying carriage.

Inside the streak of red light was a crimson flying carriage, atop which stood a red-robed man, and the carriage stopped in its tracks over ten thousand feet away, following which the man declared, "Your Highness, I was instructed by the third prince to come and escort you."

Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with Han Li upon hearing this, then asked, "Do you have any proof of that?"

The red-robed man swept a sleeve through the air in response, releasing a streak of red light that flew toward Shi Chuankong, who hesitated momentarily before raising a hand to catch the object inside the streak of red light.

Han Li could see that it was a palm-sized crescent-shaped jade pendant, and there didn't seem to be any designs engraved upon it, but the lines on its surface were rather chaotic, giving it a rather indistinct appearance.

Shi Chuankong flipped his other hand over to summon an identical jade pendant, which was also riddled with many lines.

With one jade pendant in each hand, he brought the two together, and a burst of gentle white light arose from both pendants, following which they fused together to form a whole circular jade pendant.

The lines on the jade pendants connected to form a portrait of a woman with a pair of pointy ears. It was a very simple portrait, yet it was somehow able to perfectly convey the gentle emotions on her face.

Han Li could tell that the jade pendant had been crafted from a premium material, but it wasn't a powerful treasure by any means.

However, it seemed to be very important to Shi Chuankong, and a warm and reminiscent look appeared in his eyes as he examined the portrait of the woman on the jade pendant.

"It looks like he's telling the truth," Shi Chuankong said as he turned to Han Li, and only upon seeing this did the red-robed man continue to approach them.

The man was quite youthful in appearance, and his facial features were quite gentle and soft, with the exception of his eyes, which were thin and long, resembling a pair of long sabers that were giving off a sharp gleam.

"I am Xue Cheng, and I was sent by the third prince to escort you back to Night Sun City, Your Highness," the red-robed man declared as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"You're the Blood Drop Marquis? I've heard my brother mention you before, and he's always spoken very highly of you. He says that you've slain countless devilish beasts outside the Elegant Ripple Mountain Range, and that you're one of his most prized subordinates," Shi Chuankong said.

Xue Cheng faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a look of realization flashed through his eyes, and he smiled as he replied, "You must've misremembered, Your Highness. I've always been active in the southern primordial lands, and I've never even been to the Elegant Ripple Mountain Range. On top of that, with my lowly cultivation base, how could I possibly be considered one of His Highness's most prized subordinates."

Only after hearing this response was Shi Chuankong convinced that Xue Cheng was who he claimed himself to be, and he cupped his fist in another salute as he said, "My apologies for testing you, Fellow Daoist Xue."

"It's fine, it's a good thing that you're being so careful," Xue Cheng replied, and he turned his gaze to Han Li as he spoke, clearly very interested in him.

"This is Fellow Daoist Li Feiyu. He's been accompanying me on my journey and has saved my life on many occasions," Shi Chuankong introduced.

Han Li also cupped his fist in a salute toward Xue Cheng upon hearing this, and the latter returned his salute.

"What are your plans from here onward, Your Highness?" Xue Cheng asked.

"We were originally planning to travel to Chuyu City from Grain Mountain City, but enemy forces had already infiltrated the city, and the teleportation array in Grain Mountain City was destroyed, so I'll have to find another way to reach Chuyu City," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

"Are you traveling to Chuyu City for the teleportation array there?" Xue Cheng asked.

"That's right. The teleportation array in Chuyu City won't get us directly to Night Sun City, but it can take us to Sedge Prison City, and it's the fastest route back to the capital. Once we reach Sedge Prison City, it won't be difficult for us to fly back to Night Sun City even without using any further teleportation arrays," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"The teleportation array in Chuyu City is indeed able to facilitate super long distance teleportation, but it's not very accessible. Generally speaking, only those who possess the title of duke or above can apply to use the teleportation array, and unless it's used for official purposes, a huge sum of money will have to be issued to cover the teleportation costs," Xue Cheng said in a slightly hesitant manner.

"I don't possess any lofty official title, but I hold an important status in the Vast Origin House, and that will be enough for me to access the teleportation array once. As for the fee that needs to be issued, I can take care of that as well. The hard part is getting to Chuyu City," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"Seeing as the teleportation array in Grain Mountain City has already been destroyed, we'll have to go to another city to teleport to Chuyu City, but even the nearest city to Grain Mountain City has to be around ten years away," Xue Cheng mused.

"Ten years? That's too long," Han Li said with furrowed brows.

"There's no helping it. As long as we keep our guard up along the way, there shouldn't be any major problems," Xue Cheng disagreed.

"Do you know who it was that was wreaking havoc earlier in Grain Mountain City, Fellow Daoist Xue?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Who was it?" Xue Cheng asked.

"Hua Jing," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Isn't he the fifth princess's subordinate? Even the fifth princess is coming after you?" Xue Cheng asked with a surprised expression.

"The problem here is that we killed Hua Jing, and prior to his death, he claimed that his master, Daoist Master Bone Shine, would be coming after us for revenge," Shi Chuankong explained with a wry smile.

A grim look instantly appeared on Xue Cheng's face upon hearing this.

"Daoist Master Bone Shine is a Great Encompassment cultivator, and he's extremely protective of his disciples. On top of that, Hua Jing is his most prized disciple. If he comes after us, I'm afraid I won't be able to protect you even if I sacrifice my own life," Xue Cheng sighed.

"That's why Fellow Daoist Li was saying that ten years is too long," Shi Chuankong sighed.

After a long silence, Xue Cheng's eyes suddenly lit up slightly as he said, "Your Highness, I have a potential solution to our current predicament, but it's just a matter of whether you're willing to try out my solution."

"Go ahead," Shi Chuankong prompted.

Chapter 809: Formidable Enemy

Xue Cheng began to disclose his plan to Han Li and Shi Chuankong through voice transmission, and as the two listened, their expressions became more and more hesitant.

In the end, Shi Chuankong remained silent as he fell into deep thought.

"I think that's a feasible plan, but some of the finer details need to be adjusted," Han Li said, following which he also began to communicate something to Shi Chuankong and Xue Cheng through voice transmission.

After hearing what he had to say, Shi Chuankong finally nodded as he said, "There are no other feasible options open to us, so we'll have to follow this plan."

Shortly thereafter, the two of them flew onto Xue Cheng's flying carriage, which promptly departed.

……

Close to two years flew by in a flash.

A fiery crimson shadow was flying through the air at an astonishing speed over a certain forest in the Devil Realm.

Inside the streak of crimson light was a flying carriage that had a rather remarkable appearance, and there were three people standing on the carriage, led by a red-robed man who had a hand pressed down onto an array plate on the carriage, injecting a drop of his blood essence into it.

The three were none other than Han Li, Shi Chuankong, and Xue Cheng.

"Your Highness, we should be able to reach Sulfur Forest City in two months once we emerge from this forest. We're traveling quite a bit ahead of schedule, and we should be able to get to the Sulfur Forest City over a year earlier than anticipated," Xue Cheng said.

"Thank you for your hard work, Fellow Daoist Xue. If it weren't for your willingness to sacrifice your blood essence, we wouldn't have been able to get here so quickly," Shi Chuankong said.

"Don't thank me yet, Your Highness. Let's save that for when we reach Chuyu City," Xue Cheng said.

However, as soon as his voice trailed off, a thunderous roar abruptly rang out in the sky.

"You're not getting to Chuyu City on my watch!"

Immediately thereafter, a burst of transparent ripples appeared up ahead, and an invisible barrier that was hundreds of thousands of feet tall emerged, hovering at the very center of which was an elderly figure.

"It's Daoist Master Bone Shine!" Xue Cheng said in a grim voice.

"He still managed to find us, even though we've been so careful," Shi Chuankong sighed.

Han Li was quite alarmed by this turn of events, but his expression remained calm. He had already faced Great Encompassment cultivators in battle on several occasions up to this point, and as long as the enemy wasn't also cultivating one of the three paramount laws, he was confident that he would be able to escape, but he would have to leave Shi Chuankong behind.

Thankfully, they had made some plans for this exact scenario, and Shi Chuankong had many tricks up his sleeve as well, so he wasn't completely doomed.

Daoist Master Bone Shine was a tall and thin elderly man who was missing a chunk of skin and flesh on his forehead, revealing the bone underneath, and he was wearing a dark green daoist robe.

"You think you can just get away without consequence after killing my disciple?" Daoist Master Bone Shine asked in a furious voice.

"Senior Bone Shine, it was your disciple who came after His Highness first, and he was struck down in an act of self defense," Xue Cheng said in an urgent voice as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I don't care about all of that! The ones who killed my disciple must pay with their lives!" Daoist Master Bone Shine roared as bursts of spatial ripples began to surge through the air around him.

"Split up and run!" Xue Cheng yelled, and as soon as his voice trailed off, Shi Chuankong and Han Li immediately darted away in two different directions.

As for Xue Cheng himself, he threw himself directly at Daoist Master Bone Shine as a series of crimson runes appeared over his exposed skin, and he seized the initiative by throwing the first attack in the form of an almighty punch.

At the same time, countless crimson shadows erupted out of his back, then converged to form a giant crimson devilish projection that also clenched its barbed fist before throwing a punch at Daoist Master Bone Shine.

"Insolent fool!" Daoist Master Bone Shine sneered as he raised a fist of his own and lashed out in retaliation, while white light surged over his entire body, and all of his joints were also popping and cracking audibly.

All of the flesh and skin on his outstretched fist peeled away to reveal the shimmering white bones underneath, all of which were etched with peculiar golden patterns.

The two fists clashed amid a resounding boom, and a burst of ferocious shockwaves swept through the air in all directions.

All of the space within a radius of several hundred feet collapsed inward before rapidly expanding outward, and an enormous round crater appeared on the ground, with all of the mountains and forestry inside reduced to dust.

The giant crimson devilish projection was the first to give out, and it exploded violently in the face of Daiost Master Bone Shine's fist.

All of the bones in Xue Cheng's arm were also shattered, and most of his arm had been reduced to a mangled mass of flesh and blood as he flew back through the air like a broken kite.

In contrast, Daoist Master Bone Shine appeared to be completely unscathed, and he charged forward in pursuit before plunging a hand straight through the left side of Xue Cheng's chest, with his hand ultimately protruding out of Xue Cheng's back.

However, not a single drop of blood was flowing out of the gaping hole in Xue Cheng's chest. Instead, the torn flesh there was squirming as if it were a living creature, attempting to corrode Daoist Master Bone Shine's arm.

A cold sneer appeared on Daoist Master Bone Shine's face as countless white bone spikes erupted out of his arm, giving it the appearance of a mace, and Xue Cheng's chest was instantly torn apart.

The pieces of Xue Cheng's body drifted out of the sky like shredded rags, only to disintegrate into globules of blood that fused back together, then rapidly darted back in retreat before reverting back into Xue Cheng.

Out of the corner of his eye, Daoist Master Bone Shine could see that Han Li and Shi Chuankong had already gotten very far away, and his expression instantly darkened slightly.

He raised a hand before spreading his fingers open, and a ball of white light surged out of the palm of his hand, forming a massive spirit domain that encompassed the surrounding space.

The spirit domain was filled with faint white mist, and seven or eight white pagodas could be seen within it.

Every single one of those pagodas was constructed from tens of thousands of bones, and at the top of each pagoda was an eerie green flame.

This is a Creation Tier spirit domain!

A grim look instantly appeared on Xue Cheng's face upon seeing this.

Trapped in Daoist Master Bone Shine's spirit domain, Xue Cheng could feel all of the bones in his body trembling violently, and it was as if they were threatening to tear their way out of his body to become part of the bone pagodas.

He channeled his devilish power with all his might, conjuring up a layer of protective light around his own body, but before he had a chance to do anything else, Daoist Master Bone Shine swept a sleeve through the air, all of the bone pagodas began to move rapidly, quickly forming a circle around Xue Cheng.

Immediately thereafter, the green flames on top of the pagodas brightened significantly, and ghostly green flames appeared in the eye sockets of all of the skulls on the pagodas, giving off a strange and powerful aura.

All of a sudden, Xue Cheng felt his entire body tighten as his skin was stretched taut, following which a series of extremely irregular large bulges appeared over his body, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

A string of faint thuds rang out as countless tiny gashes appeared over his skin, and bone splinters began to jut out of those gashes, threatening to fly out of his body.

Xue Cheng hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air with an alarmed expression upon seeing this, summoning a dark red spirit domain that encompassed his entire body.

The spirit domain was only around a thousand feet in size, but it was extremely dense, and bursts of crimson qi were swirling around him, quickly healing all of the gashes on his body while also suppressing the unrest in his bones.

Daoist Master Bone Shine harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and at this point, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were already completely out of sight.

All of a sudden, he reached out with hands, then swiped them over his own rib cage, and two of his ribs pierced their way out of his skin, following which he casually tossed them away in two different directions.

The two ribs shot forth through the air at an incredible speed, covering a distance of close to a hundred thousand kilometers in the blink of an eye, and it didn't take long at all before they caught up to Shi Chuankong and Han Li.

A burst of white light flashed several dozen kilometers away from Han Li, and the rib that was pursuing him took on a human form, transforming into an avatar of Daoist Master Bone Shine.

The avatar let loose a loud roar as it sped up even further amid an eruption of white light, and it was almost able to instantly catch up to Han Li.

Han Li hurriedly sped up as well, but for some reason, his speed was only elevated for a moment before he slowed down again, as if he didn't have the power required to maintain his elevated speed.

A cold sneer appeared on the avatar's face as it pounced at Han Li while reaching out with one hand, and five barely visible spatial indentations appeared up ahead, catching Han Li to prevent him from getting away.

Chapter 810: Sneaking Into Chuyu City

Han Li was instantly forced to an abrupt halt, and a pained look appeared on his face as the surrounding space constricted toward him from all directions.

Daoist Master Bone Shine's avatar chortled with glee as it spread open the fingers of one hand before swiping them downward, and a shimmering white bone claw appeared above Han Li before descending upon him with tremendous force.

A panicked look appeared on Han Li's face as he clenched both hands into tight fists and lashed out at the bone claw in retaliation.

A dull thump rang out as his fists clashed against the bone claw, but his resistance was instantly overwhelmed, and the bone claw continued to crash down with unrivaled power directly upon Han Li's head.

At this point, Han Li was still completely unable to move, and the protective spiritual light around him quickly disintegrated, following which his body was also pulverized.

The avatar was initially ecstatic to see this, but its expression then suddenly stiffened as it realized that something wasn't right.

As it turned out, Han Li's body had shrunk down into a red bean that was riddled with cracks, and a drop of golden blood essence was evaporating on its surface, rising up as a plume of white smoke.

At the same time, a rabbit mask from the Transient Guild slowly fell out of the sky.

Almost at the exact same time, Shi Chuankong's body had also been pulverized by another bone claw elsewhere several hundred thousand kilometers away, but that had been nothing more than a ruse as well.

After recovering his avatars, a furious look appeared on Daoist Master Bone Shine's face, and he turned his gaze to Xue Cheng, who was surrounded by the bone pagodas.

Despite the perilous situation that he was in, Xue Cheng didn't attempt to get away, nor did he appear particularly panicked.

Daoist Master Bone Shine took a deep breath to suppress his own fury, then said, "I'll admit that it's very impressive that you were able to create avatars convincing enough to fool even me. However, I'm in a very bad mood right now, so if you want to live, then you'd better tell me where those two are right now!"

There were several other cities near Sulfur Forest City that had teleportation arrays leading to Chuyu City, so it was most likely the case that Han Li and Shi Chuankong had traveled to one of those cities.

"You think I would just tell you where they are after going to such great lengths to create those blood essence avatars and even using myself as bait to lure you away?" Xue Cheng sneered with a derisive expression.

"Fine! I'll just have to pluck out your soul and find out for myself then!" Daoist Master Bone Shine roared as he swept both sleeves through the air, and his spirit domain instantly began to rapidly contract, converging around Xue Cheng's spirit domain. At the same time, all of the skulls on the bone pagodas rose up into the air, and the green flames in their eye sockets began to burn significantly brighter as they swarmed at Xue Cheng from all directions.

However, right at this moment, Xue Cheng flipped a hand over to produce a jade talisman, which he crushed in the palm of his hand, instantly releasing an incredibly formidable burst of spatial power that formed a door of black light behind him.

Before Daoist Master Bone Shine had a chance to do anything, Xue Cheng had already taken a step back and vanished into the door of light.

All Daoist Master Bone Shine could do was throw a punch in futility, and his fist struck the space before him with a thunderous boom.

Some time later, the commotion gradually subsided, and Daoist Master Bone Shine was also looking much more composed.

He took a glance at Sulfur Forest City, then murmured to himself, "I don't know which city you've gone to, but I can wait for you in Chuyu City! You're dreaming if you think you can get to Night Sun City alive!"

At the same time, there were two figures slowly descending out of the outside Preeminent City.

These two were none other than Han Li and Shi Chuankong, who had circled all the way back to Preeminent City. At this moment, they were disguised to look like a pair of twin brothers, and their cultivation bases had also been restrained to the late-True Immortal Stage.

The plan that Xue Cheng had proposed was for him to travel to Sulfur Forest City with a pair of his blood refined Dao Warriors posing as Han Li and Shi Chuankong. Essentially, he was using himself as bait, while Han Li and Shi Chuankong traveled to another city to get to Chuyu City.

However, Han Li felt like this was quite a risky plan as none of the neighboring cities were very far away from Sulfur Forest City, so if Xue Cheng's ruse were to fail, then Daoist Master Bone Shine would easily be able to travel to the other cities in pursuit of Han Li and Shi Chuankong. Hence, they had decided to circle back to Preeminent City.

It shouldn't have taken them this long to return to Preeminent City from Grain Mountain City, but they had taken a very cautious approach over the entire journey, not even daring to fly at full speed for fear of exposing themselves, and that was why they had only just gotten back to Preeminent City.

"Looks like your third brother really is an ally we can count on, and Xue Cheng has also proven himself to be extremely loyal, willing to lure away a Great Encompassment cultivator for your sake," Han Li remarked.

"Out of all of my brother's subordinates, Xue Cheng isn't the most powerful one, but he's always been the most loyal. I hadn't actually ever met Xue Cheng prior to this, but I had heard my brother speak about him on multiple occasions. If we're ever reunited in Night Sun City, I'll be sure to compensate him handsomely," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

Shortly thereafter, the two of them made their way into Preeminent City, and after hailing a carriage, they traveled straight to the city lord's manor.

"I don't know much about the Heavenly Ax Marquis, but judging from what you and Xue Cheng have told me, he seems to be a very ambitious man. Ambitious people like him are always very unpredictable, so we really are taking a gamble here," Han Li said.

"He chose to stand by and do nothing last time when we were being attacked in the Cloud Mountain Inn, we can only hope that he continues to turn a blind eye to us. As long as he let's us leave without interference, I'll owe him a great favor," Shi Chuankong replied.

With that, the two of them fell silent, lost in their own thoughts.

The city lord's manor was an enormous place, with the front half consisting of the city lord's office, while the back half was the Heavenly Ax Marquis's private residence.

There was a round pagoda that was around six to seven stories tall in the area between the office and the private residence, and that was the teleportation pagoda of Preeminent City.

In order to access the teleportation arrays in Preeminent City, one had to undergo a stringent screening process.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were stopped in their tracks by some guards upon reaching the entrance of the city lord's manor, and Shi Chuankong stepped forward before presenting a pair of brand new identity tokens.

Under their new identities, they were a pair of twin brothers from a prominent clan in the Devil Realm's central region, and their names were Yu Zhongyan and Yu Zhongmiao.

The guards were led by an elderly cultivator, and his expression eased slightly after examining their identity tokens, following which he asked, "Are you carrying the Yu Clan's emblem with you?"

Shi Chuankong was already prepared, and he flipped a hand over to produce a pair of round metal badges, upon each of which was engraved a ferocious horned beast, beneath which was a "Yu" character.

The elderly cultivator examined the pair of metal badges for a moment, then granted Han Li and Shi Chuankong entry into the city lord's manor.

"Thank you, Senior," Shi Chuankong hurriedly said in a grateful voice before stepping into the manor.

Right as they passed through the gate, the sensory array overhead flashed every so slightly, and it was just about to light up to indicate that it had detected something amiss when Shi Chuankong pulled out a small copper mirror before flashing it at the array in a covert fashion.

The faint light flashing from the array instantly faded before the guards stationed at the gate noticed anything, and they were able to pass through without incident.

Both of them heaved an internal sigh of relief as they began to make their way into the manor.

Security in the city lord's manor was very tight, and not only were there cultivators stationed at set intervals, there were also groups of patrolling cultivators that were constantly roaming the area. Han Li and Shi Chuankong kept their heads down as they walked along, and it didn't take them long to reach the teleportation pagoda.

There was a long line of people waiting to enter the pagoda, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong joined the back of the line.

As time passed, the people ahead of them made their way into the pagoda one after another, and their turn quickly arrived.

Upon entering the pagoda, they spotted a teleportation array with eighteen ornate pillars around it, standing within which were three men who were waiting for the array to be activated.

Standing outside the array was a middle-aged cultivator holding an array plate, as well as three groups of guards.

To the right of the pagoda's entrance was a wooden table, behind which sat a black-robed elderly man, and he asked, "Where are you going?"

"We're traveling to Chuyu City, Senior," Shi Chuankong hurriedly replied.

"You're in luck. There are still three open spots for teleportation to Chuyu City today, so you'll only have to wait for one more person to join you," the black-robed elderly man said.

"How long will that take?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"How am I supposed to know? It's all up to luck. Perhaps someone will show up right away, perhaps no one will show up for the rest of the day," the black-robed elderly man replied.

Chapter 811: Merciless

Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions instantly stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

"We have some urgent business to take care of, would it be possible to teleport just the two of us, Senior?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Yes, but the two of you will have to issue the teleportation fee that's meant to be split among three people. On top of that, it'll cost more to teleport to Chuyu City than elsewhere. Do you still want to go?" the black-robed elderly man asked.

Shi Chuankong feigned a hesitant expression as he turned to Han Li and said, "It's going to cost extra, but we really are in a hurry. If we don't get to Chuyu City in time, our clan leader is going to be furious with us. Should we do it?"

Han Li immediately played along as he replied, "If we don't get to Chuyu City by tonight, our clan leader is definitely going to punish us. I think we'll just have to foot the bill and hope that our clan leader gives us an additional reward to cover the costs."

"We'll cover the teleportation cost between the two of us, Senior," Shi Chuankong decided as he turned to the black-robed elderly man and cupped his fist in a salute.

"In that case, you can issue the fee and go wait by the array. Once the people ahead of you have been teleported away, it'll be your turn. Also, show me your identity tokens, I need to take some records," the black-robed elderly man said.

Once again, Shi Chuankong produced another new pair of identity tokens before handing them over.

Upon taking a glance at the identity tokens, the black-robed elderly man's expression instantly changed slightly, and he hurriedly rose to his feet as he cupped his fist in a salute and said, "Please forgive me, I didn't realize you were servants of the Balance Fall Duke!"

"There's no need to salute us, Senior, we're nothing more than a pair of lowly servants," Shi Chuankong hurriedly said as he returned the salute.

"The Balance Fall Duke is vastly renowned across our entire Holy Realm. Even if you're only servants of his, that's still nothing to be scoffed at. Rest assured, I'll arrange for your teleportation as soon as this group leaves," the black-robed elderly man said with a reverent look on his face.

"In that case, we'll be in your care, Senior. However, the rules are still the rules, and we'll issue the teleportation fee as per usual," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

The black-robed elderly man was very pleased with Shi Chuankong's consideration and easygoing demeanor, and the atmosphere between the two immediately warmed up a little.

"Who is this Balance Fall Duke? It seems like he's a very respected man," Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"The Balance Fall Duke and my third brother are one and the same," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Your brother is a duke?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. My father has always been very strict when it comes to assigning official titles to his children, and such titles must be earned through accolades in battle. Out of all of my siblings, only fewer than half possess official titles. Among them, my eldest brother, Shi Zhanfeng, possesses the highest official title of grand duke, while my third brother and fifth sister are duke and duchess. As for the rest, most of them hold the marquis title," Shi Chuankong replied.

"It seems like this man's admiration for your brother goes beyond that for a normal duke. Is there something special about your brother's title?" Han Li asked.

"Even among dukes, there is a certain hierarchy and also differences in assigned territories. My third brother is one of the three most highly rated dukes, while my fifth sister is a little lower on the pecking order. On top of that, my third brother has always been known to be a very fair and just man, so he had many admirers across the entire Holy Realm," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"I see."

As the two of them were conversing with each other through voice transmission, the black-robed elderly man completed his records, then led them to the teleportation array, and he issued some instructions to the cultivator holding the array plate before returning to his table.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong waited patiently as the teleportation array began to light up, but right at this moment, the two of them exchanged an alarmed glance with each other.

"He really did catch him... What a close call..." Shi Chuankong mused.

"The fact that he went after Xue Cheng means that our plan succeeded," Han Li said.

"We really led that old bastard on a wild goose chase! Once we get to Chuyu City, we'll leave right away, and he shouldn't have enough time to intercept us," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"I wonder how Xue Cheng is doing now," Han Li mused with a concerned expression, and both of them fell silent.

Before long, the light in the teleportation array faded, and the three people in the array had been teleported away. The cultivator holding the array plate replaced the Devilish Origin Stones in the array, following which Han Li and Shi Chuankong were ushered inside.

The two of them made their way to the center of the array, and the cultivator holding the array plate began to initiate the array's activation.

The array began to rumble as specks of silver light rose up from the ground before enveloping the two of them like a swarm of fireflies.

Right as the array was about to be activated, the array plate in the cultivator's hand suddenly exploded without any warning, and the light in the array instantly died down.

Immediately thereafter, a streak of purplish-golden light flew into the pagoda at an astonishing speed.

The guards in the pagoda were just about to spring into action, but upon catching a clear glimpse of the "intruder", they immediately fell to their knees as they greeted, "We pay our respects to the esteemed city lord!"

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he cast his gaze toward the middle-aged man who had just stormed into the pagoda. He had a pair of large and piercing eyes, a tall nose, and lips that were as thin as the edge of a blade.

"Could you not have turned a blind eye?" Shi Chuankong sighed with a wry smile.

"I already let you go once. You really shouldn't have come back," the Heavenly Ax Marquis sighed.

"Is there really no room for negotiation?" Shi Chuankong asked.

The Heavenly Ax Marquis offered no response. Instead, he merely declared in a cold voice, "There are wanted fugitives here that need to be detained! Everyone else, get out of here and make sure one approaches this pagoda. Anyone who tries to get in my way will be killed on the spot!"

At the same time, a burst of vast devilish qi surged out of his body alongside a mid-Great Encompassment Stage aura, and all of the people that were waiting to be teleported immediately rushed out of the pagoda in a blind panic.

They were quickly followed by the cultivators from the city lord's manor, and as the black-robed elderly man departed, he couldn't help but take a resentful glance at Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

Everyone fled to the front yard of the city lord's manor before looking back at the pagoda, and a few moments later, a resounding boom rang out as a burst of devilish qi erupted into the heavens, scattering all of the clouds in the sky.

At the same time, the teleportation pagoda exploded violently, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions, and around a dozen nearby buildings were also razed to the ground.

The cultivators standing on guard duty hurriedly sprang into action, forming arrays to withstand the shockwaves, and only then did they prevent the destruction of the entire city lord's manor.

Immediately thereafter, the Heavenly Ax Marquis suddenly flew out of the wreckage of the teleportation pagoda, and he took a cold glance at all of the bystanders, then departed without a word.

The black-robed elderly man had thought that he would be held responsible for this incident, and he was already prepared to die, so he couldn't help but weep from elation at the Heavenly Ax Marquis's inaction.

......

Over three months passed by in a flash.

Inside the city lord's manor of Chuyu City was a majestic building with a dome roof, within which was a giant teleportation array. Several figures appeared within the array amid a flash of silver light, then stepped out of the array before making their way out of the pagoda.

There were two elderly men seated behind a table at the entrance of the pagoda, one of whom was dressed in a dark green daoist robe, and he was staring intently at the people emerging from the array.

This man was none other than Daoist Master Bone Shine, and he had already been waiting for Han Li and Shi Chuankong here for over three months.

The people that had just stepped out of the array were very much disgruntled by his intrusive gaze, but they didn't dare to do anything, and they could only hurriedly depart.

The elderly man seated beside Daoist Master Bone Shine was the cultivator responsible for making records and collecting teleportation fees, and his nerves had also been worn very thin over the past three months.

"It's already been so long, Senior Bone Shine. If the people you were waiting for were going to arrive, then they would've done so long ago. I'm thinking they most likely went to some other city," the Golden Immortal said in a hesitant voice.

"It looks like I've been played for a fool again," Daoist Master Bone Shine sighed.

The Golden Immortal didn't know who Daoist Master Bone Shine was waiting for, but he had no intention of asking.

Three months ago, the city lord had instructed him to let Daoist Master Bone Shine do whatever he pleased, telling him that he didn't have to provide Daoist Master Bone Shine with any assistance, nor was he to ask any questions.

"Please thank City Lord Ouyang in my stead. I'll be sure to visit him in his manor sometime," Daoist Master Bone Shine said as he rose to his feet.

"I'll be sure to do so, Senior," the Golden Immortal hurriedly replied as he also stood up.

Daoist Master Bone Shine took one final glance at the teleportation array, then departed from the pagoda.

Chapter 812: Nurtured

The Mountain Lake Region was situated in the south of the Devil Realm, and as its name suggested, it was a region that was abundant with mountains and lakes.

East Mountain City was an unremarkable little border city inside the region, and it stood at the foot of East View Mountain. To the west of the city was an enormous lake that had a radius of hundreds of kilometers, and its close proximity to both the mountain and the lake made for some splendid scenery.

Every morning, when the sun began to rise over the lake, devilish qi would also rise up into the air from the surface of the lake, presenting a peculiar and stunning sight to behold.

East View Mountain was only around ten thousand feet tall, but the view on the mountain summit was exceptional, making it the perfect location to observe the devilish qi phenomenon.

Many devilish cultivators felt the devilish qi in their own bodies resonate whenever they gazed upon this phenomenon, and that accelerated their cultivation to a certain extent. Hence, there were always many low-grade devilish cultivators gathered on the mountain summit every morning.

On this day, the devilish qi phenomenon had just faded, and all of the cultivators on the mountain summit began to depart.

Meanwhile, a gray-robed hunch-backed elderly man and a tall young man with a wooden expression were making their way down the mountain along a set of stone steps.

The young man had a rather dull and unintelligent appearance, but his eyes were very bright and pure.

"Why did you come all this way just to see this devilish qi phenomenon, Brother Shi? Surely at your cultivation base, seeing such a phenomenon makes no difference to your cultivation," the young man asked.

"I've been growing a little frustrated after spending so much time on the run, so I decided to come here purely for some sightseeing to help me relax," the hunch-backed elderly man explained.

These two were none other than Han Li and Shi Chuankong in disguise, and Han Li said, "Even now, I still don't understand why the Heavenly Ax Marquis decided to let us go on that day. On top of that, he even warned us not to travel to Chuyu City."

"Honestly, I'm at a complete loss too. At the time, I thought we were doomed. Perhaps it has something to do with my brother. Clearly, I'm nowhere near important enough on my own to sway his decision-making," Shi Chuankong replied.

"He really had to go all-out back there. In order to convince everyone that we were dead, he had to destroy an entire teleportation pagoda. That's surely going to cost a lot to rebuild," Han Li chuckled.

"After hearing his warning, it made me realize that not only can we not go to Chuyu City, we'll also have to avoid all of the other cities that have teleportation arrays leading to Night Sun City," Shi Chuankong suddenly said.

"Indeed. Right now, everyone thinks that we're in a hurry to get back to Night Sun City, so they'll be sure to have set up measures to intercept us in those cities. If we proceed recklessly and run into another Great Encompassment cultivator, I can't guarantee that our luck won't run out," Han Li replied with a nod.

"That's why it's more important than ever for us to be patient, and we'll have to keep teleporting between regions to slowly inch closer and closer to Night Sun City," Shi Chuankong said with a wry smile.

"If we do that, it'll definitely take us longer to get to Night Sun City, but there are many benefits to such a plan as well. After all, there are many cities with teleportation arrays leading to different regions, so no one will be able to predict the route that we take," Han Li mused in a contemplative manner.

"The only problem is that what I promised you will have to be delayed, as will your return to the Immortal Realm," Shi Chuankong said with a hint of guilt in his eyes.

"It's fine. If it's possible, let's stay on East View Mountain for a little longer. I have some things that I need to take care of, and we can continue our journey once I'm done. Is that alright?" Han Li asked.

"Sure, let's do as you say, Brother Li," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

The two of them continued to walk along as they chatted, and they made their way down a winding mountain path to arrive at a secluded cliff.

From there, Shi Chuankong swept a sleeve through the air, and a spatial barrier faded away, revealing a pair of newly dug out cave abodes next to each other.

The two of them bade farewell to each other, then returned to their cave abodes.

Upon entering his cave abode, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, then stepped into it to arrive at the entrance of his spirit medicine garden.

Daoist Xie was already waiting there, and he said, "Fellow Daoist Han, the Dao Warriors in the garden have already matured. I've been suppressing them with the power of the array for now, and they're ready to be harvested."

"Thank you for your hard work," Han Li replied before quickly making his way into the garden.

The two of them made their way to the area of the garden where the Dao Warriors had been planted, and even from afar, they could hear the sound of zapping electricity.

Upon approaching the area, Han Li discovered that the Lightning Aura Soil there had almost completely dried up, and the earth had become parched and cracked, indicating that the lightning power the soil contained had already been completely exhausted.

In stark contrast, the Dao Warrior Tree was glowing, and its branches were laden with supple bean pods that had tiny arcs of purple lightning flashing over them.

Compared with the previous harvest, the tree clearly had more bean pods hanging from it on this occasion, and the aura that they were giving off was also noticeably more formidable, both of which were naturally very encouraging sights for Han Li.

He had expended all of his Dao Warriors during his breakthrough in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, so this batch had come at a perfect time.

"Remove the Array, Brother Xie. It's time to harvest," Han Li said with a smile.

Daoist Xie nodded in response before making a hand seal, and seven or eight golden array plates flew out of the soil around the Dao Warrior Tree before flying back into his hand.

A transparent light barrier vanished from the tree, and the faint crackling electricity instantly swelled to a thunderous rumbling as radiant purple light began to swell in all directions.

Han Li was slightly taken aback to see this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure light, which formed a light barrier around the Dao Warrior Tree to contain the purple lightning so that it didn't damage the other spirit plants in the garden.

A string of thunderclaps rang out as the Dao Warrior Tree rapidly wilted, and the tree distributed all of its remaining energy to the bean pods.

Immediately thereafter, the expanding purple lightning erupted, and golden beans with purple lightning patterns on their surface flew out in all directions.

Han Li flipped a hand over upon seeing this, and the Profound Heavenly Gourd instantly appeared in his grasp.

He tipped the gourd forward before patting its underside, and a green vortex immediately appeared at the mouth of the gourd, sucking in all of the golden beans.

The rumbling in the spirit medicine garden dragged on for several minutes before finally subsiding, and by then, thousands of beans had already been sucked into the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

He shook the gourd in one hand while holding a golden primary bean in the other hand, and a hint of disappointment flashed through his eyes. On this occasion, the Dao Warrior Tree had only yielded a single primary bean.

He injected a burst of immortal spiritual power into the primary, and a burst of purple lightning instantly erupted out of the lightning patterns on its surface, striking Han Li's entire arm with a numb sensation.

"This purple lightning seems to be quite formidable, and it's also retained some of the sticky properties of the Lightning Aura Soil," Daoist Xie remarked.

"Indeed. I wonder if these properties will enhance the Dao Warriors in any way," Han LI mused.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I just so happen to know of an Extreme Purple Lightning Array that would perhaps be better suited to these Dao Warriors than the Lightning Origin Locking Array. If you trust me, then you can leave these Dao Warriors for me to refine," Daoist Xie proposed after a brief hesitation.

"Of course I trust you, Brother Xie. I'll nurture these Dao Warriors in my Profound Heavenly Gourd for some time, then hand them over to you. If you require any materials for the array, just compile a list and give it to me," Han Li replied with a smile.

Daoist Xie cupped his fist in a salute upon hearing this.

"By the way, if you recall any other information pertaining to your former owner, make sure to tell me. Seeing as your former owner from the Devil Realm, and we're in the Devil Realm right now, I may be able to fulfill his final wish here," Han Li said.

"I've been trying to recover some more memories, but to no avail," Daoist Xie replied in a resigned manner.

"It's fine. Barring any mishaps, we should be staying in the Devil Realm for a while longer," Han Li replied with a nod.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before Han Li left the spirit medicine garden before making his way to the bamboo building near the pond.

Upon arriving on the second floor, he discovered that Weeping Soul was still laying unconscious on the bed.

The Purple Sun Warm Jade hovering on head had been significantly whittled down, to the point that there was only a small piece left.

Even though he knew this wasn't very effective, Han Li still pulled out another piece of mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade before replacing it with the one on Weeping Soul's head.

Thankfully, even though she remained unconscious, her aura fluctuations were becoming more and more stable, much to Han Li's relief. However, he still had no idea how to treat her condition, and he could only hope that a solution would arise once he arrived in Night Sun City.

At this point, Shi Chuankong had already been attacked by Shi Zhanfeng and Shi Jingyan, and there was no telling who else would come after him in the future, so it was certainly not going to be a smooth journey to Night Sun City, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as this thought arose in his mind.

Chapter 813: Sprout

Two Months later.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were seated across from each other on a pair of long benches in a pavilion outside East Mountain City.

"Brother Shi, I've been thinking the past few days, and I feel like it would be best for us to avoid using the teleportation array in East Mountain City," Han Li mused.

"Why is that?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"We should avoid appearing in the city on multiple occasions as much as possible. There's no guarantee that there are no high-grade cultivators or spies of your eldest brother's lurking in these cities, so it'll be safer for us if we show ourselves as little as possible," Han Li explained.

"That does make sense. My eldest brother's intelligence network isn't as extensive as my third brother's, but he's certainly no slouch in that regard. Otherwise, he wouldn't have become aware of our arrival in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range so quickly," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"According to the map that you gave me earlier, the nearest city to East Mountain City is Connected Phoenix City. Let's go there, then immediately continue onward to Seven Lake City, and we'll rest for a while once we get there," Han Li proposed.

"Are you suggesting that we disrupt our own itinerary so no one can predict where we're going?" Shi Chuankong asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"The more confused they are, the safer we'll be," Han Li confirmed with a nod.

"Impressive as always, Brother Li. If it wasn't for you, we wouldn't even have been able to survive that ordeal with Daoist Master Bone Shine. We'll do as you say," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

With the decision made, the two of them flew away into the distance atop Shi Chuankong's flying carriage.

Over ten years flew by in a flash.

On this day, a black flying carriage was racing over a primitive forest, carrying Han Li and Shi Chuankong, who had disguised themselves as an azure-robed scholar and a man clad in a suit of azure armor, respectively.

"I didn't think that it would take a whole decade to travel from the Mountain Lake Region to the neighboring Sunken Mountain Region," Shi Chuankong mused.

"It was always going to take far longer to travel without the use of teleportation arrays, and on top of that, we're regularly being attacked by devilish beasts, so that'll naturally slow us down as well," Han Li replied.

"The devilish beasts of our Holy Realm are extremely aggressive and territorial, and if anyone enters their territory, they'll often rush straight into battle, even if the opponent is far more formidable than themselves. Take that Devilish Bone Dove as an example: it was only at the early-Golden Immortal Stage, yet it pursued us for over three months," Shi Chuankong said with a wry smile.

"We would've killed that thing long ago had we not been worried that doing so would cause too much of a commotion and attract the attention of others. Let's be more careful from now on and do our best to avoid the areas where those powerful devilish beasts reside," Han Li said.

"Mountain Seal City is not far up ahead. Once we get there, we'll be able to use the teleportation array in the city to reach the midwestern region of the Holy Realm. Most of that region is my eldest brother's territory, so we have to be even more careful there," Shi Chuankong said.

"In that case, let's rest in Mountain Seal City for a while," Han Li replied with a nod.

"That's not a bad idea. Mountain Seal City is the second-largest city in the Sunken Mountain Region, and it's quite a thriving business hub, so we can replenish our supplies here too," Shi Chuankong said.

With the decision made, the two of them sped up as they made their way toward the city.

Upon entering the city, they first went to an inn and rented a pair of unremarkable and relatively cheap courtyards to stay in. After that, they split up to visit the renowned shopping streets in the city.

There weren't many things that were useful to Han Li in the Devil Realm, but thankfully, he didn't need to purchase much. All he was looking for were some lightning-attribute array materials like Lightning Restraining Wood.

Hence, he was able to get almost everything on his shopping list after passing through just one shopping street.

All that's left is the Lightning Dust Bead, but that's not going to be easy to find, Han Li thought to himself as he stood at the end of the shopping street.

He then left the street and traveled eastward onto another street, and only late that night did he return to the inn.

Upon returning to his courtyard, he activated all of the restrictions before entering the Flower Branch domain, arriving in the new bamboo building near the spirit medicine garden.

Daoist Xie was already waiting outside, and he approached Han Li as he asked, "How did it go?"

"I've managed to gather everything with the exception of the Lightning Dust Bead," Han Li sighed.

"It's no surprise that it's proving to be difficult to find these materials in the Devil Realm, but the Lightning Dust Bead is crucial for stimulating and the replenishing the lightning power in the Dao Warriors, and without it, the powers of the Dao Warriors won't be enhanced by much at all," Daoist Xie said.

"Is that the only purpose of the Lightning Dust Bead?" Han Li asked.

"That's its primary purpose. It also has some other effects, but those are negligible," Daoist Xie replied.

"In that case, I don't think it's necessary at all," Han Li said with a smile.

"Why is that?" Daoist Xie asked.

Han Li offered no response as he flipped a hand over to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd, then gently patted its underside, and a streak of purplish-golden light flew out from within, containing a shimmering, golden bean.

Daoist Xie's brows furrowed slightly as he caught the bean, and he immediately felt a powerful burst of electricity surge through his body.

He raised an eyebrow as he tightened his grip around the bean, and a loud thunderclap rang out as purplish-golden lightning erupted out of the tiny bean like a pair of giant lightning wings.

"How is this possible?" Daoist Xie exclaimed. "There's no way that the Lightning Aura Soil alone would've been able to nurture such a powerful Dao Warrior Bean!"

"If you'll recall, I stored all of the beans into my Profound Heavenly Gourd, hoping to use the gourd's special properties to enhance the beans. However, to my surprise, the lightning law powers within the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords inside the gourd began to resonate with the beans, and part of their lightning law powers was transferred into the beans.

“The beans have been in the gourd for over ten years, and their powers have been significantly enhanced over this period of time," Han Li explained.

"In that case, it does indeed look like a Lightning Dust Bead won't be necessary," Daoist Xie said with a smile.

"I'm afraid it's not all good news. Due to the outflow of lightning law powers from my Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, I can sense that they're being nurtured at a far slower rate than before inside the Profound Heavenly Gourd," Han Li sighed.

"Don't be greedy, Fellow Daoist Han. Your Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords have absorbed both Divine Devilbane Lightning and Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, both of which are some of the most potent yang-attribute lightnings in the world. Your Dao Warriors will be significantly enhanced even if they only absorb a tiny amount of those lightnings, and they'll be particularly effective against ghostly enemies," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li contemplated this notion momentarily, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

"Seeing as everything is ready, I can begin refining the Dao Warriors," Daoist Xie said.

"Do you need me to do anything?" Han Li asked.

"Not at the moment. The initial refinement process will take at least three years, and I can complete it on my own. However, someone with tremendous spiritual sense will be required to engrave the runes onto the Dao Warriors, so that task will have to be undertaken by you," Daoist Xie replied.

"In that case, I'll be counting on you, Brother Xie," Han Li said.

After that, he transferred all of his Dao Warriors Beans from the Profound Heavenly Gourd into the gourd that had been used to store his previous batch of Dao Warrior Beans.

Daoist Xie accepted the gourd from Han Li, and he gave a pleased nod as he shook the gourd gently to feel the beans inside.

Right as he was about to turn and make his way up to the second floor of the bamboo building, he suddenly recalled something, and he turned to Han Li as he said, "By the way, that tree root in the spirit medicine garden seems to have sprouted."

"Tree root?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a look of realization appeared on his face, and he hurriedly rushed into the spirit medicine garden.

Upon reaching a certain area deep in the garden, Han Li spotted a thin sapling that was no thicker than a finger. It was extending out of a withered tree root on the ground, and there were two leaves growing on its tip.

The leaves were filled with countless extremely thin veins that resembled human blood vessels, and they appeared very delicate, but also quite resilient and determined to make the most of the new life that they had been given.

Han Li crouched down next to the frail sapling, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he mused, "It's taken a lot of spirit liquid from my Heaven Controlling Vial, but you've finally sprouted, little guy."

The sapling was growing from the roots of the Twin Birth Tree that he had taken from the True Mantra Sect ruins, and Han Li reached out to stroke the leaves of the sapling, but he had only just extended a hand when the leaves suddenly began to sway toward his finger.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately released his spiritual sense to discover that the leaves had detected the time law powers within his body, and that was why they were approaching him.

Han Li gently stroked the leaves a few times without any incident, and he pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial, then opened it before tipping the latest drop of spirit liquid inside directly onto the two leaves.

Chapter 814: Rural Small Town

The spirit liquid formed a bead that was as translucent as jade before slowly flowing down the stem of the sapling, then ultimately seeped into the roots.

Han Li stood up straight again as he stowed the Heaven Controlling Vial away, and the leaves that were curling toward him returned to their normal positions.

The sapling didn't display any changes at all, and it was as if nothing had happened.

Han Li wasn't fazed by this, and he stared absentmindedly at the sapling with a contemplative look in his eyes, seemingly pondering something.

Time slowly passed by, and Han Li remained standing on the spot, lost in his thoughts.

Some time later, his expression suddenly changed slightly as a series of strange patterns lit up on the leaves of the sapling, and those patterns spread over the entire surface of the leaves in the blink of an eye.

In contrast with the veins of the leaves, these patterns appeared rather familiar to Han Li.

After staring at them for a while, Han Li suddenly clapped his hands together and exclaimed, "Why are they so similar to time dao patterns?"

The patterns only lingered for a few seconds before fading away, but Han Li's brows had become tightly furrowed in deep thought.

This Twin Birth Tree had been planted by Mu Yan, the eldest disciple of Patriarch Miro, so could it be that he had somehow managed to instill time law powers within it during the nurturing process, or was it the case that the Twin Birth Tree harbored time law powers to begin with?

Also, was it really true that the tree could assist one in overcoming their baleful decay, or was that merely an old wives' tale?

In the end, Han Li wasn't able to arrive at any concrete conclusions, so he could only shake his head to rid himself of the train of thought.

In any case, it was definitely a good thing that the roots of the Twin Birth Tree had sprouted again.

After that, he stayed in the garden for close to another half-day, only leaving after examining the state of many of the other spirit medicines planted in the garden.

He then returned straight to the bamboo building beside the pond, where Weeping Soul was still laying in an unconscious state, and he sat down with his legs crossed on the first floor.

After taking some time to meditate, he flipped a hand over to produce a piece of high-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, which he held in his hand.

He slowly injected his immortal spiritual power into the piece of jade, and a burst of purple light immediately appeared within it, basking the entire room in a warm, purple glow.

A surge of warmth also spread through Han Li's entire body, and a sense of extreme comfort arose from deep within his consciousness. It was such a blissful sensation that he found himself somewhat lost within it.

Only after a long while did he open his eyes before withdrawing his immortal spiritual power, and the light in the Purple Sun Warm Jade faded.

It's no wonder those people in Black Weasel City were willing to take such a huge risk to acquire this material. If I use it to assist me in my cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, I'll be sure to make rapid progress!

With that in mind, he gently tossed the piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade up into the air, where it hovered above his head.

He then made a hand seal and channeled the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

A burst of translucent light slowly extended out of his glabella, then twisted around a few times like a spirit snake before abruptly pouncing headfirst into the piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade.

The piece of jade trembled slightly as it lit up with purple light once again, but not as brightly as before. Instead, the light that it released only encompassed an area with a radius of around a dozen inches, only just barely enough to encompass the space above Han Li's head.

There seemed to be some murky purple smoke within the purple light, giving it the appearance of a glowing purple cloud.

As soon as the purple cloud appeared above Han Li's head, a blissful expression instantly surfaced on his face, and bursts of spiritual sense fluctuations began to spread in all directions from his head.

Five years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Inside a winding mountain range in the Yellow Grain Region was a rural small town that was completely isolated from the rest of the world.

It was nearing dusk, and plumes of smoke were beginning to rise up from the chimneys of the houses in the town. A farmer was returning to the town with a horned ox in tow, and he was passing through the wooden archway that marked the entrance of the town.

On a street at the center of the town, there were many devilish children with two heads and four arms chasing each other in a game of tag, while some well-built devilish women were standing nearby, chatting with one another while taking occasional glances at their children.

If any child fell over, their mother would immediately rush over and chastise them while helping them to their feet.

Among the group of children was a clever-looking little boy, and he was just about to sneakily jump onto one of his playmates when he suddenly spotted a pair of figures entering the town with the light of the dying sun behind them.

The town wasn't very large, so the boy was immediately able to see that this was a pair of strangers. However, instead of feeling fearful, he began to examine the duo with a hint of intrigue in his eyes.

Both of them only had one head and two arms each, so they didn't resemble the people of the town at all. On top of that, they were dressed in beautiful clothes with embroidered patterns that the boy had never seen before.

One of the two figures was an ordinary-looking young man, and upon noticing the boy's inquisitive gaze, he flashed the boy a smile, while the white-haired man walking along beside him remained silent and expressionless.

These two were none other than Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

In response to Han Li's smile, the boy immediately looked away in an embarrassed fashion, but he couldn't help but look back again shortly thereafter.

Han Li's smile became even more pronounced upon seeing this, and it occurred to him that these devilish children weren't so different from human children.

"I had thought that all devilish beings possessed innate aptitude for cultivation, so I wasn't expecting to see a mortal settlement in the Devil Realm. This place is almost like a completely isolated mortal paradise," Han Li remarked.

"All of the beings of our Holy Realm possess strong physical constitutions, so even for mortal beings, the average lifespan is around three hundred to four hundred years. However, only a small portion of them actually possess cultivation aptitude. Of course, bodily refinement is a path available to everyone, but not everyone wants to pursue such an arduous endeavor," Shi Chuankong explained.

"Indeed. By the way, what are these beings residing in this town? Their bloodline auras are quite strong, so it doesn't feel like they're ordinary devilish beings," Han Li said.

"Among the lower grade beings of our Holy Realm, the matter of bloodline isn't actually one that's held in very high regard. Hence, with all of the beings of different tribes reproducing with one another, it can be quite difficult to identify the ethnicities for certain devilish beings.

“These people seem to possess a relatively pure bloodline, but I've never seen such beings anywhere else in the Holy Realm, so I'm afraid I can't identify them," Shi Chuankong replied.

As they were speaking, they had already passed through the group of playing children, and they made their way to a small tea stall at the center of the town before taking a seat, while the women and the farmer looked on with curious expressions.

The owner of the stall was a hunch-backed elderly man with a head of disheveled hair, and he brought out some tea for Han Li and Shi Chuankong before returning to his room, not uttering even a single word in the process.

"I've reached the final stage of the refinement of my Dao Warriors, so we'll have to stay here for some time," Han Li said after taking a sip of tea.

"It's fine. We still have a long journey ahead of us anyway, so some minor delays here and there won't really matter much. This mountain range isn't particularly abundant in the world's origin qi, but the devilish qi here is also far sparser than elsewhere, so it's a suitable location for you to refine your Dao Warriors," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li was just about to respond when he suddenly felt the earth tremble beneath his feet, and he hurriedly rose to his feet while picking up the teapot and teacup on the table, while Shi Chuankongs teacup fell onto the ground, spilling tea everywhere.

Before the two of them had a chance to figure out what was happening, the children on the street began to yell excitedly, "The mountain god is snoring again!"

Meanwhile, the women were all standing still on the spot with composed expressions, seemingly already accustomed to this phenomenon, and the tremors lasted close to twenty seconds before finally subsiding.

Han Li returned to his seat, then set the teapot and teacup back down onto the table.

Tea had spilled onto Shi Chuankong's bench, so he stood up and sat down to Han Li's left.

"Was that an earthquake just now?" Han Li asked.

"I didn't detect any abnormal energy fluctuations, so it most likely was an earthquake," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

All of a sudden, the ground began to tremble once again, and this time, Han Li pressed his hands down onto the corners of the table to stabilize it.

The tremors came and went around a dozen times before finally subsiding for good, and at this point, it was already nighttime.

The hunch-backed elderly man made his way out of his room while carrying a dim yellow lantern, then hung it up outside before bending down to pick up the smashed teacup.

By the time he stood up straight again, Han Li and Shi Chuankong had already disappeared, and all that remained was a small devil stone sitting on the table.

The elderly man looked around for a moment, but failed to spot Han Li's duo, and he casually picked up the devil's stone from the table before tucking it into his pocket.

On the mountain path outside the small town, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were walking briskly with tense expressions.

"Are you sure, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked through voice transmission.

Chapter 815: Mountain-bearing Ape

"I'm certain. That man is not a devilish being. Instead, his true form is that of a fearsome beast in the Immortal Realm known as the Mountain-bearing Ape. These creatures like to carry mountains on their backs, and the more powerful they become, the larger the mountain that they carry. For them, that's their cultivation, and some can even carry entire mountain ranges," Han Li replied.

"No wonder he didn't come out even once during the earthquakes, but then immediately came out after the tremors subsided," Shi Chuankong mused.

"There's a story in the Azure Leaf Immortal Region about how an elder of an immortal sect once slew a juvenile Mountain-bearing Ape in order to refine an immortal treasure, and during the few attempts that the mature Mountain-bearing Ape came for revenge, it was wounded and forced into retreat by the sect.

“After its final retreat, everyone thought that the saga was over, but ten thousand years after that, the foundation of the entire mountain range that the sect was situated in was destroyed by the Mountain-bearing Ape, and it then carried the sect straight into the sea," Han Li said.

"That sounds almost too fantastical to be true, even in the cultivation world," Shi Chuankong mused as he took a glance back in the direction of the small town.

"It looked like the people of the town had already been living there for generations and grown accustomed to the frequent earthquakes. That Mountain-bearing Ape has already reached the Great Encompassment Stage, and it seems that its wild and vicious nature has already been smoothed over by the passage of time," Han Li said.

"I'm assuming he doesn't wish to be recognized, considering he's living in such a secluded place. In any case, I hope he doesn't come after us," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

However, as soon as his voice trailed off, a figure suddenly appeared on the mountain path up ahead, and it was none other than the hunch-backed elderly man from before.

"You really have a knack for speaking misfortune into existence, don't you, Brother Shi?" Han Li sighed with a wry smile.

Shi Chuankong was flabbergasted to see this, and he was struck by the urge to slap himself.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li took a step forward, then cupped his fist toward the hunch-backed elderly man in a salute as he asked, "Can we help you, Senior?"

Shi Chuankong remained silent, but he also cupped his fist in a salute.

"Rest assured, I mean you no harm," the hunch-backed elderly man replied with his hands clasped behind his back, and his voice was very coarse and raspy.

"Do you have any instructions for us, Senior?" Han Li asked in a careful manner.

"No, it's just that I haven't seen anyone from the Immortal Realm for a very long time, and I wanted to ask you some questions," the elderly man replied.

"Please go ahead, Senior. I'll tell you everything I know, but I can't guarantee that I'll be able to answer all of your questions," Han Li said.

"Where are you from?" the elderly man asked.

"I am from the Black Mountain Immortal Region," Han Li replied.

A reminiscent look flashed through the elderly man's eyes upon hearing this, and he said, "I stayed in the Black Mountain Immortal Region for some time in the past. It was a very rough time in my life, but I do miss the place, nonetheless. By the way, have you ever been to a place called the Floating Cloud Mountain Range?"

"Indeed, I have. In fact, I stayed there for a while. Have you been there too, Senior?" Han Li asked.

"I stayed there for some time too, but I can't recall how long ago that was. All I remember is that in the beginning, the mountain range had very few residents, but more and more people began to move in, and it was no longer as peaceful as it once was, so I left," the elderly man replied.

"I'm afraid the Floating Cloud Mountain Range is no longer the same place that it once was. It has a very large number of residents, and it's almost an independent, autonomous region. However, back when I left, the Heavenly Court seemed to have strengthened its control over the area, and many people were driven out. As for how the mountain range is faring now, I'm afraid I don't know the answer to that," Han Li sighed.

"It's fine, it's all in the distant past anyway. I presume you've managed to see through my true form, right?" the elderly man asked.

Han Li immediately tensed up a little upon hearing this, and after carefully selecting his words, he replied, "I wouldn't dare to speculate on what your true form is, but I can tell that your cultivation base is extremely advanced."

The hunch-backed elderly man nodded as he said, "I overheard you talking about needing to find a place to refine Dao Warriors, is that right? There are many uninhabited valleys in this mountain range that you can use for that purpose if you'd like."

"Thank you for the kind offer, Senior, but we won't trouble you with these trivial matters. I'll find some other place to refine my Dao Warriors, and I assure you that we won't disturb you," Han Li hurriedly replied.

"In that case, I'll treat this encounter as if it never happened," the elderly man said in a meaningful voice.

"Rest assured, Senior, as far as we're concerned, we never met you here," Han Li immediately replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"That's right. In fact, we've never even been here," Shi Chuankong hurriedly chimed in.

The hunch-backed elderly man took a long glance at Shi Chuankong, then remarked, "You certainly chose some good parents. Alright, you can go now."

Han Li and Shi Chuankong immediately extended a parting salute toward the elderly man upon hearing this, then flew away as two streaks of light.

Only after they had flown out of the mountain range did they allow themselves a faint sigh of relief, and they looked back in the direction of the small town to find that the entire mountain range had begun trembling violently.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he cast his gaze toward the foundation of the mountain range, and he was just barely able to make out a giant hunch-backed figure, carrying the entire mountain range on its back.

The hunch-backed figure was crawling on all fours, and it blended in with the mountain range so well that Han Li wouldn't have been able to tell them apart at all had it not been for his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Right at this moment, a giant mountain at the forefront of the mountain range suddenly began to slowly turn toward him, and the vegetation and rocks on the mountain were torn apart as a pair of gargantuan eyes appeared.

There was a cold gleam in the eyes' golden pupils, and Han Li immediately withdrew his Infernal Devilish Eyes upon seeing this before flying away with Shi Chuankong.

The two of them flew for three days without rest before finally stopping on a nearby mountain.

They hadn't stopped here because they felt like they were already a safe distance away. Instead, it was because the refinement of the Dao Warriors had reached its most crucial juncture, and Han Li had to inscribe runes on them without delay.

After descending onto the mountain, Han Li didn't even have the time to make a temporary cave abode, and he could only request Shi Chuankong to stand on lookout duty for him while he hurriedly entered the Flower Branch domain.

Thunderclaps were ringing out incessantly from the second floor of the bamboo building beside the pond, and the entire room was filled with purplish-golden lightning. As soon as Han Li entered the room, he felt as if he had stepped into the Bone Rinsing Lightning Pond again.

However, the feeling only lasted for a fleeting moment as the purplish-golden lightning in the room only possessed a similar aura to the Bone Rinsing Lightning Pond, but didn't possess anywhere near the same level of power.

Even so, such a fearsome lightning aura would be sufficient to quell countless ghosts and spirits.

"Thank heavens you're here, Fellow Daoist Han. I wasn't going to be able to contain this lightning pond for much longer," Daoist Xie said in a relieved voice.

"Apologies for the delay, you can leave the rest to me now," Han Li said, then quickly made his way into the array.

Daoist Xie immediately stepped out of the array so that Han Li could take his place, then stood by the entrance of the room in silent observation.

Han Li was already well aware of what runes had to be inscribed, so he required no instructions from Daoist Xie.

He began to chant an incantation, and the patterns of the array on the ground began to grow clearer and clearer before gradually peeling off from the ground to hover in mid-air.

At the same time, all of the golden beans also rose up into the air, and they were connected together by Han Li's spiritual sense threads, forming a giant tree of golden radiance.

Meanwhile, the lightning array rose all the way up to the ceiling of the room, where it encompassed the entire tree of golden light.

Han Li immediately switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this, and blue light surged out of his eyes, while the spiritual sense threads flowing out of his glabella glowed brighter and brighter.

He was rapidly cycling through a string of hand seals in an extremely well-rehearsed fashion, and indeed, he had practiced this sequence hundreds of times to ensure that he could execute it smoothly in this exact scenario.

However, this was an extremely slow process, but Han Li had more than enough patience to spare.

Three months flew by in the blink of an eye, and the process was complete, giving rise to thousands of new Dao Warriors.

Han Li handed over the Dao Warriors to Daoist Xie, then immediately left the Flower Branch domain to resume his journey with Shi Chuankong.

Chapter 816: Fifth-grade Immortal Lantern

After the Yellow Grain Region came the Ten Dreams Region.

Not only did the two regions directly neighbor each other, the eighteen major rivers in the Ten Dreams Region all had their origins in the Yellow Grain Region, so the two regions had alway shared a close relationship.

The Devil Realm naturally wasn't as large as the Immortal Realm, but even so, there could be a great deal of variance between two neighboring regions.

Aside from the eighteen main rivers in the Ten Dreams Region, there were also hundreds of branch waterways that formed a vast and complex system.

On this day, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were traveling on an ordinary boat along the Flowing Sand River to a city in the north.

In a rare turn of events, Han Li had disguised himself as a handsome scholar, and both he and Shi Chuankong were wearing identical azure robes. On top of that, he was holding a folding fan in one hand to further lend him a scholarly air.

The soil on either side of the river was very fertile, and the banks were lined with peach blossom trees. It was right at the height of the flowering season, and there was a faint, intoxicating, floral aroma wafting through the air.

However, Han Li only looked at the masses of blooming peach blossoms for a short while before returning to the cabin of the boat in a disappointed fashion.

"I thought this Dream Peach Forest was going to be a special sight to behold, but it really hasn't lived up to its reputation. Perhaps it would be quite a breathtaking sight for a mortal, but it really isn't anything special for cultivators like us," Han Li sighed as he flipped a hand over to summon a flagon of fine wine, then filled a cup for himself.

Shi Chuankong wasn't going to say anything, but upon spotting the flagon of wine, he immediately approached Han Li and sat down across from him, then brought out a cup of his own before filling it himself.

He took a sip of wine, then explained, "There are ten illusory dream areas in the Ten Dreams Region, and this Dream Peach Forest is one of them. The only reason why you see nothing special about it is because your spiritual sense is too powerful. In the eyes of the average person, there are celestial maidens dancing between the trees and rainbow deer frolicking through the forest."

"It seems like my spiritual sense isn't doing me a favor here then," Han Li remarked.

"If you withdraw your spiritual sense and don't try to resist the illusion, you'll be able to witness those sights as well. As we continue down the river, we'll also be passing through the Heavenly Dream Staircase and the Illusory Flaming Sea. Let's see if you'll be impervious to those illusions as well," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

Han Li offered no response to this. Thanks to the Purple Sun Warm Jade, he had been able to make rapid progress in his Spirit Refinement Technique. As a result, his spiritual sense had been significantly enhanced over a short period of time, but he was still some way away from reaching full mastery of the fifth level.

He downed the contents of his cup in one go, then swept a sleeve over the table in front of him, and a strange-looking glass lamp appeared amid a flash of azure light.

"Have you refined this lamp yet, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"This Soul Devouring Lamp was left behind by those sisters from last time, and I was worried that there would be some type of hidden restriction within it, so I haven't attempted to refine it yet," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"This the same Soul Devouring Lamp from last time?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed.

"Didn't you see them use it last time? Why are you so surprised?" Han Li asked.

Shi Chuankong hesitated momentarily, then rubbed his hands together as he said, "Brother Li, if you don't want to refine this lamp, then I'm willing to purchase it from you. Just state a price."

"Aren't you supposed to be a shrewd businessman, Brother Shi? I'm certainly not going to sell the lamp now that you've displayed so much interest in it! Why don't you tell me what's so special about this thing?" Han Li chuckled.

"Truth be told, this lamp is a fifth-grade immortal treasure that's powered solely by spiritual sense, so it can be used by cultivators from both the Immortal Realm and the Devil Realm. As for how much one can tap into its power, that depends on the potency of their spiritual sense. I was only joking when I offered to buy it. Only someone like you can truly make full use of this lamp," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"I've examined it earlier and didn't find any restrictions, but I was worried that there were perhaps some special hidden restrictions in the Devil Realm that I didn't know about, so I didn't refine it. Would you be able to examine it for me as well? If it's safe to do so, then I'll refine it, and it'll surely serve as another powerful weapon for us to use in future battles," Han Li proposed.

"That's precisely what I intended," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod, then took the Soul Devouring Lamp from Han Li before conducting a close examination.

Some time later, he returned the lamp to Han Li as he said, "There are indeed some secret hidden restrictions in our Holy Realm, but I didn't see any of them in this lamp."

"In that case, I can begin refining it right away," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Before that, do you know what these four beasts on the lamp are, Brother Shi?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Please enlighten me, Brother Shi," Han Li prompted in an intrigued manner.

"These four beasts appear to be quite similar, but in reality, there are minute differences between them. This one here with the single horn on its head is called Covet, and it likes to captivate souls. The one with the sunken eyes is called Clinch, and it likes to collect incomplete souls. This one with the closed ears is called Unaware, and it likes to imprison souls.

“The final one with the sharp fangs is called Glutton, and it likes to devour souls. The four of them represent the lamp's four abilities," Shi Chuankong explained.

"If you're so familiar with this lamp, then why weren't you able to identify it before?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

"Back when this lamp first appeared in our Holy Realm, it was supposed to come to our Vast Origin House. At the time, the report had already been filed, and all I had to do was sign off on it. However, I was busy with other matters at the time, so I wasn't able to address the matter in a timely fashion, resulting in the lamp being lost, and it must've somehow ended up in the hands of my eldest brother," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

"I see," Han Li mused with a smile.

"I wanted to tell you about these four beasts so that you know that they're very dangerous creatures. According to the report that I received, this lamp can't be refined through conventional means. Otherwise, there's a very good chance that you'll suffer backlash from the spirits of the four beasts, resulting in spiritual damage," Shi Chuankong cautioned.

A confident smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce the book titled Soul Devouring Refinement Technique.

"This book lays out how the lamp is to be used, and its refinement method also just so happens to be included as well," Han Li said.

"No wonder you wanted to claim the book. I should've known that you were thinking ahead," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

"We have nothing better to do anyway, so why don't I refine this Soul Devouring Lamp now? Perhaps it'll be useful to us later on," Han Li said.

"That's a good idea. We're still not out of the woods right now, so it certainly couldn't hurt to have some more tricks up our sleeves. You can focus on refining the lamp, I'll make sure to keep a lookout for you," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

With that, Han Li began setting up an array on the boat in accordance with the method laid out in the book.

After setting up an array that was around ten feet in size, Han Li made a hand seal to activate it, and the array immediately began to glow with golden radiance, encompassing the entire Soul Devouring Lamp.

Basked within the golden radiance, the glass lamp instantly became translucent, and some thin azure and purple lines had appeared within it.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. These lines were none other than the spiritual sense threads left behind by the twin sisters.

All of a sudden, a burst of scorching heat erupted out of the golden light beneath the array to roast the glass lamp, and all of the purple and azure threads inside instantly began to squirm violently like live eels thrown into boiling water.

Han Li then pointed a finger at the lamp, and the golden light in the array immediately surged into the lamp to ignite all of the purple and azure threads, rapidly melting them away.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. Now that the twins' residual spiritual sense threads had been eradicated, it was time for him to inject his own spiritual sense threads into the lamp.

With that in mind, he switched a different hand seal before slowly closing his eyes, and dozens of translucent threads shot out of his glabella before piercing into the glass lamp, where they slowly fused into the lamp.

Several months flew by in a flash.

At this point, the boat had already left the Dream Peach Forest and arrived at the Heavenly Dream Staircase.

Shi Chuankong was standing at the front of the boat, scouring the banks of the river with his gaze. At this moment, the river was lined with sheer cliff faces on either side, presenting a majestic sight to behold.

After rounding a corner, the boat suddenly arrived in a very open and spacious body of water.

It was still early in the morning, and there was still some faint mist lingering in the air. The sun was rising over the surface of the river, basking it in a warm glow.

As the sun rose up higher and higher, its radiance also grew brighter and brighter, and before long, the mist over the surface of the river had completely evaporated.

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly as he turned to the mountain face to his left. The light of the sun was shining down upon that mountain face, and a shimmering, golden stone staircase had appeared on the mountain face without any warning, leading all the way to the mountain summit.

From there, the staircase ascended even further, stretching up into the clouds in the sky before finally vanishing out of sight.

Shi Chuankong was just thinking about how it was going to be a pity that Han Li was going to miss this piece of spectacular scenery when he hurriedly swung around, and right at this moment, Han Li suddenly gave a muffled groan as his entire body began to tremble uncontrollably.

Chapter 817: Long Journey

Shi Chuankong immediately noticed that there was something different about the glass lamp at the center of the array.

As it turned out, the eyes of the four beasts on the lamp had all lit up and were glowing red.

As soon as Shi Chuankong's gaze fell upon the red light, he was immediately rooted to the spot, as if he had been struck by lightning.

At the same time, his blood began to boil in his veins, and an intense wave of heat swept through his entire body, striking him with a sense of asphyxiation.

He hurriedly channeled his cultivation arts to protect himself, and as he settled his gaze on the four beasts once again, it felt as if they had all sprung to life and were leering maliciously at him.

An indescribable sense of fury and resentment began to well up in his heart.

All of a sudden, he felt as if this entire world had been extremely unfair to him. He never had any interest in competing against his siblings. Instead, all he wanted was to be able to travel the world as a wealthy merchant and collect all of the fine treasures that the realms had to offer. In his eyes, that was the most fulfilling life possible.

However, his siblings all seemed to harbor enmity toward him, and he couldn't understand why.

The more these vindictive thoughts took root in his mind, the more violent and twisted his expression became.

Right at this moment, a loud roar suddenly rang out.

It was Han Li's voice, and in the wake of the roar, Shi Chuankong's mental clarity was instantly restored.

His expression instantly darkened slightly, while a sense of lingering fear welled up in his heart.

As he turned his gaze back to the glass lamp, he discovered that it was still glowing red, but the red light was being suppressed by a burst of formidable spiritual sense.

The spiritual sense had naturally come from none other than Han Li, and despite his composed appearance, his consciousness was reeling internally.

It was unclear whether the refinement method left behind by the sisters was fake, or whether he had injected too many spiritual sense threads into the lamp earlier. In any case, Han Li had been struck by backlash from the lamp, and the four beasts had manifested themselves in his mind to devour his spiritual sense, attempting to suck his soul into the lamp.

At this moment, four giant beast projections were closing toward the center of his consciousness from four different directions, and in response, Han Li immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique.

Bursts of formidable spiritual sense fluctuations were surging out of the center of his consciousness, forming a series of giant waves that swept toward the four beasts, resisting them in their advance.

However, this wasn't a permanent solution, and it could only delay the crisis.

Right at this moment, Han Li let loose a loud roar, and a burst of white light swept through his entire consciousness like a snowstorm, instantly freezing everything inside, including the four beasts.

However, before he had a chance to do anything else, a string of loud cracks rang out, and the four beasts freed themselves from the frozen snowscape before continuing in their advance.

Having already devoured a huge amount of spiritual sense from Han Li's consciousness, the four beasts had become too powerful to contain.

A sense of immense pressure was weighing down upon Han Li's entire consciousness, and to his dismay, the pressure was only continuing to mount further and further.

He knew that once the four beasts linked up with each other, his consciousness would be completely compressed, leading to the destruction of his soul, ultimately reducing him to nothing more than an empty husk.

Right as he was scrambling for a solution, a burst of purple light suddenly appeared above his consciousness, releasing bursts of warm and comforting energy that quickly replenished his spiritual sense.

Han Li was instantly reinvigorated, and he redoubled his efforts, resisting against the advance of the four beasts with all his might.

The four beasts were slowed down drastically, but they were still advancing forward little by little.

Han Li could feel more and more pressure building in his consciousness, and his spiritual sense was being stripped away bit by bit, while the purple light above his consciousness had also been compressed into a ball by the tremendous pressure.

A suffocating sense of fear began to well up in his heart, but right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out within his consciousness, following which the compressed ball of purple light suddenly erupted outward in all directions.

Finally, the final bottleneck standing in Han Li's path had been shattered, and he was able to push beyond his limits, achieving full mastery of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique!

Han Li was ecstatic, and bursts of formidable spiritual sense swept through his consciousness before converging to form an enormous spiritual sense sword.

The spiritual sense sword was semi-transparent, with intricate patterns etched upon its surface, and tremendous spiritual sense fluctuations were surging out of it in all directions.

As the spiritual sense sword slowly descended, the spiritual sense fluctuations only became more and more fearsome, and the four beasts were slowly forced back bit by bit, all the way until they were forced out of Han Li's consciousness altogether.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong was standing on the small boat, looking at Han Li with a tense expression. He was holding a piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade in his hand, and he was internally debating whether he should place this piece of jade on top of Han Li's head as well.

Right at this moment, a streak of semi-transparent light shot out of Han Li's glabella, giving Shi Chuankong a huge fright. He was just about to get out of the way when he discovered that the streak of light was a translucent little sword, and it was hovering in front of his glabella in a stable fashion.

Shi Chuankong remained completely still, not making any false moves, and he took a glance at the Soul Devouring Lamp out of the corner of his eye. To his relief, he discovered that the red light in the eyes of the four beasts had already faded.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li slowly opened his eyes, and it was clear that the storm had been weathered.

The spiritual sense sword flew back into his glabella, vanishing out of sight, and he took a glance up at the piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade hovering above his head, then looked back at Shi Chuankong as he cupped his fist in a salute and said, "Thank you for your help, Brother Shi. I shudder to imagine what would've happened if you hadn't intervened."

"There's no need to thank me, Brother Li. The more powerful you become, the safer I'll be. By the way, what happened just now? Everything appeared to be going smoothly, but the lamp suddenly began wreaking havoc seemingly out of nowhere," Shi Chuankong said.

"I'm not sure what went wrong myself. It seems like I injected too much spiritual sense into the lamp, thereby triggering backlash from the four beasts. I was truly in dire straits, and it was only thanks to your help that I was able to break through my bottleneck and turn the tables," Han Li explained.

Shi Chuankong had no idea what Han Li was talking about, but he had a rough idea of just how perilous the situation had been.

"What was that little sword just now?" he asked.

"That was a Spiritual Sense Sword, a spiritual sense ability that I attained after reaching full mastery of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. I don't know exactly how powerful it is right now, but it's definitely quite a formidable ability," Han Li explained.

This was a subject that concerned Han Li's cultivation, so it was inappropriate for Shi Chuankong to pry any further.

At this point, the Heavenly Dream Staircase had already been left behind, and the boat had emerged from the open body of water, leaving only a trail of ripples in its wake.

Eighty years flew by in the blink of an eye.

In a region of the sea that was as black as ink, a gargantuan black whale with a huge island on its back was swimming through the waves.

The entire island was no more than a thousand feet tall with a very level terrain, and it was thriving with lush greenery, interspersed throughout which were a series of pagodas and pavilions.

Two people were seated across from each other in a small mountain pavilion at the center of the island, having some wine in the warm breeze.

Seated on the left was Han Li, and he was holding a cup with a smile on his face as he remarked, "Surely it was overkill to rent an entire whale island just for the two of us."

"I rented this island for you, Brother Li! The arrays on the island can keep out devilish qi while drawing in the world's origin qi, and I thought that would allow you to travel in greater comfort," Shi Chuankong countered.

"I appreciate that, it's just that I'm worried that we're being too ostentatious here and could end up attracting attention to ourselves. Also, now that you mention it, the closer we get to the center of this region, the denser the devilish qi in the environment has become. I can keep it out thanks to my devilish cultivation arts, but it's still rather annoying," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"It's fine. They don't know our exact itinerary, so there's no way they can intercept us," Shi Chuankong assured with a smile.

"Your eldest brother and fifth sister are no slouches. It seems like they haven't done anything over the past few decades, but there's no telling what sinister plots they could be hatching behind the scenes," Han Li said.

"In any case, we're almost at Ink Sea City, and from there, it'll only be one more stop before we reach Night Sun City. While it's important to be on our guard, there's no need to be excessively cautious," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Right at this moment, a melodious call rang out from the gargantuan whale down below.

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze into the distance, but wasn't able to see anything, and a slightly apprehensive look appeared on his face.

Han Li also took a glance into the distance, then remarked, "We seem to have encountered a sea beast, but it's only at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, and it doesn't seem to be particularly vicious in nature."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a vast expanse of light suddenly appeared beneath the waves, following which a giant ball of water emerged from the depths, breaking through the surface of the sea.

The ball of water was a white jellyfish that was far more massive than the black whale, and it was glowing internally, giving it the appearance of a giant beacon that was sitting above the waves.

Chapter 818: Persistent Threat

"It's a Bright Heart Jellyfish! These things have always been found deep in the sea, what's this one doing on the surface?" Shi Chuankong mused with a surprised expression.

Han Li's expression instantly changed drastically upon hearing this, and he yelled, "Run!"

Immediately thereafter, he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability and sprang forward, then grabbed onto Shi Chuankong before flying up into the air.

The two of them had only just risen up into the sky when the jellyfish crashed into the whale, and a resounding boom rang out as the jellyfish exploded.

At the same time, the gargantuan whale's body also exploded with a resounding boom, and all of the bones in its body shot out before hurtling directly toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

In response, the two of them swiveled around before each throwing a punch downard, and two giant fist projections, one azure and one silver, came crashing down upon the wave of oncoming bones.

The two fist projections exploded in unison, and all of the whale's bones were also reduced to white powder.

Immediately thereafter, a white figure shot out of the cloud of bone powder, and they swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a white light barrier that encompassed both Han Li and Shi Chuankong within it.

The area contained within the white light barrier was filled with ghostly qi, and a series of tall pagodas rose up in the distance.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this.

At the same time, a cold voice rang out, and it resonated throughout the entire area encompassed within the white light barrier.

"You two sure made it difficult for me to track you down, but this is where your luck runs out!"

"It's Daoist Master Bone Shine! What a pain in the backside," Shi Chuankong groaned with tight furrowed brows.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes before looking around, and his skin immediately began to crawl at the sight that he was greeted by.

There was a pagoda that was thousands of feet tall and constructed entirely from bones standing in each of the eight directions, and there were ghostly green flames flickering in the eye sockets of all of the skulls on the pagodas.

On the very top of each pagoda was a skull that was different from all of the other ones, and they appeared to have belonged to powerful cultivators slain by Daoist Master Bone Shine.

There was clearly some type of hidden connection between them, and together, they formed a strange array that was giving off such formidable glacial qi that Han Li and Shi Chuankong could feel the immortal spiritual power circulation in their bodies becoming slower and more sluggish.

Han Li naturally didn't dare to hold back against a Great Encompassment cultivator, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air to summon his time spirit domain, which encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet.

Even though the ghostly white mist in the air was clearly moving far slower within his time spirit domain, the air temperature only continued to plummet, while the surrounding area was also becoming darker and darker.

"Let's see how you weasel your way out of this one!" Daoist Master Bone Shine roared, following which the sound of crashing waves suddenly rang out.

Han Li looked down to see that bursts of red light had appeared in the dense mist down below, and an infernal pit of fire that was over a thousand feet in radius had emerged on the surface of the sea.

Plumes of black smoke were rising up from the fiery pit, and there seemed to be lava churning inside, but it wasn't releasing any heat.

Inside the pit of fire, countless headless skeletons were struggling in futility, trying to climb their way out, only to sink deeper and deeper.

Right at this moment, a rune lit up on each of the eight different skulls on top of the surrounding bone pagodas, and all of the bones instantly began to tremble as if they had sprung to life.

The jawbones on the skulls were quite loose to begin with, and they immediately began to chatter audibly from the tremors.

At the same time, the fiery pit down below also began to tremble violently, and the bubbling lava was rapidly rising upward, threatening to gush out of the pit altogether.

All of the headless skeletons inside also rose up with the lava, and they began to ascend into the air.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he looked on with a grim expression. At this point, there was no time for him to think about how Daoist Master Bone Shine had managed to track them down. Instead, his top priority was to think of a way to escape.

"We're truly in trouble now, Brother Li. Daoist Master Bone Shine possesses a Creation Tier spirit domain, and that's far too much for us to deal with. Let's find an opportunity to split up and try to get away from there," Shi Chuankong said.

"He's clearly come into this with a plan, so I'm afraid that won't be so simple," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

He had seen Creation Tier spirit domains in the past, but none had struck him with a sense of pressure as intense as Daoist Master Bone Shine's.

All of a sudden, Han Li declared, "Here they come!"

Right as his voice trailed off, the fiery pit down below finally completely erupted, and the crimson lava inside exploded upward, carrying with it countless headless skeletons.

All of the skeletons seemed to have sprung to life, and their joints were cracking and popping audibly as they rushed at Han Li and Shi Chuankong with weapons forged from bones held in their hands.

"Are those domain spirits?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed as he hurriedly flipped a hand over to summon a black saber, while Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, and Daoist Xie emerged from the Flower Branch domain.

"Oh? Is that a domain treasure? Looks like I'll be able to claim some decent spoils from you two," Daoist Master Bone Shine remarked, but it was unclear where his voice was coming from.

"Judging from their aura, these things seem to be Dao Warriors, as opposed to domain spirits," Han Li said to Shi Chuankong, then turned to Daoist Xie before giving him a nod.

Daoist Xie immediately flipped a hand over to summon an azure gourd, which he tipped upside down before slamming hand onto its underside.

A burst of azure light flashed over the mouth of the gourd, and thousands of golden beans flew out from within before raining down from above.

Arcs of purplish-golden lightning flashed incessantly as all of the golden beans transformed into armored Dao Warriors, each of which was around ten feet tall.

Their facial features were completely identical, and all of them were rather wooden and stiff in appearance, but their eyes contained a faint, intelligent gleam.

All of them were clad in suits of antiquated golden armor that were riddled with purple patterns, and these suits of armor covered all of their vital regions.

Without requiring any instructions, the Dao Warriors raised their hands up to the sky in unison, and bursts of purplish-golden lightning erupted out of their hands, then took on the form of all types of lightning weapons, all of which were giving off formidable auras.

As soon as all of the Dao Warriors emerged, they were met by the horde of headless skeletons, and the two armies clashed violently.

Thousands of arcs of purplish-golden lightning erupted out of the hands of the Dao Warriors before exploding in unison, illuminating the night sky with spectacular purplish-golden radiance.

All of the headless skeletons that were struck by the arcs of lightning instantly fell apart before tumbling back down into the fiery pit below.

Deep within the dense mist, a white shadow stiffened momentarily in surprise, then drifted away again and vanished out of sight.

Han Li immediately turned his gaze in that direction, but by then, the white shadow was already gone.

"Even though he's at the Great Encompassment Stage, he's clearly making an effort not to approach us. It seems like he's already aware of all of our powers," Han Li said through voice transmission.

"We've been on the run for a very long time, and I'm sure the entire Holy Realm is aware of us at this point, so I suppose that's no surprise. I've been working hard in my cultivation, but I'm unable to make any significant strides without first reaching the High Zenith Stage. Having said that, if we can break our way out of this spirit domain, I can instantly get us out of here using a spatial secret technique," Shi Chuankong replied.

"According to my knowledge, Creation Tier spirit domains are different from normal spirit domains in that the law attributes of the former are significantly enhanced. It's most likely going to be quite difficult to break our way out, and the fact that Daoist Master Bone Shine is lurking in the shadows certainly won't help our cause," Han Li sighed.

Shi Chuankong hesitated momentarily, then said, "Brother Li, if you can somehow destroy one of those bone pagodas, I can try to forcibly unleash the secret technique at the cost of some blood essence to get us out of here."

"I think that may be our only way out," Han Li replied with a nod.

Right at this moment, a loud commotion rang out from down below, and Han Li looked down to discover that all of the shattered skeletons that had fallen back into the fiery pit had completely regenerated and were clashing against the Dao Warriors once again.

At the same time, a giant skeletal white hand suddenly extended out of the fiery pit, then grabbed onto its edge before pulling upward forcefully, and the body attached to the hand was vaulted out of the fiery pit.

It was a giant headless skeleton that was over a thousand feet tall, and it had four arms instead of two. On top of that, there were balls of crimson flames circling around its body, and it was wielding four bone longswords that were riddled with countless yin runes.

The giant skeleton sprang up into the air, launching itself up into the ranks of the Dao Warriors, and it was instantly surrounded by hundreds of Dao Warriors that lashed out at it with their weapons, striking it with bolts of purplish-golden lightning.

The crimson flames around the giant skeleton brightened significantly before transforming into a suit of glowing crimson armor, and it was able to keep all of the lightning at bay.

Chapter 819: Power of the Spiritual Sense Sword

"Leave that thing to me," Daoist Xie volunteered, then spread his arms open, and a pair of antiquated sabers appeared in his grasp.

Immediately thereafter, he vanished from the spot amid a rumbling thunderclap.

In the next instant, he abruptly reappeared directly in front of the giant four-armed skeleton, and two bursts of radiant lightning appeared on either side of him, resembling a pair of lightning wings as he swooped down upon the giant skeleton.

At the same time, all of the purplish-golden lightning in the air converged to form a series of giant balls of lightning, which then exploded violently to form a huge net of lightning that descended upon the giant skeleton.

Right at this moment, a formidable aura erupted out of the fiery pit down below, and another enormous skeleton slowly crawled its way out of the pit, this one even more massive than its predecessor.

Han Li knew that the longer this battle wore on, the more dire their situation was going to become, so he immediately sprang into action, sweeping a sleeve through the air to send eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords hurtling toward one of the bone pagodas.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords circled around in the air, releasing thousands of miniature azure sword projections that formed a vast azure wave.

Han Li was scouring the surrounding area for Daoist Master Bone Shine with his spiritual sense while simultaneously controlling the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but his spiritual sense was being severely suppressed in this spirit domain, rendering him unable to track down his target.

The torrent of azure sword projections quickly reached the bone pagoda, but right at this moment, the ghostly green flames in the eye sockets of the skulls on the pagoda swelled up drastically, while plumes of green mist surged out of their mouths to oppose the oncoming sword projections.

As soon as the sword projections pierced into the mist, they immediately began to rust and decay, and in the blink of an eye, close to a thousand sword projections had been corroded into nothingness.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he suddenly switched to a different hand seal, setting off a violent explosion of golden lightning that tore the entire cloud of green mist to shreds.

The green mist was no match for the lightning in the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which had integrated both Divine Devilbane Lightning and Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, and it was instantly eradicated to reveal the bone pagoda beyond it.

However, right at this moment, a burst of light flashed over the bone pagoda, and all of the skulls rose up into the air before scattering in all directions.

As a result, Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords struck nothing but empty air.

What was even more alarming was that all of the scattered bones were converging toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong from all directions, and they were still traveling extremely fast, even through Han Li's time spirit domain.

Shi Chuankong was just about to unleash a spatial ability to ward off the oncoming bones when Han Li urged through voice transmission, "Leave them to me, you focus on getting us out of here!"

Shi Chuankong immediately did as he was told, preparing his spatial secret technique, while Han Li summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis.

However, before the Mantra Treasured Axis had even fully emerged, Han Li's entire body abruptly stiffened, and his immortal spiritual power circulation also drew to a shuddering halt.

Immediately thereafter, he discovered that he seemed to have been deprived of control over his own skeleton, and his arms involuntarily raised up before extending outward, making it appear as if he had been nailed to an invisible cross.

Shi Chuankong's secret technique was also forcibly interrupted, and he was also rooted to the spot.

The only ones that remained unaffected were Daoist Xie and the Dao Warriors.

Upon noticing the predicament that Han Li was in, Daoist Xie raised Thunderslash and Heavenslash before bringing them together, and as soon as the two sabers came into contact with each other, a burst of lightning instantly erupted outward with tremendous force, intertwining to form a corkscrew-shaped pillar that hurtled directly toward Han Li.

However, the pillar of lightning was only able to travel about a thousand feet before a figure emerged from the mist in front of it, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of tremendous force that struck the pillar of lightning.

The pillar of lightning instantly exploded, sending countless tiny arcs of electricity erupting in all directions, and Daoist Xie came plummeting out of the sky.

The two giant headless skeletons immediately rushed at him, and a fierce battle ensued between the three.

The figure that had appeared up above was none other than Daoist Master Bone Shine, and he took a disdainful glance at Daoist Xie, then turned his gaze to Han Li.

Out of everyone here, only Han Li was deserving of any respect in his eyes.

"How does it feel to have your skeleton completely sealed away? Don't worry, I'll end your suffering soon and make you a part of my bone pagodas," Daoist Master Bone Shine chuckled coldly.

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and all of the skulls that were hovering in the air converged toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong, ready to sink their teeth into their flesh.

With each skull that flew past Han Li and Shi Chuankong, it would take a chunk of their flesh, and before long, both of their bodies were riddled with harrowing wounds.

The two of them were forced to endure the agony of having their flesh ripped from their bodies in chunks, yet all they could do was look on helplessly, completely powerless to resist.

Shi Chuankong possessed a devilish body, while Han Li was a Profound Immortal, so neither of them were lacking when it came to their physical constitutions, but with each shred of flesh that was torn away, the skulls absorb some of their power, and the ghostly flames in their eye sockets burned brighter and brighter.

A sadistic grin appeared on Daoist Master Bone Shine's face upon seeing this. He had originally intended to end the battle quickly and grant Han Li and Shi Chuankong a swift death, but now, he intended to slowly torment the two of them to death so that he could fully harness the power of their physical bodies.

Shi Chuankong was gritting his teeth with all his might, but he still couldn't help but snarl in pain.

The pain of having his flesh torn away was still bearable, but the problem was that each chunk of flesh that was taken out of his body, the skulls would release a plume of green mist that seeped straight into his bones, striking him with immense agony.

Han Li was also suffering from the same horrific torture, but his bones seemed to be more resistant to the green mist, and they were still glowing radiantly like jade.

As a Jade Immortal, his physical body was far more resistant to the corrosive effects of the green mist than Shi Chuankong's.

"I almost forgot that you were a Jade Immortal," Daoist Master Bone Shine chuckled coldly, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he reappeared in front of Han Li, then raised a hand before thrusting his joined middle and index fingers toward Han Li's glabella.

Han Li remained completely immobilized, but his expression remained calm and steely as he glowered at Daoist Master Bone Shine.

Right as Daoist Master Bone Shine's fingers were about to come into contact with his glabella, he abruptly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to focus all of his spiritual sense toward a single spot.

Immediately thereafter, a semi-transparent sword that was only around an inch in length shot out of his glabella, then instantly pierced into the tip of Daoist Master Bone Shine's finger.

In the instant that Daoist Master Bone Shine caught sight of the sword, a sense of foreboding had already welled up in his heart, but it was too late to retract his hand, and he could only channel his immortal spiritual power to ward off the Spiritual Sense Sword.

However, in the next instant, the Spiritual Sense Sword abruptly appeared in his consciousness.

Outside, the Spiritual Sense Sword was only around an inch in length, but inside Daoist Master Bone Shine's consciousness, it had swelled drastically in size, and it came crashing down with tremendous power.

The sword was etched with peculiar runes that were flashing incessantly, and they were releasing formidable spiritual sense fluctuations that manifested themselves in the form of powerful shockwaves.

Daoist Master Bone Shine's consciousness instantly began to churn violently, and cracks began appearing everywhere, as if his consciousness were about to be torn apart.

Inside his consciousness, his soul was looking on with an agonized and horrified look on its face. Never had he imagined that an early-High Zenith cultivator would possess such tremendous spiritual sense, and he was left ruing his decision to approach Han Li, but it was already too late.

Chapter 820: You Again?

Right at this moment, Daoist Master Bone Shine's soul raised both of its hands, and specks of white light immediately rose up from his consciousness before converging around it like countless fireflies.

At the same time, an enormous array that had been engraved deep into his consciousness emerged.

He had engraved the array into his own consciousness at an unimaginable cost, and he was saving it for a battle of life and death.

Never did he think that he would be forced to use the array at a time like this, but given the dire nature of the situation, he had no choice in the matter.

The white light radiating from the array was becoming brighter and brighter, and an enormous tiger-like beastly projection rose up from it, then pounced at the Spiritual Sense Sword with its mouth open wide.

A resounding boom rang out within Daoist Master Bone Shine's consciousness as the Spiritual Sense Sword struck the head of the beast, and both were stopped cold in their tracks for an instant before the head of the beast was split open, while the Spiritual Sense Sword continued to crash down from above.

However, even though the beastly projection had been torn apart, threads of translucent light were surging out of its body to try and reconnect the two halves.

The translucent threads resembled chains that were constantly impeding the Spiritual Sense Sword in its descent, whittling it down bit by bit.

Even so, the Spiritual Sense Sword was still able to crash down with immense power, and it sliced completely through the beastly projection before falling upon Daoist Master Bone Shine's soul.

An agonized roar rang out, and Daoist Master Bone Shine felt as if his head were about to split apart as he shuddered violently before plummeting out of the sky, while his spirit domain also faded away.

Both Han Li and Shi Chuankong regained control over their own skeletons, but at the same time, Han Li's vision turned completely dark as he fell out of the sky, having completely overexerted his own spiritual sense.

Shi Chuankong gritted his teeth through the pain of his own injuries as he hurriedly flew over to catch Han Li by the arm, and after taking a glance at the surface of the sea down below, he promptly flew away as a streak of light.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie used the azure gourd to recover all of the Dao Warriors, then also retrieved Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before also flying away after them.

……

Half a month passed by in a flash.

A black flying carriage was racing over the sea, and Shi Chuankong had already reverted back to his original appearance, with his head of silver hair dancing in the wind.

Han Li was laying on the carriage behind him with his eyes tightly shut, and he remained unconscious. There was a small piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade hovering above his head, giving off a faint purple glow.

On top of that, there was also a spatial barrier around him that kept out all of the devilish qi in the surrounding environment.

Seated on the carriage not far away from Han Li was Daoist Xie, and his eyes were also closed.

Right at this moment, his eyes suddenly sprang open as if he had sensed something, and at the same time, Han Li also slowly opened his eyes.

There was still a dazed look in his eyes, and it took a moment for them to focus.

He massaged his temples as he slowly set up, then plucked down the piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade that was hovering above his head.

"You're finally awake, Brother Li. How do you feel?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"How long was I unconscious for?" Han Li asked.

"About half a month," Shi Chuankong replied.

"What happened to Daoist Master Bone Shine?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know. At the time, he seemed to have been severely injured as well, and he fell into the sea. However, you had also fallen unconscious, so I could only prioritize taking you to safety," Shi Chuankong replied.

"He must've suffered some severe spiritual damage from my Spiritual Sense Sword, so he won't be coming after us again anytime soon. Having said that, now that we're getting really close to Night Sun City, there's no guarantee that no one else will come after us," Han LI mused.

"That's what I was concerned about as well, and that's why I didn't dare to go straight to Night Sun City. Instead, I've been flying around aimlessly this entire time, and I was thinking that we would make a decision on what to do from here once you woke up," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"I severely overexerted my spiritual sense earlier, and I would've most likely remained unconscious for a lot longer if you hadn't used that piece of Purple Sun Warm Jade to help me nurture my soul," Han Li said.

"In that case, let's wait until you're fully recovered before we set off," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li shook his head as he replied, "Spiritual sense takes a long time to replenish, and the longer we delay, the greater the chance that something could go wrong, so let's focus on getting back to Night Sun City as soon as possible."

Shi Chuankong raised no objections to this, and the flying carriage flew away into the distance.

……

Another half a month quickly passed by.

The black flying carriage continued to race over the inky-black sea, and a giant black structure that was hovering in mid-air had appeared on the distant horizon.

"We're about to reach Night Sun City soon, Brother Li," Shi Chuankong declared with an elated expression.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he observed the black structure, and he was rather surprised by what he saw.

It was an extremely irregular structure with what appeared to be many branches protruding from it. However, these branches were crystalline in appearance, and they were all of different lengths, jutting out in different directions.

The structure was thousands of feet tall, and it appeared to be a natural structure with bursts of time law power fluctuations emanating from it.

For some reason, Han Li wasn't able to clearly gauge the structure. It was clearly right in front of him, but for some reason, he felt like it was also impossibly far away, as if it were in a different realm altogether.

Right as he was about to activate his Infernal Devilish Eyes to take a closer look, he was stopped by Shi Chuankong, who warned, "This is a paramount divine artifact of our Holy Realm, so it must be treated with the utmost respect."

"Divine artifact? Why does it look like it was abandoned here?" Han Li asked.

"Let me tell you this, Brother Li: even if a Dao Ancestor were to come here, they may not be able to move this thing even a single inch," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

"What exactly is this..."

All of a sudden, Han Li's voice trailed off mid-sentence, and he suddenly turned to a certain direction with a grim look on his face.

Shi Chuankong also turned in the same direction, and moments later, a streak of light appeared in the distance, stopping several thousand feet away from them.

It was none other than Daoist Master Bone Shine!

However, he was looking very pale, and his eyes were sunken and a little dazed. His hair had also become extremely disheveled, and he seemed to be in a very sorry state.

In contrast with the grim looks on the faces of Han Li and Shi Chuankong, Daoist Master Bone Shine was looking a little panicked.

His eyes widened in shock as he raised a trembling finger to point at Han Li, and he exclaimed in a fearful voice, "How... How is it you again? This is impossible! How did you recover so quickly?"

"What is he talking about?" Shi Chuankong asked as he turned to look at Han Li, but Han Li was looking just as perplexed.

"Could it be that he sustained such severe spiritual trauma from your Spiritual Sense Sword from last time that he's been driven insane?" Shi Chuankong speculated.

"I don't think so. He had a powerful array protecting his consciousness, so there's no way that my Spiritual Sense Sword would've been able to inflict such severe damage. Something must've happened to him after we left," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"No, it must be an illusion! That's it... I'm going to kill you!" Daoist Master Bone Shine roared as a fierce look suddenly appeared on his face, and he reached out with one hand, upon which his entire arm instantly elongated drastically, transforming into a white bone scythe that swept rapidly toward Han Li.

Han Li could sense that Daoist Master Bone Shine wasn't quite in the right frame of mind, but he didn't dare to let down his guard, immediately releasing his time spirit domain, and Shi Chuankong hurriedly released his spatial spirit domain as well.

Upon flying into the two spirit domains, Daoist Master Bone Shine was instantly slowed down drastically, but he let loose a thunderous roar as he swept his scythe arm through the air, and the world's origin qi within the two spirit domains were completely shredded by a burst of violent power, allowing him to speed up significantly once again.

Han Li made no attempt to take any evasive measures upon seeing this. Instead, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a sword formed by eighteen combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and at the same time, he unleashed his Reversal True Axis ability before launching himself forward.

As he drew close to Daoist Master Bone Shine, he abruptly stopped cold in his tracks, then summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released countless rays of golden light that encompassed the oncoming Daoist Master Bone Shine.

In response, Daoist Master Bone Shine spread a hand open, and it transformed into a giant bone shield.

The surface of the shield was etched with countless runes, and it was giving off a burst of corrosive law powers that kept the rays of golden light at bay.

At the same time, he swung his other scythe arm toward Han Li with tremendous power, aiming to slice his body into two in one fell swoop.

Chapter 821: Election

Han Li remained calm and collected as a Spiritual Sense Sword shot out of his glabella once again, and in the instant that Daoist Master Bone Shine caught sight of the Spiritual Sense Sword, a look of despair and indignation immediately surfaced in his eyes.

In the next instant, the Spiritual Sense Sword pierced through the bone shield with ease before shooting straight into Daoist Master Bone Shine's glabella.

Only after the Spiritual Sense Sword pierced into Daoist Master Bone Shine's glabella did Han Li discover that his spiritual sense was virtually non-existent, and his soul was also looking extremely frail, much like a candle flame in the wind.

It was clear that he had suffered some kind of severe trauma that had left his soul in a terrible condition.

While it was true that he had managed to inflict a great deal of spiritual damage upon Daoist Master Bone Shine during their previous battle, he was certain that his Spiritual Sense Sword wouldn't have been enough to leave Daoist Master Bone Shine's soul in such a precarious condition.

Despite the befuddlement in his mind, Han Li didn't hesitate in the slightest to land the killing blow, and his Spiritual Sense Sword swung down upon Daoist Master Bone Shine's soul, tearing it apart with ease.

Immediately thereafter, Daoist Master Bone Shine fell completely still.

Shi Chuankong had only just finished setting up his Twin Heavenly Silver Mirrors, and he had no idea what had happened to Daoist Master Bone Shine, but he certainly wasn't going to pass up this opportunity.

The two mirrors began to swap positions at his behest, releasing a burst of tremendous spatial force as they did so.

However, as a Great Encompassment cultivator, Daoist Master Bone Shine's body was extremely resilient. In particular, his bones were near indestructible, and his body was only slightly warped by the immense spatial power, amounting to no substantial injuries.

Despite Shi Chuankong's best efforts, there simply wasn't much that he could do.

Meanwhile, Han Li raised a hand to make a beckoning motion, and a black ring slipped off Daoist Master Bone Shine's finger before flying into his grasp, following which a silver fire raven shot out of his shoulder before engulfing Daoist Master Bone Shine's entire body.

Shi Chuankong had witnessed the power of the Essence Fire Raven in the past, and he knew that Daoist Master Bone Shine's fate was sealed. Sure enough, as soon as the silver flames engulfed his lifeless body, he was immediately set alight, and a string of cracks and pops rang out as Han Li stared into the fire in an absentminded fashion.

"What's wrong, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Nothing, I was just thinking about what Daoist Master Bone Shine said when he first ran into us. It seemed like he wasn't in a very sound frame of mind," Han Li replied.

"Who cares? The important thing is that he's no longer going to pose a threat to us anymore," Shi Chuankong said with a wide smile.

Around fifteen minutes later, the Essence Fire Raven returned to Han Li, and at this point, Daoist Master Bone Shine had already been completely reduced to ashes.

The fire raven shrank down rapidly in size before landing on the palm of Han Li's hand, then opened its beak to release a vibrant and colorful finger bone.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then covertly stowed the finger bone away.

"Let's keep going," he said as he turned to Shi Chuankong, and with that, the two of them resumed their journey.

Shortly thereafter, Shi Chuankong arrived at the irregular object that was hovering mid-air before drawing to a halt.

"Why did you stop?" Han Li asked.

"We've arrived," Shi Chuankong replied.

"You're telling me this is Night Sun City?" Han Li asked.

"It's a long story, but to keep it concise, this divine artifact is known as a spatial domain key, and it serves as an entrance to Night Sun City," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see. No wonder it feels like it's both right in front of me, but also somewhere far away. I presume it must be something that exists in multiple planes of space at once. It makes sense now why you were saying that even a Dao Ancestor may not be able to move it," Han Li said with an enlightened expression.

"Come, let's enter the city," Shi Chuankong said with a smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a black badge, which he pressed into the lowest branch that was extending out of the spatial domain key.

The black badge immediately adhered itself to the branch like a magnet before slowly fusing into the branch, immediately following which a burst of black light emerged, giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

Shi Chuankong gestured for Han Li to follow him, then stepped into the black light, and Han Li quickly followed suit.

The two of them vanished from the spot, and the black light also faded, while the spatial domain key returned to normal.

Han Li was overcome by a rush of dizziness, and bursts of spatial power were tearing at him from all directions, but this dizzy sensation only persisted for a brief moment before he found himself in a bright space.

There was a bright sun hanging in the sky, while down below was a stretch of short hills and lush greenery, presenting a refreshing sight to behold.

The devilish qi here was roughly twice as abundant as it was outside, and there were dark purple clouds up above that were formed by devilish qi.

In comparison, the world's origin qi in the area was far sparser.

"So this is where Night Sun City is," Han Li mused as he inspected his surroundings.

"That's right. This place is known as the Night Sun Domain. It's a domain that my father created. It's good to finally be back," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"The Devilish Monarch created this entire domain?" Han Li exclaimed.

Creating a small secret area wasn't overly difficult, and it was something that even he was currently capable of. It was only a matter of creating a small and relatively stable space, and he could easily complete the task given sufficient materials and time investment.

However, this space was completely different. It was no different from the Devil Realm outside, and it even had its own set of celestial bodies. Han Li couldn't even begin to imagine how one would go about creating such an extraordinary domain.

At the same time, he was struck by a sense of inspiration and motivation. As long as he continued to work hard in his cultivation, there was no reason why he couldn't also reach that level someday.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Shi Chuankong summoned his black flying carriage, and it set off with him and Han Li onboard.

However, after flying for a while, Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly, and he said, "It'll take us about half a month to reach Night Sun City from here, and we've already taken too long to get here, so we need to speed up a little."

Immediately thereafter, a purple talisman flew out of his sleeve, then released a flurry of purple runes that encompassed the entire flying carriage.

The front of the carriage immediately became curved to form the head of a bird, while a pair of huge purple wings that were each over a hundred feet in length emerged.

After completing this transformation, the flying carriage's speed was significantly enhanced, and it sped through the air as a streak of dark purple light.

"Seeing as your brothers and sisters are already aware that our target destination is Night Sun City, the journey ahead may not necessarily be smooth sailing, so we should be on our guard," Han Li cautioned.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li. If we were in the outside world, we'd naturally have to proceed with caution, but this entire Night Sun Domain is under my father's supervision, so no one would dare to attack us here. Now that we've made it into the Night Sun Domain, we're completely safe," Shi Chuankong assured.

Han Li was slightly awestruck by the Devilish Monarch's unfathomable power upon hearing this, but at the same time, a sense of dismay also welled up in his heart.

He was certainly not a fan of being under constant supervision.

Shi Chuankong seemed to have sensed his apprehension, and he continued, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, my father will keep an eye on the Night Sun Domain for security purposes, but he won't go out of his way to spy on anyone in particular."

Han Li nodded in response, then said, "Fellow Daoist Shi, there are some things that I've been meaning to ask you. Now that we're close to reaching Night Sun City, I would like you to enlighten me."

Shi Chuankong didn't seem surprised at all to hear this, and he prompted, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li."

"You've returned to Night Sun City on this occasion to take part in some type of important event, right? I don't know exactly what's happening, but there have been multiple instances over the course of our journey where I've heard people mention that a significant event is currently unfolding in the city," Han Li said.

"I was going to explain this matter to you once we reached Night Sun City, but seeing as you've raised the question, I may as well explain it now. You are correct to assume that I've returned to Night Sun City over an important matter. This matter concerns the entire Holy Realm, and it requires me to safely deliver the Virata Lute no matter what," Shi Chuankong replied.

"What is this important event?" Han Li asked.

"The next Holy Monarch Election," Shi Chuankong replied with a faint smile.

"Why is there an election being held? Is your father abdicating his throne?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

After overcoming the five decays, one would attain true immortality, so there would be no reason for the Devilish Monarch to hand over the throne to a successor unless some type of unforeseen mishap had taken place.

"I'm afraid I don't know exactly why an election is being held. Many years ago, my father suddenly declared that he wanted to select the next Holy Monarch, and no explanation was given," Shi Chuankong replied with tightly furrowed brows.

"Could it be that you've returned to Night Sun City in order to try and claim the berth of successor?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 822: Governing Talent

"I have zero interest in becoming the Holy Monarch. Truth be told, I'm only returning the Virata Lute to Night Sun City in order to help my third brother," Shi Chuankong replied.

"You're doing this for the third prince?"

"That's right. Power is championed above all else in our Holy Realm, and there's no lack of cultivation prodigies among my siblings, the most prominent of which are my eldest brother, my third brother, my fifth sister, and my seventh brother. However, when it comes to their ability to govern a realm, I don't think even all of my other siblings combined can hold a candle to my third brother," Shi Chuankong said as a look of admiration appeared in his eyes.

"If you ask me, I think you're also very capable in that regard. At the very least, Grain Mountain City appeared to have been thriving under your hands," Han Li said.

"That's only because I've been emulating my brother's methods. In reality, I can't even hope to hold a candle to him," Shi Chuankong hurriedly replied.

"Is he really that impressive?" Han Li asked.

"Even from a young age, my third brother displayed exceptional talents and ambitions, and he began helping our father govern Night Sun City very early on. Back then, our Holy Realm had just endured a war against the Heavenly Court, and the entire realm was rife with unrest. Many powerful forces were not content to submit to the rule of Night Sun City, and the realm was plagued by extensive infighting.

“People everywhere were suffering, but my father had sustained severe injuries and was too busy resting in seclusion to worry about anything else. His plan was to send out his children to quell the unrest across the land, but everyone with the exception of my third brother was too afraid of the arduous task ahead.

“He was the only one who set off with his subordinates to personally attend to the problems plaguing the realm, and he managed to subdue all of the dissenting forces over the course of close to three centuries. After that, he strongly promoted business and trade, establishing many trading houses and eventually restoring our Holy Realm to its former prosperity.

“That's why he's so revered and respected everywhere," Shi Chuankong said with a look of admiration in his eyes.

"It certainly does sound like he's an extraordinary man. After all, cultivation is largely dependent on aptitude, and in a way, it's much harder to be a shrewd ruler. The Devil Realm isn't as large as the Immortal Realm, but the relationship between cultivators and mortals are closer and more complex, and it's definitely not easy to manage those relations. Even the slightest misstep could result in dire consequences," Han Li said.

"Indeed. Truth be told, there were many things that my brother did that I previously didn't understand, and it was only through my travels, particularly the time I spent in the Immortal Realm, that I gradually came to realize just how much foresight he possessed. He was the one who advised Father to propose a truce with the Heavenly Court, and that was the beginning of our Holy Realm's path to recovery," Shi Chuankong said.

"The third prince sounds like a very admirable and capable man. Why has he not been selected as successor to the throne?" Han Li asked.

"My brother has earned himself many admirers for quelling the unrest in our Holy Realm, but in the process, he also made many enemies. Those people have allied themselves with my eldest brother and the others, and they've been constantly opposing my third brother. On top of that, my father acknowledges how capable my third brother is, but their personalities differ quite drastically.

“My father is more domineering and decisive, and his style is to rule with power and an iron fist, while my third brother is quite averse to killing and ruling by force, so they often get into arguments over their conflicting political views. In contrast, my eldest brother and the others are constantly sucking up to our father, so it's been rather difficult for my third brother to win our father's favor," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I wonder how things are going in Night Sun City right now. For the sake of our Holy Realm's future, I have to help my third brother clinch the role of successor," Shi Chuankong declared in a determined voice.

Han Li remained silent, and the two of them continued onward.

Around half a month flew by in the blink of an eye.

The Night Sun Domain was enormous, and due to the abundance of devilish qi, it was also very rich with all types of resources. Hence, there was a far higher concentration of mortal nations and settlements in here than outside.

Even though the two of them were traveling at full speed without making any attempt to conceal themselves, they weren't confronted by any enemies, and as time wore on, Han Li gradually began to relax.

As they drew closer and closer to Night Sun City, the terrain began to flatten out, and a vast plain appeared up ahead.

Plots of farmland had been established on the boundless plain, and a type of golden grain that was several dozen feet tall was planted in those plots of land. The grains themselves were half a foot in length each, and they were shaped like blades.

Countless yellow-robed farmers were tending to the plots of farmland, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

The thriving grains resembled a sea of gold that rippled whenever a light breeze blew past, and it was truly a marvelous spectacle.

"This place is called the Scorching Golden Plains, and it's the most fertile place in the entire Holy Realm, so the entire area has been converted into farmland. Most of the Golden Saber Rice produced here is sent to Night Sun City, while the rest is transported to other regions in the Holy Realm," Shi Chuankong explained.

"This Golden Saber Rice is giving off quite a bit of devilish qi. What is it used for?" Han Li asked.

"Golden Saber Rice is found only in our Holy Realm, and consumption of it will enhance one's cultivation base and physical constitution. Some of the people in our Holy Realm who pursue the path of bodily refinement will begin eating Golden Saber Rice from birth, and they attain incredibly powerful bodies from doing so.

“In fact, some of the top-tier bodily refinement cultivators in Night Sun City could perhaps even stand toe to toe against you in terms of physical prowess," Shi Chuankong explained with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Shi, my physical constitution is nothing special. When it comes to bodily refinement, devilish beings have a natural advantage over beings of the True Immortal Realm," Han Li replied with a wave of his hand.

Shi Chuankong was quite pleased to hear this, and he nodded in response.

After walking for a while longer, Han Li observed, "It feels like not all of the Golden Saber Rice here is equal in caliber. Are they split up into different grades?"

"No. Just like other spirit plants, Golden Saber Rice isn't ranked by grade, but by age instead. You seem to be quite interested in this Golden Saber Rice, Fellow Daiost Li, " Shi Chuankong remarked.

"I have an interest in all of the exotic treasures of your Holy Realm," Han Li chuckled in response.

"This stuff is hardly an exotic treasure. Once we reach Night Sun City, I'll get my brother to collect a batch of the finest Golden Saber Rice for you," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

In reality, the reason that he was so interested in this Golden Saber Rice was because he had seen the name once before, specifically on a dao pill recipe for the Vajra Bone Pill that he had found in Gongshu Jiu's storage tool.

Golden Saber Rice was the primary ingredient for this pill, but the recipe specifically demanded Dragon-veined Golden Saber Rice, which was perhaps some type of special Golden Saber Rice.

Ever since he achieved full mastery of the Great Universe Origin Arts, he had never been able to find a suitable bodily refinement cultivation art, so his physical cultivation had completely stagnated.

Under normal circumstances, this wouldn't have been a concern, but upon mastering the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, he could sense that his body was beginning to struggle to contain his tremendous spiritual sense, so this was an area that he urgently needed to address.

The Vajra Bone Pill was a metal-attribute dao pill, but it could also enhance the consumer's physical body.

With that in mind, Han Li was determined to secure some Dragon-veined Golden Saber Rice during the rest of his time in the Devil Realm.

The two of them flew onward for several more days before finally reaching Night Sun City. Over the course of their journey, Han Li had already learned much about the city from Shi Chuankong, but seeing the city in person was still quite a shock for him.

A white mountain range had appeared on the horizon up ahead, and its main peak extended all the way up into the clouds, presenting a spectacular sight that was majestic and daunting in equal measure.

An enormous river was flowing through the southern region of the mountain range, and there was no end to it in sight.

Looking at the river from afar, it resembled a giant white dragon that was resting on the ground, and it wasn't any less breathtaking a sight to behold than the vast mountain range.

There were countless boats of different sizes on the surface of the river, and the entire area was clearly thriving.

Night Sun City was nestled in this gargantuan mountain range, and it encompassed the entire mountain range, as well as part of the river. It was referred to as a city, but in reality, it easily rivaled the size of some nations.

The city walls were over ten thousand feet tall and constructed from giant blocks of black stone that were extremely smooth and even, and countless tall buildings could be seen beyond the city walls.

Han Li could see that the buildings in Night Sun City were primarily very tall and narrow, and that was quite different from the styles of buildings that he had seen in other cities on the way here.

The white mountain range in the city stretched from the east to the west, while the river flowed almost perfectly parallel to the mountain range.

The entirety of Night Sun City was split up into three areas, and at this moment, Han LI and Shi Chuankong were standing to the south of the city.

The buildings in the area that was closest to them were all quite short, and they were extremely densely packed with virtually no gaps between them.

The buildings in the central area were clearly far taller, and they were far more spaced apart as well. The buildings were also interspersed with countless wide streets that were packed with people and carriages, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

As for the northernmost area, that was concealed behind the white mountain range, so it was out of sight from where Han Li and Shi Chuankong were standing.

These three areas were all enormous, and any single one of them was far larger than even the largest cities that they had witnessed on the way here.

Chapter 823: Eighth Prince

"This city truly lives up to its status as the capital of the Devil Realm," Han Li praised.

"Night Sun City has already been around for countless years, and it's only reached its current scale after countless renovations and expansions. The mountain range that you see right now is called the White Wave Mountain Range, while the river is called White Wave River.

“Both of them contain holy veins of extremely high calibers, and they're referred to as the holy mountain and holy river of our realm. That's why the capital city was established here," Shi Chuankong said with a hint of pride in his voice.

"This does sound like the ideal location to establish the capital city. Is this also a city where cultivators and mortals coexist?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The vast majority of the city's population actually consists of mortals and low-grade cultivators, and they reside in the outermost Laka Area. As for mid-grade cultivators at or above the Spatial Tempering Stage, they'll generally have their own cave abodes or clans, and most of them reside in the middle Maha Area. That's the most prosperous of the three areas, and it's home to countless shops, as well as the headquarters of our Vast Origin House.

“The innermost Naraka Area is reserved for nobility and cultivators at or above the True Immortal Stage. For all other residents of the city, entry to the area is strictly prohibited unless they hold a permit," Shi Chuankong explained.

"If we enter the city from here, we'll need to pass through both the Laka Area and the Maha Area before we reach the imperial city, and there are flight restrictions in the city, so we'll only be able to travel by carriage, and that would take too long. Hence, we should fly around to the northern side of the city, then enter from there," Shi Chuankong said.

This was Shi Chuankong's territory, so Han Li naturally raised no objections to his arrangements.

Thus, the two of them flew tight against the city wall, and it didn't take long before they reached a northern entrance of Night Sun City.

There were many entrances all around the city, and there had been a long line gathered in front of the southern entrance from before, but there were far fewer people at this northern entrance.

"There's a very stringent screening process for people entering and exiting the city, and each of the city gates has a Great Thousand Mirror Holy Array that can see through all disguises. Hence, you'll have to remove all disguises before you enter the city. Otherwise, you'll be seen as a spy," Shi Chuankong said as he made a hand seal, and a layer of black light flashed over his body as he reverted to his true appearance.

Han Li took a glance at the giant gray stone mirror hanging above the city gate, and sure enough, it was releasing bursts of gray light that shone down upon every single person entering the city.

He activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes and carefully observed the stone mirror for a moment, following which his brows furrowed slightly as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Moments later, he made a hand seal, and a burst of bright azure light emerged over his body, while a string of cracks and pops rang out from all of his joints.

In the blink of an eye, he had also reverted back to his original appearance.

"So this is what you look like, Fellow Daoist Li. Rest assured, people from the True Immortal Realm aren't very welcome here, but you'll be fine when you're with me," Shi Chuankong assured as he made his way toward the city gate, followed closely by Han Li.

Two of the armored guards in front of the city gate immediately stepped forward, and one of them asked, "Who are you? This is the entrance to the imperial city!"

Meanwhile, the other guard's gaze fell upon Han Li, and a look of clear enmity instantly appeared in his eyes as he exclaimed, "You're an Immortal Realm cultivator!"

All of the other guards immediately turned to Han Li with clear animosity in their eyes upon hearing this, and some of them had even pointed their weapons straight at him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, but he remained silent.

"He must be a spy from the Immortal Realm! Detain him!"

The one who had spoken was a brawny man with a coarse beard, and he was clad in a suit of dark purple armor as he approached Han Li in an intimidating fashion.

The nearby guards immediately flipped their hands over to produce lengths of thick purple chains that were etched with purple runes before surrounding Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"What's going on over there?"

"There's an Immortal Realm cultivator, and Captain Luo Tie says that he's a spy."

"Really?"

All of the people near the city gate immediately gathered around to see what the source of the commotion was.

"Stand down! He's my subordinate!" Shi Chuankong yelled in an authoritative voice.

"Your subordinate? Who the hell are you supposed to be? Get out of the way or we'll detain you as well!" the brawny man by the name of Luo Tie scoffed in a cold voice.

"I am Shi Chuankong! How dare you speak to me with such blatant insolence?" Shi Chuankong yelled in a furious voice.

"Shi Chuankong? Isn't that the thirteenth prince's name? He's been away from Night Sun City for many years, could it be that he's suddenly come back?"

"Have you seen the thirteenth prince before? Are we sure this man isn't an imposter?"

"The thirteenth prince has barely made any public appearances in Night Sun City before, so I've never seen him."

"You're the thirteenth prince? What a joke! The thirteenth prince left Night Sun City and the Holy Realm many years to carry out a secret mission for the Holy Monarch, and there's been no news of him ever since. If you claim to be the thirteenth prince, then how about you show me your Heaven Sealing Token as proof?" Luo Tie sneered.

"Who do you think you are to be asking for proof of identity from me?" Shi Chuankong snapped in a cold voice.

A Heaven Sealing Token was an identification token that was assigned to each prince by the Holy Monarch, and it was also a powerful devilish treasure that contained some of the Holy Monarch's power, able to protect its owner in times of peril.

Back in the Gray Realm, Shi Chuankong had been caught in the crossfire in a battle between two Dao Ancestors, and he was only able to survive thanks to the protection of his Heaven Sealing Token. After that, the Holy Monarch had used the power in the token to activate the Virata Lute and teleport him and Han Li back to the Devil Realm.

However, the Heaven Sealing Token had been overexerted to the point of destruction while activating the Virata Lute.

"So you don't have a Heaven Sealing Token? If you ask me, you're just an imposter! How dare you impersonate the thirteenth prince! Guards, detain both of these scoundrels!" Luo Tie yelled as he waved a hand through the air, and the purple chains in the hands of the armored guards immediately shot forth toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. He wasn't expecting these people to actually dare to attack Shi Chuankong.

"How dare you!" Shi Chuankong roared in a furious voice as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a giant purple hand appeared out of thin air, then grabbed onto the oncoming chains before tugging on them violently.

All of the chains were instantly snapped, and the armored guards were sent flying with blood gushing out of their mouths.

"You dare to attack the city guards? Are you trying to rebel?" Luo Tie roared as he thrust a palm forward, and a gust of fierce devilish wind swept out of his body, then transformed into a black wind dragon that pounced at Shi Chuankong.

Countless black runes were swirling around within the wind dragon, and it was giving off a glacial aura that caused the nearby space to twist and warp.

A look of intense righteous fury appeared in Shi Chuankong's eyes as he pointed a finger forward, and a beam of silver light shot out of his fingertip, instantly piercing straight through the black wind dragon's body.

The black wind dragon dissipated with a despairing wail, while the beam of silver light continued onward without pause, reaching Luo Tie in the blink of an eye.

Luo Tie's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he shot back in retreat while opening his mouth to release a burst of black light that clashed against the silver light.

A faint crack rang out, and the burst of black light was snapped into two. Inside was a black flying dagger, and it had also been snapped in half.

As for the beam of silver light, it wasn't even slowed down in the slightest, and it was on the verge of piercing through Luo Tie's head.

As a prince, he had never endured such humiliation in Night Sun City, let alone at the hands of a mere captain, and there were many people in the city observing the unfolding events both openly and in secret, so if he didn't stand up for himself, not only would he be denounced a coward, the third prince would also be made a laughing stock by extension.

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light shot forth, and it wrapped itself around the beam of silver light in a flash, causing it to explode on the spot.

"Long time no see, Chuankong! You've been gone for a very long time, and I've been very worried about you. Now that you're back safe and sound, I can finally heave a sigh of relief."

A tall and imposing purple-robed figure emerged from the city gate.

This man was even taller and more muscular than Luo Tie, and his skin was golden in color, giving him the appearance of a golden statue.

Shi Chuankong's expression darkened slightly at the sight of the purple-robed man, and he offered no response.

"It's the eighth prince!"

"So that really is the thirteenth prince!"

"I knew he looked familiar!"

All of the nearby bystanders were looking at Shi Chuankong with stunned expressions.

At the same time, many of them had also turned to look at Luo Tie with a hint of sympathy intermingled with schadenfreude in their eyes.

"What's gotten you so worked up, Chuankong? You were going to kill Luo Tie if I hadn't intervened," the purple-robed man said.

"He openly disrespected a prince and ordered to have me detained. Should he not be killed for these transgressions?" Shi Chuankong asked in a cold voice.

Han Li had overheard from the bystanders that the purple-robed man was the eighth prince, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

On the way to Night Sun City, Shi Chuankong had already briefed Han Li on his relationship with his siblings, so Han Li knew that the eighth prince was allied with the eldest prince.

Chapter 824: Immovable

Han Li took a quick glance at the eighth prince to find that he was the mid-High Zenith Stage, so his cultivation base wasn't particularly advanced, but his physical body was extremely formidable, and he was giving off a mountainous aura.

Devilish beings had a natural advantage when it came to bodily refinement, and as the son of the Holy Monarch, his cultivation aptitude was definitely not going to be lackluster. On top of that, he would also have access to the best cultivation arts and resources, so in terms of physical constitution alone, he could perhaps even stand toe to toe against Han Li.

Luo Tie took a glance at the eighth prince, then said, "Recently, the Holy Monarch ordered us to tighten security measures and require all people entering and exiting the Naraka Area to display proof of identity. I had never seen the thirteenth prince before, and he was unable to provide any proof of identity. Hence, I concluded that he had to be a spy, so I attempted to detain him for the safety of the city. I meant no offense."

"You see, Chuankong? It's all just a misunderstanding. Luo Tie was only transferred to Night Sun City during the time that you were away, so he never met you, and he was only doing his job. He's my subordinate, so do me a favor and let him off the hook. What do you say?" the eighth prince asked with a smile.

"He's your subordinate? Father has assigned command over the city guards to you?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"That's right. It really is quite a pain, but I couldn't turn down our father's orders," the eighth prince grinned.

Shi Chuankong's expression darkened even further upon hearing this.

"Luo Tie, come and apologize!" the eighth prince ordered.

"My sincerest apologies, Your Highness. Please forgive me."

Luo Tie delivered an apology as instructed, but he didn't appear apologetic at all. In fact, there was even a hint of mockery in his eyes.

Shi Chuankong was furious to see this, but he merely harrumphed coldly before making his way into the city, paying no further heed to the eighth prince and Luo Tie.

The eighth prince was far more powerful than he was, and the third prince's people still hadn't arrived yet, so he would only be making even more of a fool out of himself if he were to press this matter any further.

Han Li was just about to follow along when the eighth prince suddenly stepped into his path.

"Hold on a second."

"What is it now?" Shi Chuankong asked in a disgruntled voice.

"Chuankong, you can enter the city, but this Immortal Realm cultivator needs to come with us," the eighth prince said, and as soon as his voice trailed off, Luo Tie immediately raised a hand, upon which all of the armored guards surrounded Han Li with their weapons pointed directly at him.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

Shi Chuankong immediately flared up with rage once again.

"What are you doing? I already said that this man is my subordinate!"

"Our father ordered me to tighten the security measures and closely examine everyone entering and exiting the city. As a prince, you're naturally exempt from this process, but this man is from the True Immortal Realm, so we must examine him thoroughly in case he's trying to come into the city with some unsavory motives.

“I'm doing this for the safety of the city, so I'm sure I'll have your understanding and support on this matter, right?" the eighth prince said with a faint smile.

"You're going too far!" Shi Chuankong snapped in a furious voice.

"This is my duty, so I suggest you stay out of this," the eighth prince said in a cold voice. "Guards, lock this man up and take him to the barracks. I'm going to personally interrogate him."

Several purple chains immediately shot forth toward Han Li from all directions.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he was just about to retaliate when he decided against it, merely allowing the chains to wrap themselves around his body.

A hint of disappointment flashed through the eighth prince's eyes upon seeing this.

He had thought that Han Li would retaliate, at which point he would have an excuse to detain him. After that, he would beat Han Li to the verge of death and humiliate Shi Chuankong even further in front of everyone.

However, now that Han Li was giving up without a fight, he naturally had no reason to administer any physical punishment.

Having said that, this was not a cause for concern. Once Han Li was detained, he would be able to easily frame him for any crime that he pleased.

"Take him away!" the eighth prince ordered, then turned and began making his way into the city.

However, he had only taken a few steps when he realized that something was amiss, and he turned around to discover that all of the armored guards were tugging on their chains with all their might, but Han Li remained firmly rooted to the spot, not moving even a single inch.

Shi Chuankong was just about to throw all caution to the wind and intervene by force, but he immediately stopped in his tracks upon seeing this.

After a few moments of watching the armored guards struggle with all their might to no avail, someone suddenly burst into laughter from the crowd of bystanders.

"What the hell are you idiots doing?! Luo Tie, take him away!" the eighth prince snapped in a cold voice.

"Yes, Your Highness!" Luo Tie immediately replied, then took a step forward, and a purple chain that was several times thicker shot out of his sleeve before hurtling directly toward Han Li.

Once again, Han Li made no attempt to evade and simply allowed the chain to wrap itself around his body.

A cold sneer appeared on Luo Tie's face upon seeing this, and a series of black spots appeared over the purple chain at his behest.

Countless thin black threads then shot out of the black spots, and they immediately wrapped themselves around Han Li's body as well.

"What now, you arrogant little bastard? Your immortal spiritual power has been completely sealed away by my Black Bamboo Threads!" Luo Tie chortled with glee.

The frosty look on the eighth prince's face eased slightly upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, Han Li looked down at the black threads around his body, and a hint of disdain flashed through his eyes.

"Get over here!" Luo Tie roared as he tugged on his chain.

The chain instantly stretched taut with a loud clang, but once again, it was as if he were tugging on an immovable mountain.

An incredulous look appeared on Luo Tie's face, following which he let loose a low roar, and a burst of dark golden light flashed over his entire body.

In the blink of an eye, he had swelled to close to twice his original size, and his feet plunged into the ground all the way up to his ankles before he tugged on the chain once again.

However, Han Li remained standing calmly on the spot, not moving a single inch.

The eighth prince's expression instantly darkened significantly upon seeing this.

The crowd of bystanders had erupted into chatter, and many of them were pointing at the eighth prince and the city guards with disdainful looks in their eyes, but they didn't dare to say anything for fear of the eighth prince's noble status.

Devilish beings championed power above all else, and even a majority of the mortal population were formidable bodily refinement cultivators. Hence, in their eyes, it was extremely embarrassing that the city guards couldn't even move a single human.

Shi Chuankong had been suffering humiliation this entire time, and it was extremely cathartic for him that his eighth brother and the city guards had been knocked down a peg.

"If you want to take this subordinate of mine, then go right ahead!"

The eighth prince appeared in front of Luo Tie in a flash, then grabbed onto all of the chains as he ordered, "Useless fools! Get back!"

Luo Tie and the armored guards backed away with shameful looks on their faces.

"You possess a very impressive physical body for a human. Let me see how you fare against me!" the eighth prince said in a cold voice.

Han Li offered no response, continuing to stand on the spot with his hands clasped behind his back.

A hint of fury flashed through the eighth prince's eyes upon seeing this, and all of a sudden, thirty-four specks of golden light appeared over his arms.

Immediately thereafter, a pair of giant golden arm projections, each of which was several hundred feet in length, erupted out of his arms, then grabbed onto the purple chains before giving them a forceful tug.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of the pair of giant golden arms, causing all of the space within a radius of several hundred feet to warp and tremble.

All of the bystanders hurriedly flew back in retreat upon seeing this, and Shi Chuankong also took a few steps backward with a concerned look on his face.

Han Li raised an eyebrow, and thirty-six specks of starlight appeared over his chest and abdomen. At the same time, a thick membrane of light emerged over his body, and all of the Black Bamboo Threads were instantly snapped.

Despite the eighth prince's best efforts, he continued to remain completely unmoved.

A stunned look appeared in the eighth prince's eyes upon seeing this, and he let loose a low roar, following which forty-five specks of golden light emerged over his chest and abdomen.

The two giant golden arms beside him instantly took on a more substantial form while extending outward, transforming into a giant devilish deity that was over a thousand feet tall in the blink of an eye.

The devilish deity had the head of an elephant, and its long trunk almost trailed all the way down to the ground. There was a pair of curved golden tusks protruding out of its mouth, and its enormous body was covered in thick bands of muscle.

The devilish deity let loose a thunderous roar as it began tugging on the purple chains with renewed vigor, and Han Li's expression changed ever so slightly as he made a hand seal, upon which a series of true spirit projections flew out of his body, then began circling rapidly around him while giving off tremendous auras.

It was truly a clash of titans, and the nearby ground and city wall were both trembling violently.

All of a sudden, a loud crack rang out, and all of the purple chains were snapped in half.

The eighth prince shuddered, then stumbled back three steps before just barely managing to steady himself, while Han Li also shuddered slightly, but was able to remain standing on the spot.

All of the bystanders were astonished to see this.

None of them had anticipated that the almighty eighth prince would be unable to move a mere human.

Chapter 825: Defusing the Situation

"These chains don't seem very sturdy at all. Maybe the city guard barracks should consider buying some chains from our Vast Origin House to ensure a quality product," Shi Chuankong said as he turned to the eighth prince with a hint of mockery in his eyes.

Han Li could only heave an internal sigh upon seeing this. With Shi Chuankong fanning the flames, this situation was most likely only going to escalate further.

With Shi Chuankong present, Han Li didn't have to worry about his own safety, but he had no idea how this situation was going to be brought to a close.

The eighth prince could barely contain his own fury, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, a placid voice suddenly rang out.

"It sure is crowded here. What's going on?"

An ordinary-looking beast-drawn carriage had emerged from the city, and the voice had come from the cabin of the carriage.

An ecstatic look instantly appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this voice, and he immediately began approaching the carriage.

The eighth prince's expression also changed slightly, and the golden light emanating from his body quickly faded, as did the golden devilish projection.

Han Li made a hand seal upon seeing this, and all of the true spirit projections instantly flew back into his body as well.

Right at this moment, a figure slowly emerged from the cabin of the carriage.

It was a man who appeared to be around thirty years of age with a head of shoulder-length silver hair, and his facial features were quite similar to Shi Chuankong's. There was a warm and empathetic look in his eyes, and he was wearing white robe that complemented his tall figure very well.

"Pokong!"

Shi Chuankong hurriedly strode over to the white-robed man before grabbing onto his hand with an excited expression.

A hint of elation flashed through the white-robed man's eyes as well, but his expression remained unchanged.

"Welcome back, Chuankong."

All of the nearby bystanders immediately fell to their knees with reverent looks on their faces, and it was a far different reception from the one that the eighth prince had received.

The eighth prince gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then turned his head to look elsewhere.

So that's Shi Pokong, Han Li thought to himself as he observed the white-robed man.

"No need for formalities," Shi Pokong said as he swept a sleeve through the air, and all of the people on their knees were lifted to their feet by a burst of gentle force.

Shi Pokong's aura was very peculiar, and even with Han Li's spiritual sense, he was unable to detect Shi Pokong's exact cultivation base.

Shi Pokong turned to the eighth prince, then said, "I understand that ensuring the safety of the city is of the utmost importance, but at the same time, we must take care not to blow matters out of proportion and cause unnecessary commotions. Otherwise, panic could erupt within the residents of the city, and that would only have a detrimental effect on security."

A hint of apprehension flashed through the eighth prince's eyes, and he replied, "That's true, but this man is an Immortal Realm cultivator, and according to the rules, we must first verify his identity and arrange an identity token for him before he can be allowed to enter the city. I only intervened as Chuankong insisted on entering the city with him before the correct procedure had been followed."

"His name is Li Feiyu, and he's a personal guard of Chuankong's. I've already informed Father of this, and here's his identity token," Shi Pokong said as he swept a sleeve through the air to send a purple badge flying toward the eighth prince.

The eighth prince caught the badge and examined it briefly, then gave a reluctant nod.

In the next instant, the purple badge vanished from his grasp at his behest, then reappeared in front of Han Li, and the eighth prince's expression darkened even further.

"Make sure to keep that token safe, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Pokong said to Han Li with a smile.

"Thank you, Your Highness."

Han Li grabbed onto the badge to find that there was a golden dragon engraved onto one side, while the other side bore a portrait of him, and it was his true appearance.

Han Li's pupils instantly contracted slightly upon seeing this.

He had only just revealed his true appearance not long ago.

"Let's go," Shi Pokong said with a faint smile, and he made his way back into the city with Shi Chuankong on foot instead of taking the carriage.

Han Li followed along, and the stone mirror above the city gate released a burst of light that shone down upon the trio, but didn't register any abnormalities.

A cold look flashed through the eighth prince's eyes as he watched the three of them depart.

There was a gray-robed man in the nearby crowd, and he also took a glance at Han Li's trio from afar, then turned to depart. Before long, he had arrived in a peaceful corner, where he flipped a hand over to produce a purple disk before communicating something verbally into it.

A burst of purple light flashed over the disk before immediately fading away, following which the gray-robed man vanished into the ground.

Meanwhile, Han Li's trio entered Night Sun City, and beyond the city gate was a massive street that could fit over ten people side by side.

The street was lined with opulent buildings with not a single shop in sight, and there weren't many people on the street, with most of them consisting of purple-robed imperial servants or patrolling guards.

Han Li took a brief glance at his surroundings, then looked up into the air, where there were head-sized black balls hovering roughly a thousand feet up above at set intervals.

The balls were riddled with black patterns and runes, and they were constantly releasing black ripples that vanished into thin air.

The space near them was also filled with a type of pervasive invisible force, and upon noticing the object of Han Li's intrigue, Shi Chuankong explained, "What you're seeing is a flight restriction created by the array masters of the cities. Taking flight in the city is a serious crime that comes with an extremely severe punishment."

Han Li nodded in response.

"I must apologize to you, Fellow Daoist Li. It was my lack of foresight that almost led to your capture," Shi Chuankong continued with an apologetic expression.

"It's fine. Those people were determined to start a conflict, so no matter how prepared we were, there's no way we would've been granted smooth entry into the city," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"I suppose you're right. Thank heavens Pokong arrived in time," Shi Chuankong said as he turned to Shi Pokong with a smile.

"You never think things through properly before you act. I'm sure you're aware of what things are like in the city right now. Prior to entering the city, you should've notified me, and I would've arranged for someone to escort you into the city," Shi Pokong sighed.

"You're right, I'll be sure to remember that for next time," Shi Chuankong replied in a casual manner, clearly not taking the matter seriously.

Shi Pokong could only shake his head with a wry smile upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, an excited look appeared in Shi Chuankong's eyes as he began, "Pokong, while I was in the Immortal Realm..."

"This is not the place to talk, let's get back to my manor first," Shi Pokong interjected, then dragged him onto a nearby carriage.

Han Li was supposed to be Shi Chuankong's personal guard, so it was inappropriate for him to ride in the carriage with the two princes. Hence, he could only sit with the coach driver outside the cabin.

The carriage sped away into the distance, and before long, it reached a grand manor, above the entrance of which was a plaque that read "Balance Fall Duke's Manor".

The manor was enormous, and the main gate was so wide that six or seven people could walk through it together side by side.

There were two fearsome-looking lion beast statues standing in front of the entrance, and the purplish-golden gates and guards in suits of vibrant armor stationed at the entrance all reflected the regal status of the manor.

Shi Pokong exited the carriage, then led Shi Chuankong and Han Li straight into a hall in the manor.

The interior of the manor was just as grand and opulent as it appeared on the outside.

Upon entering the hall, Shi Pokong turned to Han Li as he said, "Fellow Daoist Li, I can't thank you enough for protecting Chuankong over the course of your journey together. Is there anything you want or anything I can do for you as compensation?"

"There's no need for compensation, I've already made an agreement with Fellow Daoist Shi earlier," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Shi Pokong faltered slightly upon hearing this, then turned to take a glance at Shi Chuankong before making no further mention of the subject. Instead, he said, "You must be tired after such a long journey, Fellow Daoist Li. I'll get someone to accompany you to your resting quarters."

A purple-robed servant quickly strode in from outside right on cue. It was a young man who was rather thin and short, and there was also a rather effeminate appearance about him.

The young man was an early-High Zenith cultivator, and his aura was very cold and calculating, much like that of a venomous snake lurking in the shadows, waiting to pounce at unsuspecting passersby.

"Please come with me, Fellow Daoist Li," the young man said, and Han Li knew that Shi Chuankong had some private matters to discuss with his brother, so he promptly departed, following the purple-robed servant out of the hall.

"I can tell that Fellow Daoist Li possesses both remarkable powers and mental qualities. Where did you manage to find such an ally? Is he reliable, and what is this agreement that he mentioned earlier?" Shi Pokong asked.

"I met Fellow Daoist Li in the True Immortal Realm, and he's saved my life many times, so he's definitely trustworthy. As for our agreement..."

Shi Chuankong gave Shi Pokong a brief rundown of his agreement with Han Li.

"You owe him your life, so you should do everything in your power to repay him. Tracking down that woman by the name of Violet Spirit shouldn't be too difficult, but it may not be so easy to recruit the services of the grand priest," Shi Pokong said with slightly furrowed brows.

"Aren't you on very good terms with the grand priest? Surely it wouldn't be too difficult to request his assistance," Shi Chuankong said.

"That was in the past. A few centuries ago, Father assigned Zhanfeng with the task of overseeing all of the priests, so right now, the grand priest has defected to Zhanfeng's camp. Having said that, I'll still do my best to try and recruit his services, and perhaps there's still a chance," Shi Pokong explained.

"Why is Father doing this? Could it be that he really does intend to make Zhanfeng his successor?" Shi Chuankong asked in a furious voice as he abruptly sprang to his feet.

Chapter 826: Deep Brotherly Bond

"You can say whatever you want to me, but he's still our eldest brother, so make sure you don't speak about him like that in public. Several centuries ago, Zhanfeng was sent to the Black Water Mountain Range of the Black River Region, and he eradicated all of the bandits that had laid claim to the area for many years.

“As a reward, Father granted him control over the priests. That on its own wouldn't be a significant development, but it's becoming more and more difficult to glean Father's thoughts of late," Shi Pokong said.

"There's no need to worry, Pokong. All this time that I spent in the True Immortal Realm hasn't gone to waste," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and a silver lute appeared amid a flash of silver light.

"Is that the Virata Lute?" Shi Pokong asked as his eyes lit up slightly.

"That's right!" Shi Chuankong confirmed with a smile before offering the lute to Shi Pokong.

"What are you doing, Chuankong?" Shi Pokong asked.

"Zhanfeng isn't the only one who can appease our father! The Virata Lute is one of the most powerful treasures of our realm, and now that it's been recovered, Father will for sure be ecstatic. If you offer up the lute to him tomorrow, you'll definitely be rewarded!" Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Shi Pokong stared at the Virata Lute for a moment, then pushed it away in a decisive fashion as he shook his head and said, "You were the one who recovered the Virata Lute, so you should be the one to present it to our father. I'm not so inept that I have to take your accolades and claim them as my own."

"Pokong, what's mine is yours, don't be so stubborn! What point is there for me to present the Virata Lute to our father? It would be nothing but a complete waste!" Shi Chuankong protested.

"In all these years that you've been away, Father has mentioned you quite frequently, so I can tell that he thinks quite highly of you. On top of that, you're also a prince, so I don't think you should give up your claim to the position of successor so early," Shi Pokong said with a smile.

"What are you talking about? I traveled to the True Immortal to search for the Virata Lute for your sake, and I've never even thought about claiming the position of successor for myself!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed.

"Don't think too lightly of yourself, Chuankong. You've managed the Vast Origin House extremely effectively over the years, and Father has been very pleased with you. You may be lacking in some areas, but you're a very fast learner, so if Father displays intentions of nurturing you, don't refuse. After all, you and I are in the same camp, so I'll also be very happy if you can earn more of our father's approval," Shi Pokong said.

Shi Chuankong was silent for a moment before asking, "Did something happen?

"No, don't overthink it. It's just that I was struck by some enlightenment recently, and I realized that while striving for the throne is important, there's no need to obsess over it. Instead, it's better to just go with the flow sometimes," Shi Pokong replied with a placid smile.

A surprised look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

Shi Pokong appeared to have quite a mellow personality, but he had previously expressed a very high degree of yearning for the throne, and it was no exaggeration to say that this was a lifelong pursuit of his.

"Don't worry, I'm fine. It's just that I made some progress in my cultivation base recently, and my mental state has also changed a little as a result," Shi Pokong reassured with a faint smile.

"Have you already reached the Great Encompassment Stage?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed in an ecstatic voice.

"Not yet. The Great Encompassment Stage is not so easy to reach, but I've definitely taken a step in the right direction," Shi Pokong replied.

Shi Chuankong wasn't disappointed at all to hear this.

He knew how prodigious a cultivator Shi Pokong was better than anyone else, and he was confident that Shi Pokong wasn't far away from the Great Encompassment Stage.

"I'll still do everything in my power to become the successor, but don't focus your efforts on helping me anymore, and certainly don't go taking such massive risks in the future. Think about how distraught our mother would be on the other side if something were to happen to you," Shi Pokong sighed.

A look of melancholy appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

"In any case, it's fantastic that you've returned safe and sound," Shi Pokong said with a wide smile, quickly changing the subject, and a smile reappeared on Shi Chuankong's face as well.

"What have you been up to all these years?" Shi Pokong asked.

Shi Chuankong took a moment to collect his thoughts, then gave Shi Pokong a recount of his adventures in the True Immortal Realm.

He spoke about the search for the True Mantra Sect ruins, the descent into the Gray Realm, the eventual escape, and the journey from the Ten Hazards Mountain Range to Night Sun City.

In order to try and put Shi Pokong at ease, he glossed over all of the close calls that he had, but even so, the disapproval in Shi Pokong's eyes only grew more and more pronounced as he listened to the story.

"In the end, we were able to kill Daoist Master Bone Shine before entering the Night Sun Domain, and here we are in Night Sun City," Shi Chuankong concluded.

The journey had been fraught with peril and close encounters with death, yet as Shi Chuankong spoke about it now, it was as if he were giving a recount of something that had taken place a very long time ago.

"I didn't think your journey to the True Immortal Realm would be so eventful. While it's good that you were able to experience so much, you placed yourself in far too much danger. You are a prince of our race, so make sure you don't ever put yourself in harm's way like that again," Shi Pokong scolded with a stern expression.

Shi Chuankong nodded in response.

Even though this journey had been extremely perilous, it was also one that was filled with spectacular and exciting memories.

As a prince, he had grown up his entire life under the protection of those around him, and he didn't know if he would ever get to go on such a riveting adventure again.

"That Li Feiyu is certainly an exceptional talent. Not only has he mastered the laws of time, he possesses power far beyond his cultivation base. On top of that, it sounds like he greatly cherishes friendships, so make sure to remain on good terms with him. Perhaps he'll be of great use to you in the future," Shi Pokong said.

"Brother Li and I have been through a lot together, and I have full trust in him. By the way, what are you planning to do about the Black Weasel King? In order to leave Black Weasel City, I had no choice but to accept some of his requests. I hope that hasn't caused any trouble for you," Shi Chuankong said.

The Ten Hazards were enemies of the devilish empire, so if the other princes were to acquire evidence of their collusion with the Black Weasel King, then that would be a major problem.

"Of course not. It's a good thing that you were able to forge an alliance with a Great Encompassment cultivator. The Black Weasel King has actually already sent someone to contact me, but he's a very cunning man, and I'm unable to see through his objectives for now," Shi Pokong replied with a thoughtful expression, and Shi Chuankong heaved a faint sigh of relief upon hearing this.

"Seeing as you've already overcome your baleful decay, you should focus on your cultivation and consolidate your cultivation base. I've already arranged for you to enter the Moon God Altar, and you can go in in seven days. Try and reach the High Zenith Stage before Father comes out of seclusion," Shi Chuankong said.

"Father's in seclusion again?" Shi Chuankong asked with a surprised expression.

"That's right. Recently, Father has been going into seclusion more and more frequently, and no one knows what he's up to," Shi Pokong replied.

"That's rather strange," Shi Chuankong mused as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'm sure Father can take care of himself. You must be quite weary after such a long journey. Go and have a good rest," Shi Pokong said with a smile.

Shi Chuankong rose to his feet upon hearing this, then turned to the Virata Lute beside him, but before he had a chance to say anything, Shi Pokong declared in a decisive voice, "I already told you that you recovered the lute, so you should be the one to present it to our father. According to what you've told me, our father already knows that you were the one who recovered the lute, so if I were to present it to him, that would only raise his ire."

Shi Chuankong was silent for a moment, then heaved a faint sigh before stowing the Virata Lute away and leaving the hall.

Meanwhile, Shi Pokong remained seated in the room, and he looked on with a warm smile as Shi Chuankong departed.

Moments later, a serpentine black shadow suddenly emerged from his shadow on the ground, and quickly transformed into that purple-robed young man from before.

However, this appeared to only be an avatar, and it wasn't giving off any aura fluctuations.

"Your Highness, I've already arranged for Fellow Daoist Li to stay in the Long Pavilion Garden," the purple-robed young man reported as he fell to one knee.

"That man may be a friend of Chuankong's, but he's still from the Immortal Realm, and we don't know what his objectives are, so make sure to keep a close eye on him. He's far more powerful than his cultivation base suggests, so take care not to blow your cover around him," Shi Pokong instructed.

"Yes, Your Highness," the purple-robed young man replied, then vanished back into Shi Pokong's shadow.

Shi Pokong remained in the hall for a while longer, then quickly departed.

……

There was a courtyard deep within Shi Pokong's manor that was complete with pavilions, pagodas, gardens, and flowing water, and it was even better constructed than many of the immortal gardens in the True Immortal Realm.

This was the place that Shi Pokong had arranged for Han Li to stay. There were special restrictions around the entire courtyard that were constantly pumping large quantities of spiritual power into the courtyard.

Inside one of the rooms deep within the courtyard, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and streaks of light of different colors were shooting out of his sleeves before descending around the room, creating four or five layers of restrictions.

Only after all of those restrictions were in place did Han Li conjure up a door of silver light, and he stepped into it to arrive in the Flower Branch domain.

He paid a visit to Weeping Soul to inspect her condition, but there were no improvements.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this. There was no way for him to treat Weeping Soul's condition, and he could only hope that Shi Chuankong would be able to recruit the services of the grand priest.

With that in mind, a concerned look appeared on his face.

At the moment, things were extremely complex and sensitive in Night Sun City. All of the princes and princesses were constantly plotting against one another, and he could easily be swept up in this mess if he weren't careful.

Even though he was currently good friends with Shi Chuankong, he didn't want to become entangled in all of this. However, he had already slain several trusted subordinates of the other princes and princesses to protect Shi Chuankong, so it most likely wasn't going to be easy for him to remain a passive bystander.

Chapter 827: Borrowing Books

After some contemplation, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of his current train of thought before heaving a long sigh.

Under these circumstances, he was no longer able to control his own fate, so he would just have to adapt as the situation developed.

He sat down with his legs crossed, then pulled out the black bone ring that was Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage tool.

He and Shi Chuankong had been busy traveling all this time, so he never had the chance to inspect the contents of the ring.

With that in mind, he closed his eyes and injected a wisp of spiritual sense into the bone ring, and only after inspecting the contents of the ring for close to an hour did he reopen his eyes.

Immediately thereafter, eight white stone pillars that were around half a foot tall each appeared on the ground in front of him amid a flash of azure light, along with a white bone badge and a black statue.

The eight stone pillars were giving off a faint white glow, and they were none other than the eight bone pagodas.

Every single one of the bone pagodas were giving off formidable bone withering law power fluctuations, and even though there was currently no one controlling the pagodas, Han Li could still feel his own skeleton trembling incessantly within his body.

These eight bone pagodas were most likely Daoist Master Bone Shine's bonded devilish treasures, and even though Han Li was unable to control them, he could definitely make use of the tremendous law powers that they contained.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he summoned his Profound Heavenly Gourd, and a burst of green light shot out from within before sweeping up the eight bone pagodas.

The pagodas were sucked into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, where they were shredded into pieces.

Eight balls of white light then emerged within the Profound Heavenly Gourd, every single one of which was giving off astonishing law power fluctuations.

An elated look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. These eight balls of bone withering law powers were extremely formidable, and they could serve as trump cards for him in battle.

Right as he was about to withdraw his spiritual sense from the Profound Heavenly Gourd, the eight balls of bone withering law powers suddenly converged before slowly fusing together.

A surprised look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

It didn't take long before the eight balls of white light fused as one into a collective ball of white light that was around twice to three times the size of each individual ball of light. Furthermore, a gray bone projection had appeared within the ball of light.

The law power fluctuations released by this ball of light weren't as formidable as before, but a sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart as he observed the gray bone projection.

However, his apprehension quickly turned into elation once again.

He could sense that this bone projection possessed tremendous power, and he was confident that it could pose a threat even to a Great Encompassment cultivator.

After observing the bone projection for a while longer, he set down the Profound Heavenly Gourd, then picked up the white bone badge.

It was riddled with countless tiny characters, and it contained Daoist Master Bone Shine's primary cultivation art, the "Bone Withering Scripture", as well as some of his cultivation insights.

The Bone Withering Scripture was fit to serve as the primary cultivation art for a Great Encompassment Stage devilish cultivator, so it was definitely extremely valuable, but Han Li didn't have much use for it.

His focus was still on cultivating the laws of time, and he had already collected many time-attribute cultivation arts that he was still yet to fully master, so there was no way that he would distract himself by throwing even more cultivation arts into the mix.

With that in mind, he quickly skimmed through the contents of the cultivation art, but paid particular attention to some of the cultivation insights at the end.

A few minutes later, he stowed the bone badge away, then picked up the black statue.

The statue was only around the size of his hand, and it depicted a devilish deity with three heads and six arms, seated on the ground in a strange posture.

Han Li carefully inspected the statue for a while, following which a burst of translucent light shot out of his glabella before vanishing into the statue.

The statue immediately began performing a series of motions, as if it had sprung to life, and with each action that it performed, a passage of text would appear on its back.

However, Han Li couldn't understand even a single character, and it seemed to be some type of ancient language.

Han Li didn't know what this black statue was, but for some reason, it had caught his attention, and that was why he had decided to summon it out of Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage ring.

There were a total of twelve postures that the statue could adopt, and each posture corresponded with a different passage of text.

After some contemplation, Han Li flipped a hand over to summon a blank jade slip, using which he recorded the twelve passages of text in the hope that he would be able to unearth their meaning someday.

On top of these items, the storage ring also contained many other things like materials, Devilish Origin Stones, and pills.

However, none of these items were particularly valuable, so he couldn't be bothered to sort through them.

What was worthy of note was that Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage ring contained over two million Devilish Origin Stones, which was almost certainly going to be enough to cover his costs during his time in the Devil Realm.

Han Li summoned Daoist Xie to his side, then handed him the black bone ring as he requested, "Brother Xie, please sort through the items in this storage ring for me. If you find anything useful inside, feel free to take it."

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then accepted the ring before sitting down with his legs crossed.

Meanwhile, Han Li exited the Flower Branch domain before returning to his room, and at this point, it was already dark outside.

All of a sudden, he raised an eyebrow as he cast his gaze out of the room.

It was only for an instant, but he had detected an extremely faint aura outside, as if someone were spying on him.

After a brief hesitation, he decided not to investigate.

He was an outsider as far as those in the Devil Realm were concerned, so it was only to be expected that Shi Pokong would conduct surveillance on him. As long as Shi Pokong didn't take things too far, he was happy to turn a blind eye.

With that in mind, Han Li made his way into the inner chamber of his room, then sat down onto the bed with his legs crossed.

The night quickly passed by, and the sound of door-knocking rang out from outside the courtyard early the next morning.

Han Li opened his eyes and rose to his feet, then made his way out into the courtyard to discover that Shi Chuankong had come to visit.

"Did you have a good rest last night, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked with a smile.

"It was the safest I'd felt in a very long time," Han Li replied with a smile, then stepped aside to allow Shi Chuankong into the courtyard.

"It's alright, I won't go in. I've only just returned to Night Sun City, and there are many matters for me to take care of. I came here on this occasion as I have to speak to you about something," Shi Chuankong said as his face fell ever so slightly.

A hint of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, and he prompted, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Shi."

"It's about the grand priest. I raised the matter to my brother last night, and he told me that the grand priest has pledged his allegiance to my eldest brother, so it won't be so easy to recruit his services. However, we're already searching for a solution, and I'm going to follow through on my promise to you no matter what, so please be patient," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he said, "I don't want to exert any pressure on you, but I don't have much mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade left. My current supply will only last another decade or two at most, so please hurry."

"You can rest assured of that, Fellow Daoist Li. My brother has already sent someone to purchase Purple Sun Warm Jade, and I'm sure they'll return soon," Shi Chuankong reassured.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"In that case, I can wait a while longer."

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, I made a promise to you, and I'll do everything in my power to fulfill my promise as soon as possible," Shi Chuankong said with a determined expression.

"I'll be counting on you then, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li replied with a nod.

"The second thing that I wanted to notify you of is that I'll be going into seclusion to try and make a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage, so I won't be around for a while. If you need anything, feel free to speak to the servants in the manor," Shi Chuankong said.

"I have to congratulate you in advance then, Fellow Daoist Shi. With your aptitude, a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage is all but assured," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Thank you for your kind words, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said with a smile of his own.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before Shi Chuankong departed.

Following Shi Chuankong's departure, Han Li's expression darkened slightly, and he remained standing on the spot for a moment before returning to his room.

Close to half a month flew by in a flash, and Shi Chuankong commenced his seclusion.

Han Li had stayed in his room this entire time with the exception of a visit that he had paid to Shi Chuankong prior to the commencement of his seclusion.

He was planning to borrow some books from Shi Chuankong to see if he could find any information pertaining to Weeping Soul's condition, as well as to try and find material related to the cultivation of one's spirit domain.

To this day, he still didn't know how he had defeated Daoist Master Bone Shine, and Daoist Master Bone Shine's spirit domain was different from any that he had ever seen before, so he was determined to learn more about the subject.

He had thought that Shi Chuankong would've been hesitant to lend him such resources, but to his surprise, Shi Chuankong had brought him a stack of beautiful books that very same afternoon.

Prior to his departure, he had informed Han Li that these books were from Shi Pokong's private collection, so they were not to be damaged. Otherwise, he would be reprimanded by Shi Pokong. On top of that, there were restrictions placed on the books, so they could only be read and not replicated.

For the first few days, Han Li didn't begin his reading, and only after taking a few days to familiarize himself with the environment of the Long Pavilion Garden did he begin browsing through the books.

There were around a dozen books in total, all of which had solid metal covers that were embossed with extremely elegant flowers and exotic beasts, while the pages were fashioned from some type of soft and pliable, yet durable beast hide.

The majority of the contents of the books consisted of material pertaining to spiritual damage or sealing nascent souls, and there were several devilish secret techniques in them that should've definitely been kept secret to outsiders.

However, Han Li wasn't a devilish being, nor was he primarily using a devilish cultivation art, so he had no intention of cultivating these secret techniques.

Chapter 828: Visiting the Market

What was rather disappointing to Han Li was that he wasn't able to find any cases in the books that perfectly matched Weeping Soul's current condition.

Her soul was unharmed, and even if it had been, all of the damage would've already been remedied by the Purple Sun Warm Jade, and her nascent soul wasn't sealed away, either.

In the end, Han Li could only heave a forlorn sigh and prepare to devise other plans to have Weeping Soul's condition treated.

He wasn't very optimistic about Shi Pokong's ability to secure the grand priest's help, now that the grand priest was in Shi Zhanfeng's camp. After all, they were each other's biggest rivals in the fight for the throne, and there was no way that Shi Zhanfeng would be willing to help Shi Pokong.

As Han Li continued to read through the books, he saw a great deal of material pertaining to spirit domains, and his eyes were completely opened. Only after all of this reading did he discover that his previous understanding of spirit domains had been far too shallow.

He had come into contact with many spirit domains in the past, including even Creation Tier spirit domains like the ones unleashed by Xiao Jinhan and Feng Tiandu.

After that, he was able to manifest his own spirit domain under Mo Yu's assistance, but the latter had withheld a lot of information from him, so he was only now able to systematically learn about spirit domains.

Even though there were two tiers of spirit domains, namely the Creation Tier and the Spiritform Tier, there was no set sequence for which one had to be attained before the other, and one didn't necessarily have to reach the Creation Tier in order to manifest a domain spirit.

However, the majority of cultivators in the Immortal Realm would choose to cultivate their spirit domains to the Creation Tier before making a push to the Spiritform Tier.

This was not difficult to understand. Essentially, it was like building a house. Only after the house had been built and furnishings had been arranged would one generally move in.

It wasn't unfeasible to pursue the Spiritform Tier right away, but that would essentially be like forcing your domain spirit to reside in a barren wilderness, and that would have detrimental effects on the domain spirit's future growth.

In any case, both the Creation Tier and the Spiritform Tier took an extremely long time to reach, and doing so required a huge investment of resources and dedication.

Even manifesting an ordinary spirit domain had proven to be quite a difficult endeavor for Han Li.

Manifesting a Creation Tier spirit domain was an endeavor that was going to take tens of thousands of years at the very least, and it required fusing items of different attributes that complied with one's Great Dao into the spirit domain to manifest objects like buildings, mountains, rivers, etc.

On top of that, this wasn't a process that was guaranteed to succeed as long as one was willing to invest the time. Just like in pill and tool refinement, there was a chance of failure, and in the case of failure, whatever was being fused into the spirit domain would be destroyed in vain.

Even if this endeavor proved to be successful, it would still take extensive periods of time for the objects that were fused into the spirit domain to reach a significant scale. For example, it had taken Daoist Master Bone Shine millions of years to construct those eight bone pagodas in his spirit domain.

As for giving rise to sentient domain spirits in a spirit domain, that was even more difficult.

Very few cultivators were willing to spend so much time on this endeavor as it massively delayed their cultivation progress.

Hence, out of all of the high-grade cultivators that Han Li had encountered, even those at the Great Encompassment and High Zenith Stages, most of them only had ordinary spirit domains, while Creation and Spiritform Tier spirit domains were exceedingly rare.

Through his readings, Han Li had developed a newfound appreciation for spirit domains of these two tiers, but he didn't have that much time on his hands at the moment, so he wasn't planning to pursue the two tiers in the near future.

Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, then closed his eyes and began to cultivate.

The past century or so had been spent entirely on the run, so he hadn't actually even had a chance to carefully study the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra that he had recompiled from the five time-attribute cultivation arts.

Having already cultivated the Mantra Axis Scripture, the Water Divination Time Arts, and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, he had developed a good level of mastery over the laws of time, so he wasn't expecting to have much trouble cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

……

Over three years flew by in a flash.

Han Li had already come out of seclusion, but Shi Chuankong was still in seclusion.

Over these past three years of cultivation, he hadn't made much progress in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, but he had discovered many misconceptions that he had previously held toward it in his cultivation.

For example, he had assessed that he was currently at a level equivalent to mastery over the third level of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, so he had thought that he would be able to make very smooth progress in the cultivation art, but that proved not to be the case.

The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra wasn't just a simple combination of the five cultivation arts. Instead, it had become much more profound and complex, requiring one to perfectly integrate the five elements with one another.

Hence, in terms of overall progress, Han Li was actually still only on the first level. He had come out of seclusion not because anything had gone wrong during his seclusion. Instead, he had come out to check on Weeping Soul.

After paying her a visit, he discovered that her condition was still the same as before, and there wasn't any news from Shi Pokong, either.

Ever since Shi Chuankong had gone into seclusion, Shi Pokong hadn't visited Han Li even once, but Han Li could sense that the surveillance on him had never ceased.

Waiting around like this wasn't going to yield any positive outcomes, so Han Li decided to go out into Night Sun City to see if he could find any other way to save Weeping Soul.

On this day, Han Li emerged from the Long Pavilion Garden, and he was planning to travel out into the imperial city.

Along the way, he encountered many devilish cultivators in the manor, and all of them extended respectful bows to him as they had been informed of his relationship with Shi Chuankong.

Right as he was about to leave the garden, he suddenly heard someone call out from behind him.

"Please wait a moment, Senior Li!"

He turned to discover a petite black-robed woman jogging toward him.

The woman was very youthful in appearance and had a set of spritely facial features, and her aura indicated that she was an early-Body Integration cultivator.

"Do you have some instructions for me?" Han Li asked.

"Of course not, Senior Li, you think far too highly of me. I was instructed by His Highness, the third prince, to serve as your guide whenever you go out so you can find your way around the city," the woman hurriedly replied with a respectful curtsey.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this.

It seemed like Shi Pokong was still quite apprehensive of him.

The person that had been conducting surveillance on him had suddenly left a few days ago, and Han Li had been wondering why that was the case. It seemed that whoever had been conducting surveillance on him had been replaced by this young woman.

Instead of continuing to conduct surveillance on him in secret, Shi Pokong had openly sent this woman to accompany him during his outings.

"Alright, I'll be in your care then," Han Li said with a smile.

The young woman was ecstatic to hear this, and she said, "Please wait a moment, Senior Li, I'll summon a carriage for us."

She removed what appeared to be a spirit beast pouch from her waist as she spoke, and a streak of azure light flew out from within before transforming into a pair of horse-like horned beasts with azure scales all over their bodies.

Connected to the pair of horse-like beasts was a luxurious black carriage that had no cabin, but there was a soft chair that could fit three people side by side.

Han Li and the young woman got onto the carriage, following which the latter asked, "Where do you intend to go, Senior Li?"

"I want to visit the areas in the city where there's an abundance of shops," Han Li replied.

"Alright, in that case, I'll take you to the Imperial River Market. That's one of the eight largest markets in the Maha Area, and it's also the one that's closest to us," the young woman replied.

"What's your name?" Han Li asked with a smile.

The young woman was clearly taken aback by this question, and she faltered slightly before replying, "My name is Hu Jingjing. You can call me Jingjing or Jing'er."

"Alright, let's go," Han Li said with a nod.

Hu Jingjing nodded in response, and with a flick of the reins, the two horse-like beasts set off.

……

The Naraka Area was enormous, and aside from the imperial city, it also contained a huge imperial garden.

The Imperial River Market was situated on the border of the Naraka Area and the Maha Area, and the two were separated by a branch of the holy river called the Imperial Garden River.

To the left of the river was the Maha Area, while the Naraka Area was on its right, and the two areas were connected by an enormous white bridge.

The Imperial River Market's name was derived from the Imperial Garden River, and it stretched for dozens of kilometers along the bank of the river across from the Naraka Area.

"Once we enter the Imperial River Market, we can no longer travel by carriage, so we'll have to continue on foot. This is a rule laid down by His Highness, Shi Zhanfeng, and it's applicable to all of the markets in the city," Hu Jingjing informed in an apologetic manner.

"That's fine," Han Li replied with a nod.

"What would you like to buy, Senior Li? The Imperial River Market is a massive place, and if you wander through it aimlessly, you could go days without finding what you're looking for," Hu Jingjing said.

"I'm not looking for anything in particular. I intend to have a wander through the market, so why don't you tell me about the market's rough layout?" Han Li replied with a smile.

Hu Jingjing duly obliged, giving Han Li a brief rundown of the layout of the Imperial River Market before also telling him about some of the other large markets in the city.

Chapter 829: Dismissal

While listening to Hu Jingjing, Han Li swept his gaze over the surrounding area to find that the bridge was packed with carriages and pedestrians.

Not far beside him was the railing of the bridge, and through it, he could see a series of giant water-dwelling beasts, carrying beautiful louchuans on their bags or dragging them along through the water.

"The largest and most prestigious shop in the Imperial River Market is one by the name of the Flowing Wind Pavilion, and His Highness, Shi Zhanfeng, is the backer of the shop. Most of the items sold in the shop are of an extremely high caliber and also very expensive. The second-largest shop is run by the Vast Origin House, and it's only slightly inferior, but has the best reputation," Hu Jingjing introduced.

"Is the Vast Origin House headquarters here?" Han Li asked.

"No, the Vast Origin House shop in the Imperial River Market is only a branch, not the headquarters. The headquarters is also in the Maha Area, but it's over in another market on the other side of the Maha Area," Hu Jingjing replied.

As they were speaking to each other, the carriage passed over the bridge and was stopped on the other side.

From there, the two of them got down from the carriage and started traveling on foot.

"Continue," Han Li instructed.

Hu Jingjing was very pleased that Han Li seemed to be listening very attentively to what she had to say, and she continued, "The Imperial River Market has shops that sell treasures and materials from both our Holy Realm and the Immortal Realm. In particular, there's a shop called the Immortal Spirit Pavilion that specializes in selling wares from the Immortal Realm.

“As for the strangest shop in the market, that would have to be the Exotic Wares Shop. Some of the items sold in the shop are enough to create a massive stir in the entire city, while other items are downright inexplicable."

"That's quite an interesting shop. Does it have any backers?" Han Li asked.

"The backer of the Exotic Wares shop is His Highness, the twelfth prince, Shi Jingkai," Hu Jingjing replied.

"Shi Jingkai... Does he share the same mother with the fifth princess, Shi Jingyan?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. His Highness is a very interesting man. He's very handsome, but he has a very casual and easygoing personality, and he's never invested much time and effort into cultivation, so he's still at the True Immortal Stage. On top of that, he loves to travel and visit all types of secret areas and ancient immortal cave abodes.

“Many of the items sold in the Exotic Wares Shop were personally gathered by him over the course of his journeys," Hu Jingjing replied.

"He dares to visit all those places even though he's only at the True Immortal Stage? Her sister must be constantly worried about him," Han Li chuckled.

"Indeed. I've heard that Her Highness has arranged for three High Zenith cultivators and a Great Encompassment cultivator to look after him. Otherwise, she wouldn't be allowing him to embark on his journeys," Hu Jingjing replied with an amused smile.

The two of them reached the entrance of the market, and looking up at the tall stone archway, Han Li suddenly stopped in his tracks as he said, "Alright, you can go back now."

Hu Jingjing's expression instantly stiffened upon hearing this, and a perplexed look appeared on her face.

Han Li's smile faded as he said, "You know a little too much for a Body Integration cultivator. You've already led me to the Imperial River Market, and I know the way back, so there's no need for you to accompany me any longer."

The smile on Hu Jingjing's face also gradually faded, and she extended an expressionless curtsey toward Han Li as she said, "As you wish."

Han Li gave her a dismissive wave, then made his way into the market.

Hu Jingjing looked on as Han Li slowly vanished into the crowd, and she stomped a foot onto the ground in frustration before making her way back toward the bridge.

After walking for a while, Han Li took a backward glance to find that Hu Jingjing hadn't chosen to follow him in secret, and he gave a pleased nod before turning his attention to the shops that lined the street.

The buildings in the Imperial River Market weren't as uniform in style as those in Shi Pokong's manor. Instead, there was a wide range of styles on display, and the streets were also extremely packed.

Most of the people on the streets appeared to be no different from humans, retaining only minor devilish traits such as the odd scale, horn, or pupils of various colors.

Of course, there were also some who looked completely identical to humans, so Han Li didn't stick out much in the crowd.

After walking for a while, Han Li spotted a three-story pavilion that had been constructed more so in the style of the Immortal Realm, and hanging above its entrance was a plaque that read "Immortal Spirit Pavilion".

Compared with the neighboring shops, business was clearly a little slow for the Immortal Spirit Pavilion.

Han Li stepped into the shop, and as soon as he did so, he immediately felt a burst of abundant immortal spiritual power.

As it turned out, there was a massive array in the shop that could confine the surrounding spiritual qi and keep it enclosed within the shop.

A young man in a scholarly robe emerged to approach Han Li, and he smiled as he asked, "What can I help you with today, esteemed customer?"

"I was wondering why this shop has been opened in the capital city of the Devil Realm," Han Li inquired in a casual manner.

"Just as there are devilish beings in the Immortal Realm, there are also human cultivators in the Devil Realm. You are precisely one of them, are you not? Our shop caters to foreign human cultivators like yourself," the young man explained, and Han Li nodded in response.

"Can I help you with anything today?" the young man asked.

"I would like to purchase some materials," Han Li replied, then pulled a list out of his sleeve before offering it to the young man.

The man accepted the list, but as he inspected the items on it, his brows gradually began to furrow.

The young man hesitated momentarily, then said, "All of these premium materials. I'm afraid our shop doesn't stock any of the materials on the list aside from the first two. However, if you'd like, I can consult my superiors to see if we can transfer stock over from elsewhere."

"That would be great. Ideally, I'd like to have all of the items on the list ticked off," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I'm afraid that's going to be very difficult. These materials are all extremely precious, and by estimates, we won't even be able to gather half of them, so you'll have to find the rest elsewhere," the young man said in an apologetic manner.

"That's fine, just gather what you can," Han Li replied in a nonchalant manner.

"A large amount of resources must be expended to transfer stock over from the Immortal Realm, so if you're not in a hurry, you can wait for the next scheduled stock transference between the two realms. If you require these items urgently, then we can transfer the stock earlier than scheduled, but that's going to make the materials more expensive," the young man said.

"It's fine, I can wait as long as it's not too long a wait," Han Li replied.

"The next scheduled stock transference will be roughly in ten years," the young man said.

"How much extra will I have to pay to cover the transference cost?" Han Li asked.

"According to the rules of our trading house, transferred stock will set you back an extra 10%," the young man replied.

"Can I pay using Immortal Origin Stones?" Han Li asked.

"Of course," the young man replied with a smile.

"Alright, then I'll wait the ten years," Han Li confirmed.

"In that case, please come with me, and I'll bring out the two materials that we have in stock for your inspection," the young man said.

……

Inside an elegant courtyard in the imperial city.

Hu Jingjing rushed through the front yard, then drew to a halt in front of a beautiful white building at the very rear of the courtyard.

Back when she was with Han Li, she had only displayed an early-Body Integration Stage cultivation base, yet now, her cultivation base had swelled to the early-Golden Immortal Stage.

She was just about to speak when the door in front of her opened up inward on its own, and she hesitated momentarily before stepping inside.

The room that she stepped into was quite spacious, and there was a silver-haired man in a tight-fitting robe, gently stroking a brush over a huge canvas.

The painting on the canvas depicted a tall and steep black mountain, standing on the summit of which was an indistinct figure, while a ferocious storm raged around them. At the very center of the painting was a bolt of white lightning that divided the entire image into two halves.

"What happened, Jingjing? Why are you back so soon?"

The silver-haired man was none other than Shi Pokong, and he turned to face Hu Jingjing with a warm smile on his face.

Hu Jingjing extended a respectful curtsey, then began to deliver a recount of what had happened.

She did so in an extremely detailed fashion, even going as far as to relay everything that Han Li had said to her word for word, as well as the expressions that he had displayed during their interactions.

Shi Pokong crossed his arms as he listened in silence, and only after Hu Jingjing had completed her recount did he ask, "You didn't try to follow him in secret after he chased you away, did you?"

"You told me not to overstep any boundaries, so I didn't dare to try and follow him," Hu Jingjing hurriedly replied.

"You did very well," Shi Pokong replied with a smile.

A hint of hesitation flashed through Hu Jingjing's eyes, and it was clear that she wanted to say something.

"What is it?" Shi Pokong asked with a smile.

"On the way to the market, he was very pleasant and easygoing, but his demeanor suddenly shifted at the entrance of the Imperial River Market, and part of the reason that I refrained from following him was because I was scared," Hu Jingjing revealed.

Chapter 830: Those Who Possess Discerning Eyes

"He did that intentionally to send a message. In the beginning, he allowed you to serve as his guide as a gesture of respect to me. He then dismissed you upon reaching the Imperial River Market to warn me not to overstep my boundaries and. It's clear that he's not very pleased with my surveillance measures, but he's expressing his discontent in a very tactful manner," Shi Pokong analyzed with a smile.

"Such insolence from a mere human! Does he not know that he's currently in the capital city of our Holy Realm? I think you've been too kind and tolerant of him up to this point, Your Highness! Hu Jingjing said in a disgruntled voice."

"That's enough. He's a guest of Chuankong's, so we should be respecting his boundaries. Instruct everyone not to conduct any further surveillance on him," Shi Pokong said.

"Yes, Your Highness," Hu Qingqing hurriedly replied.

"Alright, you can go now," Shi Pokong said with a dismissive wave.

Hu Qingqing immediately departed as instructed, while Shi Pokong turned to stare at the giant artwork with a thoughtful expression.

After a long silence, he murmured to himself, "As expected, he's quite an interesting character..."

......

Inside the Imperial River Market, Han Li had already left the Immortal Spirit Pavilion and arrived in front of a strange building that was situated by the river with its entrance facing the river rather than the main street.

The entire building was constructed from some type of black stone material, and it had a dome ceiling with circles of peculiar patterns etched onto its surface.

At this moment, he was standing in front of the building, looking up at the plaque above the entrance, which read "Exotic Wares Shop".

After a brief hesitation, he made his way into the shop, and as soon as he did so, he discovered that there wasn't even a single customer inside.

The items sold in the shop were split up into two clear sections, and hanging on the counter to the left was a black wooden sign that read "reserved for those who possess discerning eyes". The writing was very old, and a thick layer of dust had accumulated over the sign's surface.

There was a wooden sign hanging from the counter on the right as well, and this one appeared a little newer, bearing the words "reserved for those who possess plentiful wealth".

There was an employee standing behind each counter, and one of them was yawning in a sleepy fashion, while the other was engrossed in an antiquated azure book that he was reading.

Upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered the book to be a raunchy romance novel, rather than any cultivation art.

The employee's brows furrowed slightly with disdain at the sight of Han Li, and he turned away slightly before putting the book away.

"How can we help you today? You won't find much legitimate wares in our shop, but we stock a lot of weird and wacky items," the employee declared, and Han Li was momentarily rendered speechless by this bizarre spiel.

He took a glance at the shelves behind the employee to find that they were laden with all types of devilish treasures and pills, all of which were placed haphazardly with no rhyme or reason to be found.

All of the items were of a high caliber, but the price tags attached were downright astonishing, and they were very expensive in Han Li's eyes, even after securing Daoist Master Bone Shine's entire wealth.

However, after some inspection, Han Li didn't find anything that caught his eye, so he shook his head before turning to the counter on the left.

The employee seemed to be accustomed to customers displaying no interest in the shop's wares, and he casually picked up his book again before continuing his reading.

The items on the shelves behind this counter were strewn around even more haphazardly, and they had no price tags attached, either.

Han Li could see various beastly appendages on the shelves, some of which were still giving off a faint sheen, while others were looking completely withered and lifeless.

Beside all of these appendages were many transparent vials that held spirit liquids of different colors, submerged within which were eyeballs that belonged to different types of beasts and even human cultivators.

All of a sudden, an eyeball that resembled a gray rock caught Han Li's attention, and he pointed at it as he asked, "How much for that one?"

Only then did the employee at the counter stop dozing off, and he turned to look at the eyeball in question in a bleary-eyed manner, then replied in a lazy voice, "3,500 Devilish Origin Stones."

"Why is it so expensive? Aren't these items supposed to be reserved for those who possess discerning eyes?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"They are indeed reserved for those who possess discerning eyes, but we never said that we were giving out these items for free," the employee yawned in a lazy manner.

Han Li had no response to this.

If he wasn't mistaken, the eyeball belonged to a mature Primordial Fei Beast, so it was an item that contained time law powers.

However, a restriction seemed to have been cast onto the vial that housed the eyeball, sealing in all of its energy fluctuations.

Han Li turned his attention away from the eyeball, then asked, "Do you have any maps of Night Sun City here?"

"We do, but there are some sensitive places in the Naraka Area and elsewhere in the city that aren't displayed on the map," the employee replied.

"That's fine. If you could throw in a brochure that introduces all of the noteworthy locations in the city, then that would be even better," Han Li said.

"The map of Night Sun City costs fifty Devilish Origin Stones, and we also sell journals that lay out all of the noteworthy locations in the city for three hundred Devilish Origin Stones each. If you want to purchase some pieces of information that aren't publicly available, we can help you as well, but those services will be rather pricey," the employee replied.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then said, "I'll pass for now. Just get me a map and a copy of the journal."

After handing over the Devilish Origin Stones in exchange for a black jade slip and a thick black book, Han Li turned to depart, but right as he was about to step out of the shop, the employee suddenly called out after him, "Would you like to reconsider the Primordial Fei Beast eyeball? The price is negotiable."

"Oh? How so?" Han Li asked.

"The deputy shopkeeper of our shop has established a rule for us, which states that if a customer can offer something of sufficient value, then the prices of items on the shelves reserved for those who possess discerning eyes can be negotiated," the employee replied.

"Something of sufficient value?" Han Li mused.

"Something that's sufficiently strange or exotic will do as well. We'll decide if it's valuable or not," the employee added.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li suddenly asked, "I can see that you have many beastly appendages here, do you purchase complete bodies?"

"That would depend on what body you have to offer. Generally speaking, we only purchase bodies of beings at or above the High Zenith Stage. Otherwise, the body of a normal cultivator has no use to anyone," the employee replied.

"I want to sell the body of a Gray Immortal," Han Li declared.

A look of intrigue instantly appeared in the employee's eyes upon hearing this, and he asked, "What cultivation base?"

"He was a Golden Immortal during his lifetime," Han Li replied.

A hint of disappointment flashed through the employee's eyes upon hearing this.

"If it were a High Zenith Stage Gray Immortal's body, then you could even directly exchange it for this Primordial Fei Beast eyeball. However, if it's only a Golden Immortal Stage body, then it'll only cover part of the eyeball's cost."

"How much do I have to pay to make up the difference?" Han Li asked.

"Five hundred Devilish Origin Stones," the employee replied.

"Deal," Han Li declared with a nod, then swept a sleeve through the air, and a white-robed body of a Gray Immortal appeared on the counter.

This was the body of the first Gray Immortal that he had encountered back in the True Mantra Sect ruins.

The employee approached the body, then pried open its eyelids, and after conducting a close examination, he pulled out a palm-sized silver mirror before hovering it over every single inch of the body from head to toe.

After putting the mirror away, he nodded as he confirmed, "This is a satisfactory body."

With that, Han Li paid five hundred Devilish Origin Stones in exchange for the Primordial Fei Beast eyeball, then left the shop.

Not long after his departure, a tall and slender woman slowly emerged from behind the screen at the back of the shop.

She was wearing a suit of tight-fitting silver armor that only covered her chest and abdomen, and it perfectly highlighted her exceptional curves. Her silver hair was arranged into a tall bun that was fastened with a silver hairpin, and her features were strikingly beautiful.

The two shopkeepers hurriedly rushed out from behind their counters before extending respectful bows as they greeted, "Welcome, Shopkeeper."

The woman waved a dismissive hand, and her gaze was fixed on the body of the Gray Immortal on the counter.

She then cast her gaze outside as she murmured to herself, "I tried to give you an opportunity to gather more information, but it seems like you're a very patient man."

Upon returning to the main street, Han Li took a glance up at the sky to find that it was still quite early, so he continued to stroll through the Imperial River Market, but he made a point not to visit the Flowing Wind Pavilion, which had the backing of the eldest prince.

......

Only at night did Han Li return to Shi Pokong's manor on a beast-drawn carriage that he had purchased, and he quickly retired to his room.

After activating all of the restrictions, he sat down onto a chair, then flipped a hand over to summon the Primordial Fei Beast eyeball that he had purchased earlier.

He slowly injected a wisp of time law powers into the eyeball, and a series of cracks instantly appeared on its surface, with golden light shining through all of the cracks.

Only after the outermost layer of rock-like skin had completely peeled off was the golden eyeball inside completely revealed, and it was giving off tremendous time law power fluctuations.

Chapter 831: Searching for a Cure

Han Li hurriedly stowed the eyeball away upon seeing this, and only then did the time law power fluctuations in the room fade away.

The eyeball definitely hadn't come from an ordinary Primordial Fei Beast. The time law powers that it contained were many times more potent than the first Primordial Fei Beast eyeball that he had obtained, and he couldn't help but wonder if the eyeball had come from a mutated Primordial Fei Beast.

In any case, he had clearly stumbled upon a massive bargain, and he truly did live up to the requirement of possessing discerning eyes.

Most of the items on the catalog that he had obtained from the Immortal Spirit Pavilion earlier were items that contained time law powers, and he was gathering them in preparation to further his cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

He could still make progress in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra without these items, but progress would be very slow. With these items at his disposal, he would be able to make much faster progress, and this Primordial Fei Beast eyeball was perfect for his current needs.

A contemplative look appeared on his face after he stowed the eyeball away.

His original plan for the day was to try and find some way through which he could contact the grand priest of the devil race in private, but even though the employee at the Exotic Wares Shop had presented him with the opportunity to purchase information that wasn't readily available, he ultimately turned down the opportunity after some consideration.

He didn't trust the shop, and on top of that, he wanted to familiarize himself with the rules of Night Sun City first before he made any moves.

At the moment, he was in a completely alien realm, so it was best to proceed with caution.

Some time later, Han Li's brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

Daoist Xie stepped out of the door of silver light, then said to Han Li, "Fellow Daoist Han, I'm getting this strange feeling again..."

"What is it?" Han Li asked as he invited Daoist Xie to take a seat.

"While you were exploring Night Sun City, some memories surfaced in my mind, but they were all very fragmented and impossible to make sense of," Daoist Xie replied.

"What are the memories? Can you describe them to me?" Han Li asked.

After taking some time to collect his thoughts, Daoist Xie said, "There's a small black city, an azure river, and a massive arched bridge."

"That's it?" Han Li asked.

"For some reason, when those images first surfaced in my mind, they were extremely clear, but now that I'm trying to recall them, they've become very blurry and indistinct," Daoist Xie sighed as he massaged his own temples.

"Don't push yourself too hard. We won't be leaving Night Sun City anytime soon, so we'll have plenty of time to get to the bottom of things. Once Shi Chuankong comes out of seclusion, I'll ask him about the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Han Li said.

Daoist Xie nodded in response with a hesitant expression.

"Why did you want to see me so urgently? I'm assuming there are other things you wanted to speak to me about, right?" Han Li asked.

"Regarding the Scalptia Spatial Domain... That seems to be... a very dangerous place," Daoist Xie replied in a hesitant manner.

"Have you recalled some things?" Han Li asked.

"Only very fragmented and indistinct bits of information," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

"It looks like this place is somewhat beneficial to the recovery of your memories. Perhaps your former owner was here in the past," Han Li speculated.

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then said, "I found some materials in Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage ring that would benefit my cultivation, and I also have to upgrade Thunderslash and Heavenslash, so I want to go into seclusion for some time."

"Go ahead. Right now, we're relatively safe in Night Sun City, so you can rest assured and go into seclusion," Han Li replied with a nod.

Daoist Xie expressed his gratitude to Han Li, then returned to the domain.

As for Han Li himself, he sat in silence for a moment, then brought out the map and journal that he had purchased from the Exotic Wares Shop.

......

Around half a month later, Han Li set off for the Imperial River Market again. On this occasion, Hu Jingjing didn't appear, and he didn't notice anyone else following him in secret, either.

From that point onward, it was as if Shi Pokong had completely forgotten about him, and there was no further interaction between the two.

Several months later, Han Li had already visited all of the shops in the Imperial River Market, and he had also sold some of the devilish treasures in Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage ring and purchased several time-attribute treasures.

At the same time, he had also been searching for information pertaining to the grand priest, as well as ways to treat Weeping Soul's condition, but next to zero progress had been made on both fronts.

As a precautionary measure, Han Li had intentionally avoided all of the shops with powerful backers, such as the Flowing Wind Pavilion.

During a conversation with a shopkeeper that he had become rather familiar with, the shopkeeper suggested that he pay a visit to Sky View Street.

According to the shopkeeper, there were many high-grade pill refinement masters on Sky View Street, and in particular, one of the Heavenly Pill Masters of the Prosperous Origin Hall was very renowned for treating all types of strange conditions.

On this day, Han Li traveled across most of Night Sun City to visit Sky View Street.

Sky View Street was over twice the size of the Imperial River Market, and it was actually a market that consisted of a total of fourteen streets, all the shops in this market primarily sold pills and pill refinement ingredients.

Situated at the main entrance of the market was a massive white stone archway, and beyond the archway was a white stone plaza that was completely empty with the exception of a copper cauldron that was over a hundred feet tall at its very center.

There was a flame burning within the cauldron, and smoke was swirling around in the air above.

Han Li made his way over to the cauldron, then took a whiff of the nearby air, and he discovered that there were no pills being refined in the cauldron. Instead, some type of incense had been lit inside, and the aroma that it was releasing was masking the smells of all of the pills and ingredients wafting throughout the entire market.

After passing by the cauldron, Han Li made his way down the street directly in front of him.

The construction styles of the buildings that lined the street were more uniform than that of the ones in the Imperial River Market. Most of them had white outer walls and either conical or dome roofs.

The street was packed with people, but it wasn't rowdy or chaotic at all. None of the shopkeepers or employees of any of the shops were verbally advertising their wares, and everything was very calm and orderly.

Han Li followed the instructions given to him by the shopkeeper, making his way to the midsection of the street before turning left onto another street en route to the Prosperous Origin Hall.

Once there, he discovered that the Prosperous Origin Hall was around twice the size of all of the other shops in the area, and business also seemed to be booming inside.

There were devilish cultivators standing in front of all of the counters in the shop, and they were being served by seven or eight employees. The shop was so busy that Han Li was being left unattended.

Right at this moment, a middle-aged man in a brocade robe emerged from the inner hall, and he immediately approached Han Li with a warm smile.

"Sorry to keep you waiting," the man hurriedly apologized.

"It's fine, I only just came in," Han Li replied with a smile.

"How can I help you today? Would you like to purchase pills or ingredients?" the brocade-robed man asked.

"Neither. I'm here to see someone," Han Li replied.

A hint of surprise flashed through the brocade-robed man's eyes upon hearing this, following which a wary look appeared on his face.

"Please don't misunderstand, I just want to meet the chief Heavenly Pill Master of your Prosperous Origin Hall. I have something to ask of him, and I bear no ill will," Han Li explained as he cupped his fist in a salute.

The brocade-robed man's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "So you're here to see Master Kang. Unfortunately, he's currently refining some pills in seclusion, so I'm afraid he won't be able to see you."

"He's in seclusion right now? That's a pity," Han Li said.

"If you wish to purchase some pills refined by Master Kang, we still have some stock left. Would you like to take a look?" the brocade-robed man asked.

"May I ask when Master Kang will be coming out of seclusion?" Han Li asked after a brief hesitation.

"I'm afraid I don't have an answer to that question," the brocade-robed man replied in an apologetic manner.

"In that case, I'll come again another day," Han Li said before turning to depart.

After arriving on the street outside, Han Li took another glance back at the Prosperous Origin Hall, then began to make his way toward the other side of the street.

Right at this moment, a tall purple-robed young man also emerged from the Prosperous Origin Hall, and he began to follow Han Li from a moderate distance away.

For some reason, he made no attempt to hide himself, so Han Li quickly noticed that he was being followed.

Upon arriving at a crossroads, Han Li stopped in his tracks and turned to face the purple-robed man.

The man had an unremarkable appearance with the exception of his pupils, which were dark purple in color, and even though it was still daytime, it was as if his eyes were gleaming with specks of starlight.

A smile appeared on the man's face as he openly approached Han Li, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

He had discovered that he was unable to detect the purple-robed man's cultivation base.

"Are you waiting for me, Fellow Daoist?" the purple-robed man asked.

"No. Instead, are you not the one who has been following me this entire time?" Han Li countered.

"My name is Gao Feng. I heard in the Prosperous Origin Hall that you were searching for a Heavenly Pill Master, is that right?" the purple-robed man asked.

Chapter 832: Emerging from Seclusion

"I'm looking for Master Kang in particular, not just any Heavenly Pill Master," Han Li replied.

"Master Kang is not just an exceptional pill refinement master, he also excels in treating all types of conditions related to spiritual damage. However, I can tell you that he won't be able to help you, so pursuing a meeting with him won't get you anywhere, Fellow Daoist Li," Gao Feng said with a smile.

"You know who I am?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I can perhaps help you out, so why don't you come with me, and we'll continue this conversation somewhere more private?" Gao Feng invited with an earnest smile.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was feeling very conflicted.

It was clear that Gao Feng had approached him with some type of agenda, and it was also very apparent that he had to have been somehow tied to one of Shi Chuankong's siblings.

However, Weeping Soul's condition was in desperate need of treatment, so after some contemplation, Han Li ultimately decided to go with Gao Feng.

He was confident that none of Shi Chuankong's siblings would dare to do anything out of line in Night Sun City, and even if he had to face a Great Encompassment cultivator, he had decent chances of being able to escape.

With that in mind, Han Li was just about to accept Gao Feng's offer when another voice suddenly rang out nearby.

A beautiful silver-haired woman squeezed her way past Han Li as she exclaimed, "Is that you, Brother Gao? What are you doing here? Did you slay another Primordial Fei Beast somewhere?"

The woman was the same woman that had appeared in the Exotic Wares Shop following Han Li's departure on that day, but as opposed to a suit of armor, she was currently wearing a white dress that gave her a more feminine charm.

Gao Feng clearly wasn't very pleased to see the woman, and his brows furrowed slightly as he said, "I have no time to deal with you right now. Let's go, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li's heart stirred ever so slightly upon hearing mention of a Primordial Fei Beast, and he knew that the silver-haired woman was dropping him a subtle hint.

A sense of wariness welled up in his heart, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he declared, "My apologies, but I suddenly recalled that I have some other matters to attend to, so I'll be taking my leave now."

With that, he immediately departed, returning straight to the Naraka Area.

......

That night, Han Li returned to Shi Pokong's manor.

While passing through a garden, he just so happened to run into Shi Pokong, who was sitting in a stone pavilion, drinking by himself while looking up at the moon.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Li. Care to join me for a drink?" Shi Pokong offered with a welcoming smile.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then made his way into the pavilion and sat down onto a chair.

Shi Pokong had already brought out a second cup, and Han Li smiled as he asked, "What's put you in the mood to be drinking here by yourself, Your Highness?"

Shi Pokong filled Han Li's cup, then replied, "I've been quite busy recently, so I haven't had the chance to visit you, and I apologize for that. I finally have some spare time on my hands, and I heard that you were quite an avid wine enthusiast, so I came here today in the hope that we could share a drink together. However, you weren't here, so I could only drink by myself."

"Sorry to keep you waiting, Your Highness. I'll drink as punishment for my tardiness," Han Li said, then downed his cup of wine in one go.

"You're quite the breath of fresh air, Fellow Daoist Li! No wonder you became such good friends with Chuankong," Shi Pokong chuckled.

"Speaking of Brother Shi, when will he be coming out of seclusion?" Han Li asked.

"Chuankong endured a great deal of hardships during his journey, and he accumulated many internal injuries. However, at the same time, he's also gained a lot of insight into cultivation as a result of those hardships, so I'm sure his breakthrough will elevate him to exceptional heights," Shi Pokong said.

"In that case, let's drink to celebrate his breakthrough in advance," Han Li said as he touched his own cup to Shi Pokong's, then downed his drink once again.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, I feel like I owe you an explanation regarding Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul's treatment. It's not that I'm unwilling to help you, it's just that there are some rather complex circumstances involved, so I need to bide my time. I hope you can understand," Shi Pokong said.

"It's fine. I trust you, Your Highness," Han Li replied with a nod.

Only then did Shi Pokong finish his drink, following which he promptly departed.

Han Li remained seated in the pavilion for some time before also returning to the Long Pavilion Garden.

Upon entering his room, he activated all of the restrictions, then summoned that Primordial Fei Beast eyeball before channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Ever since then, he remained in seclusion in Shi Pokong's manor.

......

Ten years flew by in a flash.

On this day, Han Li was cultivating in his room, and there was golden light rippling like water around him.

The ground beneath him was covered in a layer of golden sand, while golden flames were swirling around to his left, and there was a projection of a tree situated to his right. At the same time, there was a golden vial hovering above his head, and a golden wheel slowly revolving behind him.

The entire room was filled with time law power fluctuations, and the light in the room seemed to be warping slightly, with some parts appearing very dim, while other parts were particularly bright.

Right at this moment, all of the phenomena around Han Li suddenly vanished into his body, and the rippling golden light in the room also faded away.

Only then did the light in the room return to normal, and it was already close to dusk, so the light was rather dim.

Han Li opened his eyes as he exhaled and rose to his feet.

After taking a moment to smooth down his robes, he deactivated all of the restrictions in the room before making his way outside.

Waiting for him outside was none other than Shi Chuankong, and he immediately approached Han Li with an elated expression.

"Congratulations on reaching the High Zenith Stage, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said with a smile.

"Thank you, Brother Li. I can see that your cultivation base has advanced quite a bit as well. It's already been close to a month since I came out of seclusion, and I wouldn't have disturbed you if it wasn't for the fact that I have something to speak to you about," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"It's fine. I've been in seclusion for quite a while, so it's about time that I came out for some exercise. What did you want to speak to me about?" Han Li asked.

"A few days ago, my brother told me that our father is about to come out of seclusion soon, and that means that there could potentially be a change in the circumstances surrounding Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul's treatment," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Is that right?" Han Li asked.

"My brother and I have already planned to tell Father about your contributions after he comes out of seclusion, and I'll make sure that everyone knows that it was only thanks to your protection that I was able to make it back to Night Sun City with the Virata Lute," Shi Chuankong declared in a confident manner.

"What do you intend to do by showering me with all of the accolades while completely downplaying your contributions? Are you trying to tell your siblings that you're still the same mediocre and unambitious brother that you've always been?" Han Li asked.

"They won't believe me no matter what I say, I'm only doing this to try and request a reward for you from my father," Shi Chuankong explained with a smile.

A look of realization appeared in Han Li's eyes as he asked, "You want your father to order the grand priest to save Weeping Soul?"

"That's right. If Father issues the order, even Zhanfeng won't be able to refuse," Shi Chuankong confirmed with a smile.

"No wonder His Highness told me that he had a plan, this must be the opportunity that he was waiting for," Han Li said as a faint smile appeared on his face.

"Pokong has always been very meticulous and thoughtful in everything that he does, so you can count on him, Brother Li," Shi Chuankong said.

The two of them hadn't met in a very long time, so they had an extensive chat before parting ways.

After returning to his room, Han Li felt himself unable to enter the appropriate headspace to continue cultivating, so he entered the Flower Branch domain to see Weeping Soul again.

Over these past years, he had never stopped searching for a cure for Weeping Soul, but no progress had been made on that front, and if Shi Chuankong had remained in seclusion any longer, he was about to leave on his own.

Now that he had received a promise from Shi Chuankong, he was feeling much more reassured.

......

Close to a year flew by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, Han Li was cultivating in his room when the thunderous strikes of a giant gong suddenly rang out from outside, easily piercing through the restrictions that he had set up in the room.

The sound carried some type of inexplicable power that caused the immortal spiritual power within his body to ripple incessantly, but it wasn't harmful in any way. Instead, it struck him with a sense of comfort.

He got up from his cultivation, then left his room and stepped out into the Long Pavilion Garden.

The sound was coming from the summit of the holy mountain, and rings of silver light were also spreading outward incessantly from the mountain summit.

All of the servants in Shi Pokong's manor were ecstatic to hear this sound, and they immediately stopped what they were doing before sitting down on the spot with their legs crossed.

The gong was struck over and over again, and only after around fifteen minutes did the sound subside, following which all of the servants in the manor opened their eyes with elated expressions.

All of their auras had clearly become slightly elevated, and a hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon sensing this.

Right at this moment, a voice rang out from beside him.

"That's the Holy Essence Guarding Gong of our race. It's able to cleanse one's essential energy, but striking it requires an immense amount of energy expenditure, so it'll only be struck on important occasions."

At the same time, specks of silver light appeared out of thin air, then converged toward a single spot to form a semi-transparent Shi Chuankong in the blink of an eye.

"Is this a spatial avatar? Your control over the laws of space has become even more exceptional following your breakthrough, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li praised with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Li. This is only a mirrored avatar that possesses around 10% to 20% of my power, but it can be projected over long distances and is commonly used for communication purposes," Shi Chuankong explained.

Han Li was rather intrigued to hear this, and he suddenly thought back to the scene that he had witnessed back when he was first transmigrated to the Devil Realm through the Heaven Controlling Vial. Back then, the Devilish Monarch had descended upon the battlefield using an ability similar to a mirrored avatar, but his was clearly far more profound than Shi Chuankong's.

Chapter 833: Audience With the Devilish Monarch

"Does the striking of the gong signify that the Devilish Monarch has come out of seclusion?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. He'll most likely summon us for an audience tomorrow, and we'll be able to carry out our plan then," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

Han Li nodded in response, but he was looking a little concerned.

"There's no need to be worried, Fellow Daoist Li. Pokong's plans are always very sound, so I'm sure our father will agree," Shi Chuankong reassured.

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response.

After that, Shi Chuankong advised Han Li on some things to keep in mind during the audience with the Devilish Monarch, following which the spatial avatar dissipated.

Han Li took a glance at the summit of the holy mountain, then returned to his room.

The next morning, Han Li emerged from the Long Garden Pavilion in a set of formal clothes, and Shi Pokong and Shi Chuankong had already arrived.

Both of them were dressed in opulent purple robes with a jade belt around each of their waists and golden crowns on their heads, giving them a very regal and noble appearance.

Three bright jewels were encrusted onto Shi Pokong's crown, while Shi Chuankong's crown was completely devoid of jewels and also a lot dimmer in terms of luster.

"Sorry to keep you waiting," Han Li said.

"It's fine, we only just arrived," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Shi Pokong was looking calm and collected as usual, and he gave Han Li a slight nod as he said, "Let's go."

There were two beast-drawn carriages waiting nearby, and the first one was extremely luxurious.

It was entirely golden in color, and it was also drawn by a golden lion beast that was covered in thick golden fur. Above the carriage was an ostentatious golden canopy that was rippling slightly in the wind.

The second carriage was far more mundane in appearance, but it was significantly larger than the first carriage, and standing beside it was none other than the Blood Drop Marquis, Xue Cheng.

Xue Cheng smiled and extended a greeting upon catching sight of Han Li, and Shi Chuankong said, "Father is very strict about upholding the laws and rules of our Holy Realm, so I'm afraid we won't be able to travel in the same carriage together, Fellow Daoist Li. You'll have to travel in the second carriage with Fellow Daoist Xue."

Han Li nodded in response and stepped onto the second carriage with Xue Cheng.

"Let's go," Shi Pokong instructed, and the two carriages immediately set off.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Xue. Fellow Daoist Shi and I owe you utmost gratitude. If you hadn't lured Daoist Master Bone Shine away, we wouldn't have been able to return to Night Sun City safely," Han Li said.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Li. Honestly, I feel quite embarrassed whenever I think back to what happened back then. I was sent to escort you and His Highness safely back to Night Sun City, but I completely failed in my duty, and to add more insult to injury, I was severely wounded by Daoist Master Bone Shine. I had to go into seclusion for a long time to recover from my injuries, and I only recently came out.

“I heard that Daoist Master Bone Shine was later killed by you. That's truly an unfathomably remarkable feat for someone of your cultivation base, Fellow Daoist Li," Xue Cheng said with a smile.

"It was only through a series of massive strokes of fortune that I was able to kill Daoist Master Bone Shine, and even then, I was only just barely able to come out on top by the skin of my teeth," Han Li replied in a modest fashion.

"You're far too humble, Fellow Daoist Li," Xue Cheng chuckled.

The carriage continued onward as the two of them chatted with each other.

Over the past few years, Han Li had only made very few outings, mostly to purchase things in the Maha Area or to try and find a cure for Weeping Soul. Hence, he wasn't actually very familiar with the Naraka Area, and only now did he get a chance to take a good look at the area.

Due to its close proximity to the holy mountain, the terrain of the entire Naraka Area followed an upward trend from north to south.

This terrain also formed the basis for the area's layout, with layers of buildings stretching all the way from the foot of the holy mountain all the way to the edge of the city walls, and they were laid out in an extremely uniform fashion, like steps on a staircase.

The closer the proximity to the holy mountain, the taller and more opulent the buildings in the area would be.

The two carriages passed through a few streets, then arrived before an extremely wide white jade road.

The road was over a thousand feet wide, and it extended directly toward the holy mountain.

To Han Li's astonishment, the road was currently lined with people stretching all the way to the holy mountain, and all of them were kneeling and kowtowing reverently toward the holy mountain, paying no heed to Shi Pokong and the others.

"Whenever the Holy Monarch comes out of seclusion, a grand ceremony will be held, and all of the people in the city will gather at the holy road to pay their respects for an entire day," Xue Cheng explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

The two carriages continued to make their way down the jade road toward the holy mountain, and close to an hour later, the carriages finally arrived at the foot of the holy mountain, where they drew to a halt in front of an enormous cluster of palaces.

These palaces took up hundreds of acres, and there were thousands of them in total, all of which were entirely constructed from some type of black crystalline material.

This material was smooth and translucent, giving off a pure black glow, and it was clear that this was an exceptional material.

All of the palaces were etched with extremely elegant reliefs of devilish deities or ferocious beasts, and Xue Cheng introduced, "This is the Holy Imperial Palace, the residence of the Holy Emperor."

Beside the palace was an enormous white jade plaza that was no smaller in area than the cluster of palaces, and at the center of the plaza was a huge antiquated altar that was entirely constructed from some type of dark green material.

The people paying their respects stretched all the way from the plaza to the beginning of the white jade road, and at this moment, the plaza was packed with worshippers that were chanting prayers.

"According to the rules, we also have to go and pay our respects, and only then can we enter the Holy Imperial Palace to meet my father," Shi Pokong said after emerging from his carriage, then made his way toward the altar.

Han Li and the others quickly followed along, and Han Li couldn't see anything remarkable about the altar aside from the two tall statues standing on it.

The statues were very antiquated in appearance, and the lines on them weren't very clear and pronounced, but they still appeared extremely lifelike, as if they could suddenly begin moving at any moment.

One of them was completely white in color and depicted a benevolent-looking woman standing with a smile on her face, giving off an aura of universal motherly love.

The other statue was completely different. It was completely black in color, and it had twelve heads and twenty-four arms.

Each of its faces was displaying a different emotion, such as rage, elation, detachment, or sorrow, and all of its hands were also arranged into different signs and gestures.

Having studied extensively about the Devilish Realm through Shi Pokong's books, Han Li knew that the two deities being worshiped here were the Infernal Holy Mother and the Baleful Holy Emperor.

It was said that the Devilish Realm had been created by the Baleful Holy Emperor after slicing through boundless space, while the Infernal Holy Mother had created all of the life forms within the Devilish Realm.

Han Li naturally wasn't a believer of this story, but he was still quite intrigued by the sight of these statues.

His gaze only lingered momentarily on the Infernal Holy Mother before he turned his attention to the Baleful Holy Emperor, upon which his brows suddenly furrowed slightly.

This was definitely the first time that he had seen a statue of the Baleful Holy Emperor, but for some reason, it struck him with a sense of familiarity, as if he had seen it before.

A faint purple gleam surfaced in his eyes as he took a closer look.

At this moment, there was still some distance left until he reached the pinnacle of the altar, but with his exceptional eyesight, he was able to clearly see both statues in meticulous detail.

All of a sudden, he noticed a line of strange text engraved onto the jade belt around the Baleful Holy Emperor's waist.

This line of text appeared to be of the same language as the text that he had seen on the statue in Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage ring.

He had occasionally tried to study the text on that statue over the past few years, but to no avail, and he certainly wasn't expecting to see more of the same text here.

Right as he was about to take a closer look, a hint of black light suddenly flashed through the eyes on one of the Baleful Holy Emperor's heads, and it abruptly turned its gaze toward him, giving off a boundless aura of darkness that instantly devoured all of the surrounding light.

Han Li shuddered involuntarily, and in that instant, he felt as if his soul were about to be sucked out of his body and into the boundless darkness.

He felt as if he were trapped under an ice shelf that was billions of feet thick, and everything inside his body was completely frozen solid, rendering him powerless to do anything.

However, in the next instant, everything returned to normal. The black gleam in the eyes of the statue had faded, and it was as if nothing had ever happened.

Even though it was only for an instant, all of the fine hairs on Han Li's body were standing up on end, and his heart was thumping in his chest as he took an involuntary step backward.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Li?" Xue Cheng asked.

Shi Chuankong also turned to him with a perplexed expression, and it was clear that they hadn't seen what Han Li had just witnessed.

Han Li took a moment to compose himself, then replied, "It's nothing, I'm just feeling a little apprehensive now that I'm about to meet the Holy Monarch."

"There's no need to be concerned, Fellow Daoist Li. Father is a very strict man, but he's not unreasonable," Shi Chuankong assured with a smile.

Han Li forced a smile in response, then snuck another glance at the Baleful Holy Emperor statue, but it had completely returned to normal.

"Let's go," Shi Pokong said, then stepped onto the staircase leading up to the altar.

Han Li and the others immediately followed along, and they quickly arrived on the summit of the altar.

On the summit was a plot of flat land that was several hundred feet in size, and in addition to the two statues, there was also a giant ovular array engraved onto the ground.

At this moment, there were dozens of priests seated within the array, holding various types of artifacts while chanting to the two statues

Chapter 834: Sowing Dissension

While standing on the summit of the altar, Han Li took a glance at his surroundings to find that the entire group was enshrouded within the giant shadows cast by the pair of statues, and they resembled a pair of deities looking down at the mortals below.

At this moment, he could clearly sense tremendous pressure from the two statues, and even with his cultivation base, he was struck by a sense of asphyxiation.

He took a glance at Shi Pokong and the others out of the corner of his eye to find that their complexions were slightly pale, clearly indicating that they were also feeling the pressure.

The three of them immediately extended respectful bows to the pair of statues, and their expressions instantly eased significantly thereafter.

Han Li decided to follow suit upon seeing this, extending a bow of his own, and to his surprise, the tremendous pressure from the statues slowly faded after this gesture of respect.

A hint of intrigue immediately welled up in Han Li's heart. Could it be that the Baleful Holy Emperor and the Infernal Holy Mother truly were deities that existed in the Devil Realm?

One of the priests rose to his feet, then bowed toward Shi Pokong's group as he said, "The holy mother and the holy father have seen your earnest gestures of respect, and they'll be sure to bless you with good fortune."

The priest was a middle-aged man with a head of messy yellow hair and dark and coarse skin that looked more fitting on an old farmer, but his eyes were particularly bright.

Han Li's brows furrowed ever so slightly at the sight of the man.

His aura suggested that he was only at the early-Golden Immortal Stage, but for some reason, Han Li felt an inexplicable sense of apprehension at the sight of the man.

"Thank you for your kind words, Priest Lian Zhen," Shi Pokong replied with a smile.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

For the sake of Weeping Soul, he had made an effort to learn about Night Sun City's Priestly Temple. The Priestly Temple was a very special place in the city, and all of the priests were directly overseen by the Devilish Monarch, but they didn't have to carry out any missions and were solely dedicated to serving the holy emperor and the holy mother.

The leader of the Priestly Temple was the grand priest, and there were also several head priests beneath him, one of whom was none other than Priest Lian Zhen.

Han Li turned his gaze away from Priest Lian Zhen to look at the other priests, and he was a little disappointed to discover that none of the priests possessed a cultivation base superior to Lian Zhen's.

Right at this moment, a boisterous voice rang out from down below.

"You're here quite early, Pokong."

A group of people stepped onto the altar, and they were led by a purple-robed man who appeared to be close to forty years of age. He was dressed in the same attire as Shi Pokong and Shi Chuankong, and there was a faint purple insignia on his glabella that was flashing with mysterious purple glow.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this. This was the same person who had extended that invitation to him back in the Maha Area ten years ago, except his hair had been black back then, but it was silver now.

The two people standing beside him were also dressed in luxurious purple robes, and one of them was none other than the eighth prince, who was currently glowering at Han Li with clear animosity in his eyes.

The other purple-robed figure was a thin young man who appeared to be rather unwell, with a waxy complexion and a rather uneven aura, and the three of them were accompanied by several servants.

"Long time no see, Zhanfeng," Shi Pokong said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute toward the group.

It immediately became clear to Han Li upon hearing this that the purple-robed man was none other than the eldest prince, Shi Zhanfeng.

At the same time, he couldn't help but wonder what objective Shi Zhanfeng had for extending that invitation to him ten years ago, and he was also quite puzzled about the identity of the silver-haired woman who had intervened.

With so many questions emerging in his mind at once, he began to scan his surroundings to see if he could find some answers.

"You've already met my eighth brother, Shi Chuanjia. The other one is my tenth brother, Shi Bofu. He suffered from a very strange ailment from a young age, and it took him a long time to recover, but the silver lining is that he was able to master an extremely formidable type of curse law powers, so he's not to be underestimated. Both of them are in Zhanfeng's camp," Shi Chuankong explained to Han Li through voice transmission.

Han Li took a subtle glance at Shi Bofu upon hearing this.

He was also at the early-High Zenith Stage, and he was giving off a peculiar aura that was very unsettling.

"Indeed. We're all in Night Sun City, but it's been a very long time since we last met. I recently acquired two flagons of Purple Silk Immortal Wine from the True Immortal Realm, so why don't we all meet up in my manor for a drink after our audience with Father?" Shi Zhanfeng proposed.

Shi Chuankong's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he was just about to covertly urge Shi Pokong to turn down the offer when Shi Pokong nodded and replied, "Of course! It's not every day that we all get to gather in one place, so we have to take full advantage."

Shi Chuankong was very agitated to hear this, but there was nothing that he could do at this point.

"Alright, then it's settled. By the way, you can come as well if you're interested, Fellow Daoist Li. The offer that I made to you during our last meeting still stands," Shi Zhanfeng said with a smile, then turned his attention to paying his respects to the pair of deity statues on the altar.

Shi Chuanjia and Shi Bofu both flashed Han Li a devious smile upon hearing this, then also turned to pay their respects to the two statues.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was very disgruntled by this blatant attempt to sow dissension from Shi Zhanfeng.

"Would you care to elaborate on what His Highness just said, Fellow Daoist Li?" Xue Cheng interrogated through voice transmission with a cold look on his face.

"Xue Cheng! Show some respect!" Shi Pokong scolded as he gave Xue Cheng a stern glare.

Xue Cheng immediately fell silent upon hearing this, but a clear hint of suspicion and animosity had surfaced in his eyes.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he heaved an internal sigh.

Han Li had been quite grateful to Xue Cheng for luring Daoist Master Bone Shine all those years ago, and now that they had been reunited, he had thought that they could perhaps become friends. However, the fact that he was so easily swayed by Shi Zhanfeng's words clearly showed that he was not a good judge of character, nor was he to be relied on or confided in.

"Let's go," Shi Pokong said as he flashed Han Li a reassuring smile.

The four of them began to make their way toward the Holy Imperial Palace in the distance, and the atmosphere was a little heavy.

"Fellow Daoist Li, what was Zhanfeng referring to just now?"

In the end, Shi Chuankong was unable to suppress his own curiosity, but there wasn't any accusation in his voice as he raised the question.

"Zhanfeng was clearly trying to sow dissension among our ranks, Chuankong. Fellow Daoist Li is a close friend of yours, do you not trust him?" Shi Pokong asked with a nonchalant smile.

"Of course I trust Fellow Daoist Li, I'm just a little curious about what moves Zhanfeng has been trying to pull behind the scenes," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

"While I was exploring the Maha Area, I ran into His Highness, and we spoke a little about Weeping Soul's condition. However, he adopted a disguise at the time, so I wasn't aware of his identity," Han Li explained, then provided a recount of what had happened on that day.

"I knew it! Zhanfeng always resorts to underhanded tactics like this!" Shi Chuankong harrumphed in a disdainful manner.

"This is how Zhanfeng has always been, we just have to be careful not to fall for his tricks," Shi Pokong said in an indifferent manner, then took a subtle glance at Xue Cheng.

An awkward look appeared on Xue Cheng's face, and he extended an apologetic salute toward Han Li as he said, "Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist Li. I let my emotions get the better of me just now."

"It's fine," Han Li replied in an aloof fashion.

Xue Cheng knew that his apology was too little, too late, and a remorseful look appeared on his face.

The group continued onward before quickly arriving in front of a black palace.

This palace was over a thousand feet tall, significantly taller than the other nearby palaces, and there was a thick black stone pillar standing at each of its four corners, all of which were etched with extremely lifelike reliefs of devilish deities.

Hanging outside the palace was a giant plaque that read "Holy Imperial Palace" in large purple characters, and the two purple-robed servants standing at the entrance of the palace hurriedly extended respectful bows toward Shi Pokong and Shi Chuankong at the sight of their approach.

"Is Father inside?" Shi Pokong asked.

"The Holy Monarch is indeed inside. Please wait here a moment while we inform him of your arrival," one of the servants said, then rushed into the palace.

Moments later, the servant re-emerged and declared, "The Holy Monarch would like to welcome the four of you into the palace."

Shi Pokong and Shi Chuankong took a collective deep breath, then smoothed down their robes before entering the palace, while Han Li and Xue Cheng followed along from some distance away.

The interior of the palace was enormous, but it was completely empty, making it appear even more spacious. There were all types of reliefs engraved onto the walls, depicting extremely lifelike humanoid and beastly creatures that looked as if they could spring to life at any moment.

The lighting in the palace was rather dim, giving all of the reliefs a rather sinister, shadowy appearance.

Shi Pokong and the others continued onward in silence, and only in the deepest part of the hall did the lighting become brighter. There was a raised platform there, atop which was a seat that was occupied by a purple-robed man.

The man appeared to be around forty to fifty years of age with a head of silver hair, and his facial features gave him the appearance of a refined scholar, but his aura was that of a domineering king.

Even though he was only seated in his chair, all those in his presence were still involuntarily struck by a sense of awe and veneration.

Han Li had seen the Devilish Monarch once while transmigrating through the Heaven Controlling Vial, but that was only an avatar, and he couldn't help but take a glance at the Devilish Monarch in his full glory.

The Devilish Monarch seemed to have detected his gaze, and their eyes met.

Han Li was instantly struck by a bone-chilling sensation, and he felt as if the Devilish Monarch could see through all of his secrets. He immediately channeled his immortal spiritual power and his spiritual sense to try and ward off the Devilish Monarch's gaze, but his efforts proved to be completely futile, and the cold sensation was only becoming more and more intense, making him feel as if he were about to pass out.

A peculiar look flashed through the Devilish Monarch's eyes at the sight of Han Li, but his expression then returned to normal as he looked away again.

Only then did the bone-chilling sensation in Han Li's body fade away, and he heaved an internal sigh of relief.

The Devilish Monarch's gaze only rested on him for a moment, but it felt like an eternity to Han Li, and in this moment, he felt even more exhausted than after an intense battle.

Shi Pokong and Shi Chuankong fell to their knees in front of the Devilish Monarch as they greeted in unison, "Welcome back Father!"

Chapter 835: Exemption From Formalities

Xue Cheng also hurriedly knelt down upon seeing this, but much to Shi Chuankong's shock and horror, Han Li only extended a slight bow toward the Devilish Monarch instead.

The Devilish Monarch was extremely strict when it came to rules, and not kneeling in his presence was a severe offense.

In this moment, Shi Chuankong sorely regretted not further emphasizing the importance of this notion to Han Li.

Before he had a chance to do anything, an accusatory voice suddenly rang out from the side.

"Insolent scoundrel! How dare you not kneel in the presence of the Holy Emperor!"

As it turned out, there was a row of seats arranged on the left side of the palace, and two of them were already occupied.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this. Upon entering the palace, his attention had been entirely drawn to the Devilish Monarch, so he hadn't noticed the two seated figures at all.

There were a total of thirteen seats, all of which were golden in color, presenting a stark contrast with the red seats behind them.

At this moment, the fifth and sixth seats were occupied. The figure on the fifth seat was an incredibly beautiful young woman wearing a purple palatial dress, while the one next to her was a short and rotund purple-robed young man. He was also the one who had called out in accusation to Han Li just now.

Seated behind each of them was a devilish being in a suit of blue armor, and they appeared to be personal guards, just like Xue Cheng.

Han Li paid no heed to the rotund young man, but a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes at the sight of the woman.

She was the same woman who had intervened during his conversation with Shi Zhanfeng ten years ago.

Unlike the indignant young man, she didn't look bothered in the slightest, and as their eyes met, she gave Han Li a faint smile.

Her smile only further elevated her already stunning beauty, and even Han Li was dazed for an instant as he gazed upon her, but he immediately snapped back to his senses before looking away.

"I am not from the Holy Realm, and I only came to Night Sun City as a personal guard of His Highness, the thirteenth prince. While it's true that I greatly admire Your Majesty, you are still only a senior in my eyes, so there's no need for me to kneel," Han Li said.

He didn't want to kneel, but he didn't want to offend the Devilish Monarch, either, as he had to count on the Devilish Monarch to save Weeping Soul.

The rotund young man was just about to flare up with rage again when the Devilish Monarch interjected, "Forget it, Mingzhen. There's no need to bicker over such an insignificant matter."

The rotund young man was very surprised to hear this, but he immediately replied, "Yes, Father."

He then gave Han Li a cold glare before sitting back down.

Shi Chuankong was also very surprised that the crisis had been averted so easily, while Shi Pokong's expression remained unchanged with the exception of a minute raising of his eyebrows.

"So you're Li Feiyu, is that right? Seeing as you're not from our Holy Realm, I'll spare you from the formalities. Pokong, Chuankong, you two can get up as well," the Devilish Monarch said.

Shi Pokong, Shi Chuankong, and Xue Cheng rose to their feet upon hearing this, while Han Li extended another slight bow as a gesture of gratitude.

"Chuankong, you were away for quite some time. How did your trip to the True Immortal Realm go?" the Devilish Monarch asked as a faint smile appeared on his face.

"I witnessed many incredible things in the True Immortal Realm, and I've reaped many rewards too," Shi Chuankong hurriedly replied.

"I can see that your cultivation base has advanced quite a bit, so it does indeed appear that you've made a fruitful trip. Young cultivators like yourselves should all go out and experience some hardships. Only then will you be able to grow," the Devilish Monarch said.

Shi Chuankong was very much in agreement with this statement, and he gave an affirmative response.

"Father, while it's important to advance in one's cultivation base, our imperial clan is responsible for the lives of all of the people of our Holy Realm, so we can't just focus solely on our own cultivation. Recently, the Heavenly Court has been mobilizing more and more troops to areas near our Holy Realm, and it seems like they're about to make a big move.

“I implore you to look into this matter so that we can be prepared if the Heavenly Court decides to attack again," Shi Pokong said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Alright, I'll look into it," the Devilish Monarch replied in an indifferent manner.

Right at this moment, a servant rushed into the palace, then fell to his knees as he reported, "Your Majesty, the eldest prince, the eighth prince, and the tenth prince are waiting outside."

"Tell them to come in," the Devilish Monarch, then waved a hand toward Shi Pokong and the others.

Shi Pokong sat down onto the third of the thirteen seats, and Xue Cheng sat down behind him, while Shi Chuankong sat down on the final seat, with Han Li also sitting down behind him.

"Fellow Daoist Li, Father has a very strict and unyielding personality. I don't know why he decided to spare you from the formalities just now, but I can tell you that you're extremely fortunate. Make sure you do not do anything else that could be considered to be offensive from here onward. Otherwise, if Father decides to administer a punishment, no one will be able to save you," Shi Chuankong warned through voice transmission.

Han Li nodded silently in response.

He was aware that his refusal to kneel could've been construed as offensive, but he simply couldn't bring himself to kneel to someone else for no just reason.

Shi Chuankong's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, while Han Li took a glance at the woman and the rotund young man before asking through voice transmission, "Who're those two, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"They are my fifth sister, Shi Jingyan, and my sixth brother, Shi Mingzhen," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Are they tied to the eldest prince?" Han Li asked.

"Jingyan has extremely lofty ambitions that's matched by her cultivation base, so she can stand toe to toe against Zhanfeng and Pokong. On top of that, she's amassed a great deal of power, and Mingzhen is a supporter of hers," Shi Chuankong informed.

Han Li was quite stunned to hear this, and he couldn't help but wonder what motive Shi Jingyan had for interfering with his conversation with Shi Zhanfeng ten years ago.

Right at this moment, Shi Zhanfeng's group entered the palace, then collectively knelt down and extended a respectful greeting.

"Go and take a seat," the Devilish Monarch said, and a faint smile had appeared on his face, indicating that he was quite pleased to see Shi Zhanfeng.

Shi Zhanfeng and the eighth and tenth princes duly obliged, taking their seats as well.

After they had sat down, Shi Zhanfeng took a glance at his surroundings, then gave nods of acknowledgement to Shi Pokong and Shi Jingyan before his gaze settled on Han Li.

Han Li paid no heed to him, and he merely looked away, completely unbothered.

More and more people continued to arrive, and all of them held lofty noble titles, overseeing certain matters in Night Sun City and in the rest of the Devil Realm.

Shi Chuankong introduced all of the new arrivals to Han Li as they arrived, giving Han Li a rough idea of all of the Devil Realm's important figures.

It didn't take long before almost all of the seats in the palace had been occupied.

However, only seven of the first row of thirteen seats had been occupied, with no more princes or princesses making an appearance.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, isn't this supposed to be an extremely important occasion? Where are the other princes and princesses?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"My seventh brother is currently stationed at Black Duck City to keep an eye on the Heavenly Court's movements, so he couldn't come. My twelfth brother is always out traveling, and even Father can't do anything about him. As for my second sister, fourth sister, ninth sister, and eleventh sister, they're cultivating under a Dao Ancestor of our Holy Realm, and I haven't seen them in many years, so they most likely won't be coming, either," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see," Han Li replied.

A short while later, the Devilish Monarch tapped on the table in front of him as he said, "Seeing as everyone's here, let's begin. What important events have taken place in our Holy Realm during my seclusion?"

Shi Zhanfeng rose to his feet as he reported, "Father, during your seclusion, I visited the Ink River, Cold Trite, Frost Cloud, and Lone Star Regions, and here are my findings."

Shi Zhanfeng pulled out a jade book as he spoke, and a gray shadow flew out from behind the Devilish Monarch, appearing in front of Shi Zhanfeng in a flash to take the jade book before returning to the Devilish Monarch.

Only now did Han Li notice that an indistinct gray figure had been standing behind the Devilish Monarch this entire time.

His facial features were concealed behind a layer of black qi, and he had an insubstantial body that appeared more like that of a soul than a body of flesh and blood.

"That man's name is Shadow. He is Father's personal guard, and no one knows who he is or what he looks like, but he's extremely powerful," Shi Chuankong explained through voice transmission.

The Devilish Monarch quickly read through the jade book, then nodded as he praised, "Well done. You've done very well in eradicating the bandits in those four regions."

"It was the least that I could do to share some of your burden, Father. Now that you've come out of seclusion, I'd like to offer up a Spatial Origin Herb that I obtained by chance some years ago. I hope it'll be of help to you, Father."

Shi Zhanfeng flipped a hand over as he spoke to summon a white wooden box, then removed the lid to reveal a small plan that was only several inches tall.

The plant was silver in color, and it had nine leaves, all of which were different in color and riddled with silver patterns that were giving off formidable spatial power fluctuations.

Shadow accepted the wooden box in the Devilish Monarch's stead before setting it down in front of him.

The Devilish Monarch's eyes lit up slightly at the Spatial Origin Herb in the box, and he gave a pleased nod before stowing it away.

"A fine offering you've made, Zhanfeng. In return, I'll reward you with three Exquisite Azure Sky Pills, ten suits of Primordial Holy Armor, and ten Dragon Elephant Infernal Swords," the Devilish Monarch declared.

Shadow vanished from the spot in a flash, only to return just a moment later with a white jade platter, which carried three palm-sized crystalline boxes, each of which contained an azure pill, ten suits of white armor, and ten golden longswords.

A faint medicinal fragrance was emanating from the three pills, and the thirty-six profound acupoints that Han Li had opened up thus far all began to stir as he caught a whiff of this aroma.

Chapter 836: Reward

Aside from the three Exquisite Azure Sky Pills, the ten suits of white armor also appeared to be quite remarkable.

At a glance, there didn't seem to be anything special about them, but upon closer inspection, one would discover that these suits of armor were woven out of countless tiny scales, all of which were etched with even tinier runes that were giving off radiant white light.

The golden longswords were also radiating dazzling golden light, within which a projection fo a wyrm and a giant elephant could be seen, prowling around while roaring incessantly.

"Thank you, Father," Shi Zhanfeng said as he accepted the reward with elation.

Everyone was very envious to see this, including Shi Chuankong, and it seemed that Shi Zhanfeng had been given a very handsome reward.

In contrast, Shi Pokong and Shi Jingyan remained quite composed, and it was unclear what they were thinking.

"What is this Exquisite Azure Sky Pill, Fellow Daoist Shi? It is some type of dao pill?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"The Exquisite Azure Sky Pill is not a dao pill. Instead, it's one of the most sought after pills for bodily refinement. Tens of thousands of years ago, my father ventured deep into the Ten Hazards Mountain Range and personally slew a Great Encompassment Stage Azure Devilish Cow, then used its blood essence in conjunction with hundreds of different precious ingredients to refine eighty-one Exquisite Azure Sky Pills over the course of centuries.

“All of my siblings and I were given one pill each, and many more have been given out as rewards since then, so there can't be many left now. As long as one is using a suitable cultivation art, taking a single one of these pills could allow one to open several or even up to twenty profound acupoints," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see. I presume those suits of armor and those swords must also be quite powerful, right?" Han Li mused.

"Indeed. If a normal Golden Immortal Stage Profound Immortal were to be equipped with a suit of Primordial Holy Armor and a Dragon Elephant Infernal Sword, then they would be able to take on a High Zenith cultivator on their own," Shi Chuankong replied, and it was clear that he wasn't very pleased that Shi Zhanfeng had been given such a huge reward.

With this set of armor and swords, Shi Zhanfeng could instantly develop a formidable unit of profound cultivators with overall power that wouldn't be inferior to that of an early-Great Encompassment cultivator.

Shi Zhanfeng quickly returned to his seat after accepting his reward, following which Shi Pokong stood up and stepped forward, then extended a deep bow toward the Devilish Monarch before flipping hand over to produce a jade book.

"I've been overseeing all of the activity across the borders of our realm, and here is a report of all of my findings."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the jade book had already appeared in the Devilish Monarch's hand, delivered to him by Shadow.

The Devilish Monarch quickly read through the book, then nodded as he said, "You did well."

Shi Pokong extended another deep bow, seemingly completely unbothered by the Devilish Monarch's lukewarm reception, then calmly returned to his seat.

"What is Pokong doing?" Shi Chuankong sighed in a frustrated manner. "Father is clearly in a good mood today, so he should be copying Zhanfeng and taking this opportunity to present something to our father!"

Han Li took a glance at Shi Pokong, and the latter looked back at him with a faint smile, seemingly having detected his gaze.

Shi Jingyan rose to her feet to take Shi Pokong's place, then said, "I'm not as capable as Zhanfeng and Pokong. All I've done over the years is manage the Hundred Flower House. This is a piece that took the women of the Hundred Flower House and I a hundred years to embroider, I hope it's to your liking."

She swept a sleeve through the air as she spoke, unfurling a giant picture scroll that was hundreds of feet long and over a hundred feet wide.

The picture scroll depicted an undulating mountain range that stretched as far as the eyes could see, while a giant red sun was riding up in the east.

The craftsmanship was exceptional, and it struck the beholder with the illusion that they were truly standing before a majestic mountain range.

"That's a very thoughtful gift, Jingyan. Shadow, go and fetch that Green Smoke Regal Cauldron for Jingyan," the Devilish Monarch instructed.

Shadow instantly vanished from the spot, then quickly returned with a green cauldron in his hands.

It was an antiquated cauldron that was around half the height of a grown man, and it had nine openings on top, out of which plumes of green smoke were being released before circling around and ultimately seeping back into the cauldron, presenting a profound sight to behold.

"Thank you, Father," Shi Jingyan said with an elated expression, then stowed the cauldron away before returning to her seat.

After that, it was Shi Mingzhen's turn to step forward, and before long, all of the princes and princesses had taken their turn, reporting some official matters before presenting some gifts to the Devilish Monarchs.

All those who presented gifts were given handsome rewards in return, and it didn't take long before it was Shi Chuankong's turn.

"I've been absent from the Holy Realm for many years, and during my absence, the performance of the Vast Origin House has been very inconsistent. For that, I'm willing to accept my punishment," Shi Chuankong said as he presented a small accounts book.

"No punishment is warranted. While it's true that the Vast Origin House's performance has been inconsistent during your absence, the general trend is still a positive one. Now that you've returned, I'm sure things will be back to normal in no time," the Devilish Monarch encouraged.

"Your kindness and generosity are truly unmatched, Father. During my time in the True Immortal Realm, I was able to enter the True Mantra Sect ruins, and I recovered this treasure that I would like to offer to you."

The Virata Lute appeared amid a flash of silver light as he spoke, and he offered it up with both hands.

Everyone in the palace was immediately able to identify the Virata Lute, and all of Shi Chuankong's siblings were also looking at the lute with different expressions.

"The Virata Lute is finally back," the Devilish Monarch murmured as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the lute immediately rose up into the air before returning to his side.

The Devilish Monarch gently stroked the lute as a reminiscent look appeared on his face, and no one in the palace dared to disturb him.

"You've done exceptionally well, Chuankong. I'm very pleased. What would you like as your reward?" the Devilish Monarch asked.

"It was my duty to bring back the Virata Lute, so I don't deserve a reward," Shi Chuankong said.

"I've always rewarded those who make contributions to our Holy Realm. If such a massive contribution from you goes unrewarded, the entire realm is going to point fingers at me," the Devilish Monarch chuckled.

It was clear that the Devilish Monarch was very pleased, and everyone in the hall immediately put on smiles to play along.

Shi Zhanfeng and Shi Jingyan were also smiling, but at the same time, they were looking at Shi Chuankong with wary expressions.

"For recovering such an important treasure, I bestow upon the thirteenth prince the title of Heavenly Merchant Marquis. As for his fiefdom, the Heavenly Rainbow Region currently has no master, so you can have it," the Devilish Monarch declared.

Everyone present fell into a stunned silence upon hearing this, and Han Li was also rather taken aback by this announcement.

Through his readings, he had learned that the Heavenly Rainbow Region was an extremely rich and bountiful region. On top of that, several of the major roads of the Devil Realm also passed through the region, thereby giving it significant geographic importance.

With that in mind, it was no wonder that everyone was so surprised by this decision.

Shi Chuankong hurriedly fell to his knees with a stunned expression as he said, "Thank you for boundless generosity, Father, but I can't accept such a significant reward, so please rescind it."

"I've never rescinded any reward that I've given out. With your business-oriented mind, you're the ideal candidate for making full use of the Heavenly Rainbow Region, so make sure you live up to the high hopes that I have for you," the Devilish Monarch said.

Shi Chuankong could see that the Devilish Monarch wasn't going to change his mind, so he could only accept this arrangement in the end.

"You can return to your seat now," the Devilish Monarch said with a dismissive wave.

"Before that, there's one more thing that I must report," Shi Chuankong hurriedly said.

"Oh? What is it?" the Devilish Monarch asked.

"It was all thanks to Fellow Daoist Li that I was able to recover the Virata Lute from the True Mantra Sect ruins, and on the way back to Night Sun City, we were attacked several times. If it wasn't for Fellow Daoist Li's protection, there's no way I would've been able to make it back alive, so Fellow Daoist Li is much more deserving of a reward than I am," Shi Chuankong said.

The Devilish Monarch turned to Han Li upon hearing this, and Han Li rose to his feet.

Even though he had become the center of attention for everyone in the palace, he remained calm and collected.

"Li Feiyu, you may not be from our Holy Realm, but seeing as you've made such a significant contribution to our realm, your efforts cannot go unrewarded. What would you like?" the Devilish Monarch asked.

"Fellow Daoist Shi and I are close friends, so I shouldn't be asking for a reward here, but at the moment, I'm facing a problem that I can't resolve myself, so I can only turn to you, Senior," Han Li said.

"What is this problem of yours?" the Devilish Monarch asked.

"A good friend of mine suffered severe spiritual damage some time ago under some rather inexplicable circumstances, and her true form is that of a Xing Beast. At the moment, her essential energy is constantly seeping away, and I haven't been able to treat her condition through conventional means, so I would like your permission to have the grand priest inspect her condition," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I see. That's not a problem. Zhanfeng, summon the grand priest and have him fulfill Li Feiyu's request," the Devilish Monarch instructed.

"The grand priest went into seclusion ten years ago. Would it be possible to wait until he comes out of seclusion before he fulfills Fellow Daoist Li's request?" Shi Zhanfeng asked as he gave Han Li an apologetic look.

Han Li wasn't surprised at all to hear this, and he said, "I can wait for the grand priest to come out of seclusion. How long will that take?"

"That's difficult to say. After all, seclusions can be long or short, and it could take anywhere from a few years to over a century. However, you can rest assured that I'll have the grand priest come to you as soon as he comes out of seclusion," Shi Zhanfeng promised.

Chapter 837: Blatant

"Zhanfeng, the Priestly Temple is currently under your supervision, how could you not know when the grand priest is going to come out of seclusion?" Shi Chuankong harrumphed coldly.

"Your accusations are misguided, Chuankong. The Priestly Temple is indeed currently under my supervision, but the grand priest holds a very lofty position, so he's not under my control. As such, I truly cannot tell you when he'll be coming out of seclusion. If you don't believe me, then you can ask Priest Qing Yang," Shi Zhanfeng said in a resigned manner.

As soon as his voice trailed off, an elderly priest immediately stood up. The priest was very thin, and his hair and beard were all giving off a faint azure gleam, perhaps a result of some cultivation art that he was using.

Priest Qing Yang extended a deep bow toward the Devilish Monarch, then turned to Shi Chuankong as he said, "Your Highness, the grand priest really is in seclusion right now. Otherwise, he wouldn't be absent today. The grand priest never tells us when he plans to go into seclusion and come out of seclusion, so there's no way for us to know."

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

He still had his suspicions, but it would be inappropriate for him to force the issue any further.

"In that case, we'll just have to wait until the grand priest comes out of seclusion before fulfilling Fellow Daoist Li's request," the Devilish Monarch said.

"I don't wish to be a pain, but the problem is that my friend's condition is currently only being stabilized using Purple Sun Warm Jade, and I only have enough Purple Sun Warm Jade to last about two or three more decades, so I can't afford to wait much longer," Han Li sighed.

Shi Pokong had promised to acquire some mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade for him, yet he had only managed to secure a small piece thus far.

"I just so happen to have some Purple Sun Warm Jade, and it's all of the mid-grade variety. I'm happy to gift them to Fellow Daoist Li as thanks for what he's done for Chuankong and our Holy Realm," Shi Zhanfeng said with a smile, then summoned a storage ring before offering to Han Li.

Han Li exchanged a glance with Shi Chuankong, then accepted the storage ring, and his eyes lit up ever so slightly after inspecting the ring's contents.

There were seven or eight pieces of mid-grade Purple Sun Warm Jade, all of which were of an extremely high quality.

A subtle hint of displeasure flashed through Shi Pokong's eyes upon seeing this.

"Thank you, Your Highness. This batch of Purple Sun Warm Jade should be enough to last about a century, but after that, I'll still have to trouble the grand priest," Han Li said.

"You can rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Zhanfeng assured with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response, and a faint smile appeared on the Devilish Monarch's face upon seeing this.

Right as he was about to dismiss everyone, Shi Pokong stepped forward as he said, "Please wait a moment, Father."

"What is it?" the Devilish Monarch asked.

"Chuankong just mentioned that he was attacked on the way back to Night Sun City, and he spoke to me about this as well. Regarding the people who attacked him..."

"I've already heard of this matter, and I've sent people to investigate," the Devilish Monarch suddenly interjected to cut Shi Pokong off.

Shi Pokong faltered slightly upon hearing this, while an indignant look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face, yet before he had a chance to protest, Shi Pokong grabbed onto his sleeve and said, "In that case, I'll leave this matter in your capable hands, Father."

The Devilish Monarch's expression eased slightly as he said, "There's no need for you to pursue this matter any further, just focus on what you need to do."

"Yes, Father," Shi Pokong replied.

Shi Chuankong was still feeling quite disgruntled, but he also gave an affirmative response.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, but he continued to observe in silence.

"Alright, you can all go now," the Devilish Monarch said with a dismissive wave, and everyone promptly departed.

The ceremony continued, and more and more people entered the palace to offer up reports and presents.

The ceremony wore on until the afternoon before drawing to a conclusion, and in the wake of everyone's departure, only the Devilish Monarch and Shadow were left in the palace.

"Shadow, do you also feel like that Li Feiyu bears a striking resemblance to that man?" the Devilish Monarch asked with a contemplative expression.

Shadow offered no response.

The Devilish Monarch didn't seem to actually want to hear Shadow's opinion on the matter, and he abruptly vanished from the spot, followed immediately by Shadow.

Outside the palace, Shi Zhanfeng caught up to Shi Chuankong's group, then said with a smile, "Congratulations on your official title and your new fiefdom, Chuankong. I'm truly happy for you."

Everyone else hurriedly departed upon seeing this, seemingly terrified of hearing something that they shouldn't, but Shi Jingyan and Shi Mingzhen also approached Shi Chuankong's group to join the conversation.

"You're far too kind, Zhanfeng. The reward that Father has given to me can't compare with the pills, armor, and swords that were given to you," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Honestly, if Father isn't against the idea, I would be more than happy to exchange rewards with you," Shi Zhanfeng chuckled.

Shi Chuankong offered no response to this.

"Fellow Daoist Li, you may not be from our Holy Realm, but you've made significant contributions to our realm, and I think that's very admirable. How about you pay me a visit in my manor if you have some spare time?" Shi Zhanfeng invited as he turned to Han Li with a smile.

Han Li cupped his fist in a salute, but offered no definitive response.

Shi Zhanfeng also cupped his fist in a parting salute to everyone, and in the next instant, he abruptly vanished from the spot along with Shi Chuanjia and Shi Bofu, only to reappear in the distance a moment later.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

Shi Zhanfeng's teleportation ability had been unleashed without any warning, and only now did Han Li detect some faint spatial fluctuations in the air.

It was clear that Shi Zhanfeng's mastery over the laws of space far exceeded Shi Chuankong's.

"It looks like Zhanfeng's Bright Mirror has become even more refined," Shi Pokong remarked with a smile, while Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly as a grim look appeared on his face.

"It looks like you had a very eventful and fruitful trip to the True Immortal Realm, Chuankong. I've always wanted to visit the True Immortal Realm as well, but I can never find the time with all of my official duties," Shi Jingyang said with a wide smile.

Shi Chuankong merely nodded in response with a slightly cold look in his eyes.

Shi Jingyan remained completely unbothered, and she suddenly began to approach Han Li, who immediately became apprehensive.

A peculiar, alluring fragrance wafted toward him, striking him with a sense of intoxication.

Even when the distance between them had been reduced to no more than three feet, Shi Jingyan still continued to approach Han Li, and there seemed to be some type of attractive force in her eyes that was attempting to suck in Han Li's soul.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a step backward and asked, "Can I help you with something, Your Highness?"

"I just wanted to take a closer look at the man who was able to kill Hua Jing and Daoist Master Bone Shine," Shi Jingyan replied with a smile as she finally stopped in her tracks.

Han Li offered no response to this.

All of a sudden, the fragrance emanating from Shi Jingyan's body became significantly more pronounced, and it was converging from all directions.

Han Li had already noticed that there was something strange about this aroma, so he was holding his breath and had shut off all of his immortal acupoints, and in this instant, he was even channeling his time law powers to ward off the fragrance.

However, the fragrance was able to instantly seep through the layer of time law powers around his body, and he instantly felt as if he were laying in a floral garden.

Not only was this fragrance infiltrating his body, it was also seeping into his soul, and all of a sudden, all of the apprehension in his heart had completely melted away, only to be replaced by a sense of yearning.

It was as if Shi Jingyan had become the woman of his dreams, and he was willing to lay down his own life for her at a moment's notice.

However, immediately thereafter, his tremendous spiritual sense began to circulate on its own, and an enormous Spiritual Sense Sword appeared, releasing an incredibly sharp aura that easily tore the fragrance in his mind to shreds.

At the same time, a hint of green light appeared within his sleeve, and all of the fragrance that had infiltrated his body instantly surged into the green light.

A hint of surprise flashed through Shi Jingyan's eyes upon seeing this, while Shi Pokong warned, "Jingyan, we're in the Holy Imperial Palace right now, so do try to keep yourself in check."

"I was just extending a greeting to Fellow Daoist Li, isn't that right?" Shi Jingyan asked with a mischievious grin as all of the fragrance around her faded away.

"That was definitely quite the greeting," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"You're a remarkable man, Fellow Daoist Li. If you ever feel like, you can come and visit me as well. I would love to hear more about the True Immortal Realm from you," Shi Jingyan said before departing, quickly followed by Shi Mingzhen.

"Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Li? Jingyan's Heavenly Dream Fragrance can be a real pain to deal with," Shi Pokong said.

"I'm fine, thank you for asking, Your Highness," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Good. Let's go back as well," Shi Pokong said, and the four of them set off back to his manor.

Chapter 838: Physical Transmigration

It didn't take long for Han Li and the others to return to Shi Pokong's manor, and after emerging from their carriages, Xue Cheng promptly departed, while Shi Chuankong gestured for Han Li to follow him and Shi Pokong into a conference hall.

"I don't understand what Father is thinking! Why didn't he allow us to reveal the truth about the attacks that I had to endure on the way back? Zhanfeng and Jingyan need to be exposed for the backstabbing scoundrels that they are!" Shi Chuankong grumbled in frustration.

"Father most likely didn't want others to know about the extent of the infighting among us siblings, and at the same time, he gave you a huge reward as compensation. Having said that, I certainly didn't expect him to grant you the Heavenly Rainbow Region," Shi Pokong said.

"That's true. With the Heavenly Rainbow Region in our grasp, we're in a far more advantageous position than before. Given enough time, I'm confident that we can surpass Zhanfeng and the others," Shi Chuankong said with a smile as he sat down onto a chair, then invited Han Li to sit down beside him.

Some servants of the manor had just brought in some cups of spirit tea, and Shi Pokong took a sip of his tea, then cautioned, "Don't celebrate just yet. You're going to attract a lot of envy from our brothers and sisters now that you've been granted the Heavenly Rainbow Region, so you have to be extra careful from now on."

"Don't worry, Pokong. I'm a High Zenith cultivator now, so they won't just be able to step all over me as they please. If they dare to come after me, then I'll make sure they pay the price. Besides, I still have you, don't I?" Shi Chuankong replied in a nonchalant manner.

"That may be true, but you can never be too careful. By the way, please be patient in the matter regarding the grand priest, Fellow Daoist Li. Feel free to use the Purple Sun Warm Jade given to you by Zhanfeng, and I'll send out more people to gather some more Purple Sun Warm Jade for you," Shi Pokong said.

"Thank you, Your Highness," Han Li replied.

This was the first time that he had spoken after entering the conference hall, and the cup of spirit tea beside him had remained untouched this entire time.

"Zhanfeng's response today doesn't really come as a surprise at all. However, even if he wants to delay things, he wouldn't dare to blatantly ignore Father's orders. Even so, it looks like you'll have to stay in Night Sun City for a while longer, but rest assured, Pokong and I will continue to try and find ways to treat Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul's condition," Shi Chuankong said in an apologetic manner.

"In that case, I'll be in your care for a while longer. I'm sure the two of you still have some things to discuss, and I have some matters to take care of too, so I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

"Don't be in such a hurry to leave, Fellow Daoist Li, I still have to speak to you about the Heavenly Rainbow Region!" Shi Chuankong called out.

"I don't know much about the Holy Realm at all, so I'll leave it to His Highness to offer you counsel on this matter. Of course, if you require my assistance with anything, I'll be happy to help," Han Li said.

"Don't keep Fellow Daoist Li any longer. Now that he's gotten some Purple Sun Warm Jade from Zhanfeng, he must be in a hurry to get back to Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul," Shi Pokong said with a smile.

"Alright, in that case, you can attend to Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul first, and I'll go find you after you're done," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li gave the two a nod, then departed from the hall.

Upon returning to the Long Garden Pavilion, he activated all of the restrictions, then paid Weeping Soul a visit in the Flower Branch Space before returning to his secret chamber.

The delay naturally wasn't ideal, but thankfully, he had secured some Purple Sun Warm Jade, so at the very least, Weeping Soul would be fine for the next century or so.

With that in mind, Han Li commenced his cultivation.

One night, over ten years later.

The entire secret chamber was filled with radiant golden light, and Han Li was seated with his eyes tightly shut, making a rapid string of hand seals while trembling uncontrollably.

The Mantra Treasured Axis was hovering behind him, revolving incessantly while releasing rays of golden light. To his left was the Clear Time Vial, which was also giving off golden ripple, while to his right was an hourglass formed by flowing sand, within which particles of golden sand were swirling like a miniature sandstorm.

In front of the left side of his chest was a torch that had been lit with Time Severing Flowing Fire, while to its right was a lush and vibrant golden tree that was slowly taking shape under the rays of golden light.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes sprang open, and he brought his palms together in one swift motion.

Immediately thereafter, all of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis, the Clear Time Vial, the Time Severing Torch, and the Illusory Dawn Hourglass lit up, releasing bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations.

Several seconds later, the small golden tree completely took shape, and all of the time law power in the room converged toward it, manifesting a series of Time Dao Runes on its surface.

The pained look on Han Li's face was immediately eased, and he exhaled as a faint smile appeared on his face.

After cultivating diligently for over ten years, he had finally manifested an Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

Up to this point, he had finally reached the third level of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Han Li carefully sensed the time law powers flowing through the air around him, and it was as if he had entered a fully immersive state. Even without counting, he knew that there were currently 720 Time Dao Runes flashing on his Mantra Treasured Axis, while his Clear Time Vial had 360 Time Dao Runes on its surface.

The Time Severing Torch and the Illusory Dawn Hourglass each had 180 Time Dao Runes, while more and more Time Dao Runes were continuing to appear on the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree that had just been manifested.

Right at this moment, forty-five time law threads flew out of the Mantra Treasured Axis and all of the other time-attribute artifacts, then began to swirl around Han Li.

The time law threads then linked up with one another to form a golden circle that revolved incessantly around Han Li, absorbing the surrounding time law powers while slowly shrinking toward the center.

At the same time, the five time-attribute artifacts released five bursts of time law powers that converged in unison before surging into the golden circle, transforming it into a giant golden ring.

A flurry of Time Dao Runes flew out of the time-attribute artifacts before falling upon the golden ring, and it immediately began trembling incessantly while emitting a sharp ringing sound.

At the same time, bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations swept through the surrounding area, threatening to overwhelm all of the restrictions in the room.

Right at this moment, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he murmured to himself, "Is it coming again?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a ball of azure light instantly shot out of the front of his robes, and it contained none other than the Heaven Controlling Vial.

The vial was glowing as radiantly as a green sun, and it was giving off a burst of tremendous suction force.

The golden ring immediately flew high up into the air, then rapidly shrank down to the same size as the mouth of the Heaven Controlling Vial before the two came together to release a burst of immense time law powers.

The Heaven Controlling Vial instantly swelled rapidly in size, while countless green runes emerged within it, forming a green cloud that was swirling incessantly.

Tremendous time law power fluctuations surged out of the green cloud, causing the nearby space to tremble and ripple incessantly.

Immediately thereafter, the green cloud within the vial abruptly brightened, then shot out of the vial as a thick pillar of green light before vanishing into the space up ahead.

The space was torn apart, and countless rays of translucent light surged forth to form that familiar translucent wall of light.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out in Han Li's mind.

"You've been progressing faster than I expected..."

Han Li immediately turned to the Heaven Controlling Vial with a bewildered expression, and sure enough, a pair of tiny black eyes had appeared on its surface and were looking directly at him.

Han Li wanted to communicate with the vial through their spiritual connection, but it was as if there were an invisible wall between them, thwarting his attempts at communicating with what appeared to be the vial spirit.

Before he had a chance to do anything, the translucent wall of light began to glow radiantly, and an enormous vortex appeared, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that quickly inundated his entire body.

By the time he returned to his senses, he was greeted by the sight of a barren plain.

There was an enormous river flowing from the ends of the heavens on the distant horizon. The river stretched as far as the eyes could see in both directions, and it contained countless balls of light.

The river appeared to be flowing rapidly, flowing slowly, and not flowing at all, all at the same time, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

Han Li had witnessed this river in the past, but he still couldn't help but be amazed by what he saw. Right as he was about to fly toward the river, he suddenly seemed to have sensed something, and his expression changed drastically as he hurriedly looked down at his own body, only to find that he was present in his physical form, rather than a spiritual one.

He shook his head from side to side, then pressed a hand against his own cheek, and he was able to confirm that this wasn't an illusion, which meant that his physical body had been sucked into the vortex along with his soul!

Chapter 839: Mystery Unraveled

Only after looking around in bewilderment for some time did Han Li gradually compose himself before slowly flying toward the river.

Even though he had already been here on several occasions, this was the first time that he had been here in his physical form, so it was still a unique experience.

Hovering high up in the air, Han Li peered into the river, and thanks to his prior experience, he knew not to focus his gaze on any single one of the balls of light. Instead, he only took brief glances at the images flashing through them.

Right at this moment, a large ball of light passed by beneath Han Li, moving significantly slower than the other balls of light.

As soon as Han Li caught sight of the image displayed on it, his attention was immediately drawn to it.

However, as soon as he gave the ball of light his undivided attention, it immediately released a burst of immense suction force that sucked him in without giving him any chance to resist.

……

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li's eyes sprang open, and he found himself laying on top of a black rock above a turbulent sea. Waves were constantly crashing into the rock around him, splashing water in all directions.

Han Li sat up on the rock, then inspected his surroundings to discover that the seawater around him was of a very dark and foreboding color.

His ears were ringing slightly, while his breathing was also a little heavy, and he was struck by an inexplicable sense of discomfort.

Nothing appeared to be amiss in the area around him, but he couldn't help but feel as if something was different, and this sense of discomfort was only slowly compounding with each breath that he took, but only by a minute degree.

Under normal circumstances, perhaps he would've also detected this slight change, but he wouldn't have paid it much heed. However, given the special nature of the circumstances at hand, he had to be extra careful.

He strode over to the edge of the rock, then peered into the water, and the reflection looking back at him was one of his own face.

Sure enough, he had experienced physical transmigration on this occasion!

Han Li exhaled as he sat back down onto the ground, and he didn't know if this was a good thing or a bad thing.

He habitually took a glance upward to discover that the usual Mantra Treasured Axis projection was nowhere to be seen. Instead, there was an indistinct golden ring above his head that was riddled with Time Dao Runes.

After a brief count, Han Li discovered that there were 1,620 Time Dao Runes, which appeared to be the total number of Time Dao Runes on all five time-attribute artifacts combined.

It seemed that the duration of this transmigration was still going to depend on the rate of expenditure of his time law powers.

Right at this moment, he spotted half of a giant black carcass floating on the surface not far behind the rock. The carcass was already a little decomposed, and it was giving off a foul odor.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he rose up into the air for a closer look, upon which he discovered that it was a chunk of a black whale's body, and it looked a little familiar.

At the same time, he suddenly recalled the scene that he had witnessed in the ball of light. To put it more accurately, he recalled the person that he had seen within it.

All of a sudden, a theory began to take shape in his mind. Could it be that the strange state that Daoist Master Bone Shine was in during their second encounter was the result of this transmigration?

The more he pondered this theory, the more plausible it seemed in his mind, and thus, he rose to his feet again.

After inspecting his own internal condition to ensure that nothing was amiss, Han Li closed his eyes, then released his spiritual sense in all directions.

Moments later, he reopened his eyes, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "I guess there's only one way to find out."

Immediately thereafter, he put on a Reincarnation Palace mask, then sped away in a certain direction.

……

Tens of thousands of kilometers away, a dark green figure was seated on the surface of the water, bobbing up and down like a floating lilypad.

It was a very thin elderly man wearing a loose-fitting dark green Daoist robe, and it was none other than Daoist Master Bone Shine!

At this moment, there was a fist-sized purple bead hovering above his head, and it was giving off bursts of purple smoke and hazy purple light that encompassed his entire head.

The purple bead was an immortal treasure that was beneficial to the soul, but it was only a ninth-grade immortal treasure.

Under normal circumstances, Daoist Master Bone Shine would never use this immortal treasure, but he had no choice in the matter here.

While hunting down the two perpetrators who had killed his disciple, he had been caught off guard and suffered severe spiritual damage from an attack unleashed by that High Zenith cultivator, and he had taken several restorative pills without much effect.

Left with no options, he was forced to use this immortal treasure that wasn't actually meant for restorative purposes.

"Once I get my hands on those scoundrels, I'll make them wish they were never born!" Daoist Master Bone Shine spat through gritted teeth.

Right as his voice trailed off, a streak of light flew over from afar, then drew to an abrupt halt around a thousand feet away, revealing a familiar figure.

Daoist Master Bone Shine hurriedly sprang to his feet in a panic as he exclaimed, "You again?"

I knew it!

Up to this point, Han Li's theory had been confirmed. He had indeed returned here through transmigration to battle Daoist Master Bone Shine again.

During what Han Li had thought to be their second encounter, he was wondering how Daoist Master Bone Shine had suffered such severe additional spiritual damage, and the answer was now clear.

A grim look appeared on Daoist Master Bone Shine's face at the sight of Han Li's triumphant expression, and a sense of unease welled up in his heart, but he couldn't pinpoint where this sense of unease was coming from.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Daoist Master Bone Shine harrumphed coldly, "You dare to come after me on your own? You must have a death wish!"

"You still haven't recovered from the spiritual damage from last time, have you?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"So what? There's no way that you could unleash that same secret technique a second time in such a short span!" Daoist Master Bone Shine countered, but internally, he was not without doubts.

"That secret technique was extremely taxing on my spiritual sense, so it's indeed not something that I can recover from in a short time, but how are you so sure that I don't have any other tricks up my sleeve?" Han Li asked with a mocking sneer.

For some reason, the unease in Daoist Master Bone Shine's heart grew even more pronounced.

However, he then quickly dismissed his own concerns. How could a single early-High Zenith cultivator possibly pose a threat to himself?

"What a load of bullshit!" Daoist Master Bone Shine harrumphed coldly as he swept a a sleeve through the air, instantly conjuring up his bone withering spirit domain.

A thin cloud of mist spread through the surrounding area, and the eight bone pagodas appeared once again.

As Daoist Master Bone Shine channeled his spiritual sense, he could feel a sharp pain in his consciousness, and the circulation of his spiritual sense and devilish qi were also rather sluggish.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he remained unfazed as he flipped a hand over to summon a strange-looking glass lamp.

"That's the Soul Devouring Lamp! Why do you have it?" Daoist Master Bone Shine exclaimed.

"So you recognize this lamp as well, but do you have a way to ward off its powers?" Han Li asked.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, sending the lamp flying toward Daoist Master Bone Shine, who immediately summoned a purplish-golden talisman without any hesitation before pressing it to his own forehead.

The talisman instantly lit up in flames before being incinerated into nothingness, leaving a complex purplish-golden rune at the center of Daoist Master Bone Shine's glabella.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he began making a rapid string of incantation seals.

As the Soul Devouring Lamp approached Daoist Master Bone Shine, its wick suddenly lit up with two flames, one purple and one azure, both of which were intertwined with each other like a pair of miniature fiery snakes.

The purple and azure flames weren't particularly bright. Instead, they were quite dim, but Daoist Master Bone Shine's gaze was involuntarily drawn to them, following which a slightly dazed look appeared in his eyes.

He felt as if he could see two exceptionally beautiful young women dancing within the lamp, seductively flaunting their gorgeous bodies, and it didn't take long before they captured the entirety of his attention.

Chapter 840: Second Battle Against Daoist Master Bone Shine

At this moment, a projection of a giant lamp was taking shape in Daoist Master Bone Shine's consciousness, and the four beasts below the lamp opened their mouths in unison while green light flashed through their eyes.

Daoist Master Bone Shine's soul had already been quite severely damaged to begin, and he immediately felt his own consciousness begin to churn violently once again.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, summoning an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword before sending it flying toward Daoist Master Bone Shine right as he stood transfixed by the lamp.

A burst of bright golden lightning erupted out of the sword, then whipped through the air before crashing down upon Daoist Master Bone Shine, scorching the air in its wake, yet right as it was about to strike Daoist Master Bone Shine, the rune on his glabella began to glow radiantly with golden light.

At the same time, a formidable shockwave swept through his consciousness, sweeping toward the giant oil lamp projection.

The projection remained completely unmoved by the shockwave, not displaying signs of strain of struggle, but immediately thereafter, the shockwave abruptly froze solid, and the oil lamp projection was also encased in a layer of ice.

All of this had transpired in the same instant that the rune on Daoist Master Bone Shine's glabella had lit up, and Han Li immediately detected that something was amiss.

He channeled his Reversal True Axis ability without any hesitation, then flew back in retreat right in front of Daoist Master Bone Shine.

Right at this moment, a sharp, white bone spike abruptly pierced its way out of Daoist Master Bone Shine's chest, and on the tip of the spike was what appeared to be a white water droplet.

Han Li was hovering high up in the air, and a hint of lingering fear flashed through his eyes at the sight of the water droplet.

This was a water droplet formed entirely by Daoist Master Bone Shine's law powers, and if Han Li hadn't reacted in time and been struck by the water droplet, then he would've at least suffered extremely severe injuries, if not been killed on the spot.

Even though he was currently in a state of transmigration, this was still his body, and he had no idea what would happen if he were to sustain injuries or even die in this state.

Han Li took a glance at the golden ring above his head to find that over a hundred Time Dao Runes had already faded, which was a rate that was a little slower than his past transmigrations.

However, this wasn't the time to be pondering such matters, and he immediately turned his gaze back to Daoist Master Bone Shine.

At this point, Daoist Master Bone Shine had already awakened from the effects of the Soul Devouring Lamp, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which one of the bone pagodas in his spirit domain split up on its own to surround the lamp, instantly severing Han Li's spiritual connection with it.

"This Soul Devouring Lamp is even more formidable in your hands than it was in the hands of those sisters, but now that it's been sealed, let's see what other tricks you have to offer!" Daoist Master Bone Shine spat through gritted teeth.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a vicious look suddenly flashed through his eyes, and Han Li immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis to dart away again upon seeing this.

In the next instant, another bone pagoda came crashing down upon him without any warning, and Han Li had only just gotten out of the way when a third bone pagoda appeared in his path, and both of them were burning with green flames.

The seven bone pagodas were flashing through the spirit domain in pursuit of Han Li, slowly driving him into a corner.

At the same time, the initial sense of discomfort that Han Li had experienced had finally compounded to a point where he felt as if it were close to reaching a breaking point.

He had transmigrated to a time and space that he didn't belong in, and the entire world seemed to be rejecting him.

With that in mind, Han Li knew that he couldn't afford to delay any longer, and he made a hand seal to summon eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, all of which began circling around him with golden lightning flashing over them.

All of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been refined in the golden Baleful Lightning Pond back in the Gray Realm, and that seemed to have triggered some type of change within them.

Not only had his spiritual connection with them become more intimate, their spiritual nature had also been significantly enhanced.

The eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords lit up in unison at Han Li's behest, releasing a burst of tremendous sword qi and a wave of golden lightning that erupted through the air in all directions.

A giant ball of golden light was swelling rapidly with Han Li at its center, and all of the green flames in Han Li's path were immediately forced back into their respective bone pagodas.

Right at this moment, a faint sound rang out nearby, and Han Li immediately swiveled around to discover that the strange bone spike protruding out of Daoist Master Bone Shine's chest was darting toward him from behind at an extraordinary speed and an angle that made it very difficult to ward off.

The white water droplet remained adhered firmly to the tip of the bone spike, and it was also rapidly approaching Han Li.

At this point, it was already too late to channel his Reversal True Axis ability, so Han Li could only summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

A beam of dark green light shot out of the mouth of the gourd before instantly clashing against the white water droplet, and a burst of destructive law powers instantly erupted out of the beam of green light.

However, the white water droplet was only stopped in its tracks for a split second before continuing to hurtle directly toward Han Li's chest, but this split second was enough for Han Li to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Ripples of golden light surged out of the Mantra Treasured Axis, slowing down the flow of time in the surrounding area, and the white water droplet was instantly slowed down significantly.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Han Li slashed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword through the air, unleashing a violent torrent of lightning that struck the white water droplet with tremendous power.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as arcs of golden lightning erupted in all directions, and the white water droplet exploded before dissipating into a cloud of a mist, while the white bone spike was trembling violently as it flew back through the air.

Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis upon seeing this, then flew after the white bone spike as he aimed the tip of his Profound Heavenly Gourd directly at it.

A green vortex instantly emerged from the mouth of the gourd, releasing a burst of immense suction force that drew the white bone spike into the gourd in a flash.

A cold look flashed through Daoist Master Bone Shine's eyes upon seeing this, and he quickly made a hand seal, upon which the entire bone withering spirit domain shuddered violently.

At the same time, the green flames burning over the eight bone pagodas were snuffed out one after another until only the flames in the eight giant skulls on top of the pagodas were still lit.

As a result, the light in the spirit domain had become quite dim, and Han Li could sense that the surrounding environment was undergoing some subtle changes.

"It's truly very impressive for a mere early-High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal to press me to this extent, but unfortunately for you, such a massive disparity in cultivation base cannot be bridged by your spiritual secret techniques alone," Daoist Master Bone Shine said as he began to approach Han Li.

"I beg to differ. I still haven't used all of my spiritual secret techniques yet, so how do you know they're not enough to bridge the gap between us?" Han Li countered with a composed smile on his face.

Daoist Master Bone Shine hesitated involuntarily upon hearing this, clearly still a little apprehensive of Han Li's spiritual attacks.

"Your Soul Devouring Lamp has already been sealed, and there's no way you can use that spiritual sense sword ability again in such a short time, so you're clearly bluffing," Daoist Master Bone Shine harrumphed coldly.

"Is that so? Why don't you come and find out?" Han Li goaded.

"Fine, I will," Daoist Master Bone Shine chuckled coldly, and as soon as his voice trailed off, his body instantly began to swell drastically in size.

His robes were torn to shreds as a series of jagged bone spikes protruded out of his body, and in the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a giant skeletal devil.

At the same time, his aura had been drastically elevated to an incredibly fearsome level.

The entire bone withering spirit domain seemed to have also been affected by his transformation, and the light within it became extremely dim, while the pressure on Han Li was compounded by severalfold.

In the wake of his transformation, Daoist Master Bone Shine's eyes had already turned a crimson color, but the golden rune on his glabella still remained, and he let loose a thunderous roar before bounding straight at Han Li.

All of the space in his wake shuddered violently, as if it were being compressed by his immense power, and the golden ripples released by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis were also forced back alongside the compacted space, rendering them unable to impede Daoist Master Bone Shine's movements.

The giant skeletal devil raised an enormous hand, then swung it down upon Han Li's head, and its finger resembled five bone scythes that tore through the space up ahead, threatening to tear Han Li to pieces.

Chapter 841: Just in the Nick of Time

All of a sudden, Han Li swept both sleeves through the air, sending five Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flying toward the oncoming giant hand, while he rushed back in retreat.

Five sharp clangs rang out in rapid succession, and the five Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were sent flying back before tumbling into the sea down below after clashing against the giant skeletal devil's hand.

At this point, Han Li had only just retreated to several thousand feet away, and before he had a chance to recover his flying swords, a gust of howling wind abruptly swept through the air behind him.

The giant skulls on top of the eight bone pagodas had all opened their mouths up wide to release thick bone chains that were hurtling directly toward him like eight white bone spears.

Han Li was just about to channel his Reversal True Axis to take evasive measures when he suddenly discovered that his arms had been completely immobilized by his sides, rendering him unable to make any hand seals.

Only then did he notice that an exoskeleton of white bone had appeared over his arms, enveloping his elbow joints, and it was spread like creeping frost toward his hands and his shoulders.

Was it that drop of white liquid? Han Li thought to himself with a bewildered expression.

His brows furrowed tightly as he stomped both feet heavily down onto the space beneath him, launching himself upward, and at the same time, countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of his body to strike the spreading exoskeleton.

However, after the golden lightning faded, not only had the exoskeleton not been broken, it had spread to cover an even larger area on his body.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, the eight bone chains had already wrapped themselves around his arms and legs, immobilizing him in mid-air.

Han Li could feel the chains pulling him apart with tremendous power, causing all of his joints to creak and groan. If the average Jade Immortal had been in his place, they would've most likely already been pulled apart at the seams.

At the same time, jets of green flames erupted out of the eye sockets of the eight skulls on the bone pagodas, and they surged along the bone chains before inundating Han Li's entire body.

The green flames weren't giving off any heat. Instead, it was merely slightly cool to the touch, but in the instant that it came into contact with Han Li's body, an alarmed look instantly appeared on his face.

The green flames weren't harming his body or his soul, but they were directly incinerating his bones.

After just a few seconds, Han Li began to feel a numb sensation in his bones, as if they were being gnawed on by countless tiny bugs, making them frail and brittle.

After reaching the High Zenith Stage, Han Li's skeleton had become extremely resilient, but it stood no chance against Daoist Master Bone Shine's bone withering law powers.

Right at this moment, a burst of silver light flashed over his body, following which a layer of scorching silver flames erupted forth like a fiery silver cloak, forcing back the invasive green flames.

After completely refining the three balls of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, the Essence Fire Raven's silver flames had become far more formidable than before, and the green flames were quickly overwhelmed and forced back into retreat.

However, the Essence Fire Raven refused to let the green flames off the hook, and it sped along the bone chains in pursuit, determined to devour every last ounce of the green flames.

Daoist Master Bone Shine only took a single glance at the Essence Fire Raven before his gaze returned to Han Li.

This High Zenith Stage human seemed to have an endless bag of tricks, and if this battle were to drag on any longer, there was no telling what other tricks he could pull out.

With that in mind, Daoist Master Bone Shine raised a hand before plunging it directly toward Han Li.

At this point, Han Li's arms and his entire abdomen had been encased in that layer of white exoskeleton, and on top of that, he was also bound by the eight bone chains, so it was impossible for him to take any evasive measures.

However, as Daoist Master Bone Shine's gaze fell upon Han Li's face, he discovered that Han Li was looking completely calm and collected, displaying no panic or fear at all.

Something's not right...

A sense of foreboding welled up in Daoist Master Bone Shine's heart, yet before he had a chance to retreat, a familiar cold gleam suddenly flashed through Han Li's eyes.

"Impossible!" Daoist Master Bone Shine exclaimed with an alarmed expression.

A semi-transparent sword that was only around an inch in length had shot out of Han Li's glabella, and it instantly pierced through Daoist Master Bone Shine's hand before hurtling directly toward his glabella.

A faint crack rang out, and in the next instant, the golden rune on his glabella disintegrated into specks of golden light, following which an enormous translucent sword appeared in his consciousness before swinging down with tremendous power.

The runes on the surface of the sword were flashing incessantly, giving off immense spiritual sense fluctuations that caused Daoist Master Bone Shine's consciousness to churn and tremble violently, as if it could split apart at any moment.

At the same time, his spiritual sense was rapidly dissipating like snow under the scorching sun.

His soul was already severely wounded, and it was trembling violently in the face of the powerful shockwaves, barely able to hold itself together.

Daoist Master Bone Shine let loose an indignant roar of fury, but his spiritual sense was still rapidly fading, and his vision was gradually becoming blurry.

His giant skeletal body began to shrink, and he quickly reverted back to his human form.

At the same time, the green flames on the eight bone pagodas gradually began to wane, and the bone chains protruding out of the mouths of the skulls on top of the eight bone pagodas were also quickly retracted.

With no more green flames to devour, the Essence Fire Raven circled around in the air, then flew back to Han Li.

Upon noticing the hard exoskeleton immobilizing Han Li's arms and abdomen, it transformed into a silver fireball that crashed straight into Han Li's chest, then spread itself over the exoskeleton to incinerate it with all its might.

Right at this moment, a near-animalistic roar rang out.

At this point, Daoist Master Bone Shine's eyes were completely bloodshot, and there was a deranged look on his face as he slammed a palm heavily onto his own glabella.

Inside his consciousness, a giant palm projection descended out of the heavens before slamming into the Spiritual Sense Sword with tremendous power.

The sword shuddered violently, and the translucent light radiating from it rapidly faded away, following which it vanished from within Daoist Master Bone Shine's consciousness.

In the next instant, a tiny translucent sword shot out of the back of his head, then circled around in the air before flying back to Han Li and vanishing into his glabella.

After striking himself on the forehead, Daoist Master Bone Shine was able to dispel the crisis of the Spiritual Sense Sword, but his injuries were further exacerbated as a result, and he involuntarily flew back through the air.

His hair had become extremely disheveled, and his eyes had almost turned completely dull, giving him the appearance of a lost and panicked old man who stumbled away before fleeing as a streak of light.

Following Daoist Master Bone Shine's departure, his bone withering spirit domain faded away along with the eight bone pagodas.

Meanwhile, as soon as the miniature sword flew back into Han Li's consciousness, his head immediately shot back as if he had been dealt a heavy blow, and his spiritual sense had also been severely overexerted. He was only just barely able to recover all of his treasures before his body gave out, and he plummeted straight out of the sky.

The Essence Fire Raven could see that he had fallen unconscious, and it caught him on its back, then gently flew down onto the same rock from before.

Once there, the silver flames continued to swirl over his body, burning away the white exoskeleton.

Only the next morning did the exoskeleton completely fall away, and during this entire time, the Time Dao Runes on the golden ring above his head continued to fade one after another.

……

Several days passed by in a flash.

One morning, as the sun rose up over the horizon, the first ray of sunlight shone down onto Han Li's face, and his eyelashes fluttered slightly before his eyes slowly opened.

After burning away the restrictive exoskeleton, the Essence Fire Raven reverted back into a miniature silver figure, then sat down onto Han Li's chest with its arms and legs crossed to keep a lookout for him.

As soon as Han Li opened his eyes, it immediately jumped up to look at him with an elated expression.

Han Li's head was feeling very dull and heavy from spiritual sense overexertion, and his vision was unable to focus. He wanted to get up into a sitting position, but his entire body was racked with agony, and he felt as if there were an enormous mountain weighing down upon him.

It seemed that due to the fact that he had come here through physical transmigration, he was constantly being suppressed by the Great Dao of this time and space, thereby resulting in these negative symptoms.

Han Li channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts, and a layer of hazy white light appeared over his body. Only then were his eyes able to focus on the Essence Fire Raven, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

The fiery silver figure immediately jumped onto his shoulder, then began to make wild and exaggerated gestures in an attempt to communicate something to him.

"Alright, I know, I know, you were the one who freed me from that exoskeleton, and you also brought me here and protected me this entire time," Han Li said with an amused smile.

Chapter 842: Two Pieces of News

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he looked up at the golden ring above his head to find that almost all of the Time Dao Runes on it had been snuffed out.

"Come back, we have to go soon," Han Li said as he turned to the Essence Fire Raven.

The fiery silver figure nodded in response, then flew back into Han Li's body.

After that, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed to meditate, and it didn't take long before the final Time Dao Rune faded.

Immediately thereafter, the golden ring above his head abruptly swelled to several times its original size, and a dark vortex appeared within it, releasing bursts of formidable suction force that drew Han Li into the vortex.

Moments later, Han Li reappeared in his room in the Long Pavilion Garden amid a flash of golden light.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he swept his gaze across his room, and only after ensuring that nothing was amiss did he allow himself a sigh of relief.

His consciousness was still reeling from the overexertion of his spiritual sense, but now that he was no longer being suppressed by the very environment that he was in, he felt a lot more comfortable.

Not far away from him, the translucent wall of light was gradually fading away, and the Heaven Controlling Vial was also slowly returning to its normal state.

Han Li raised a hand to draw the vial into his grasp, following which his brows furrowed slightly as he stroked the vial and attempted to establish a spiritual connection with the vial spirit.

Prior to his transmigration, he had clearly heard someone speaking to him in his mind, and he was confident that that had been the voice of the vial spirit, but unfortunately, his attempts to establish a spiritual connection proved to be futile.

A few moments later, he placed the Heaven Controlling Vial back around his own neck, then tucked it into the front of his robes.

As he did this, he suddenly noticed that a golden ring had appeared on the ring finger of his right hand. It appeared to have been crafted from pure gold, and even though though there weren't any features or designs on its surface, it was very full and supple in appearance.

He fought through the pain in consciousness to inspect the ring with his spiritual sense, but he wasn't able to detect any energy fluctuations from it, and it was as if this really was just an ordinary ring.

He then attempted to remove the ring, only to discover that it seemed to have fused as one with his body.

Even after tugging on the ring with such force that he felt as if he were about to rip off his own finger, it still refused to budge even a single inch.

Hence, Han Li could only give up on this endeavor. In any case, the ring didn't seem to be having any detrimental effects on him at the moment.

After sitting in silence for a short while, Han Li channeled the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and bursts of faint golden light appeared around him as the five time-attribute artifacts emerged one after another, but all of the Time Dao Runes on the artifacts had been snuffed out, and the time law power fluctuations that they were giving off had also become much weaker.

However, right at this moment, the golden ring on his finger suddenly lit up, then flew off his finger on its own before hovering in mid-air in front of him.

Immediately thereafter, it began to swell rapidly in size, and the light that it was radiating also became brighter and brighter, to the point that it had taken on a slightly transparent appearance.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then peered through the golden ring to discover that there were dozens of translucent golden threads swirling around incessantly within it, giving off bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations.

This golden ring was the very same ring formed by his time law threads, and as soon as the ring appeared, all of the other time-attribute artifacts immediately flew into it before glowing far brighter than before.

At the same time, Han Li could sense the Heaven Controlling Vial begin to stir a little in front of his chest, as if it were about to fly out once again.

Han Li was very alarmed by this, and he immediately braced himself for another potential transmigration, but the vial only trembled a few times before falling still again.

As for the ring of time, it hovered in mid-air for a short while before returning to his finger as a golden ring.

Is this due to a lack of active Time Dao Runes? Han Li thought to himself as he stroked the ring with a perplexed expression, but his pondering clearly wasn't going to yield any answers for now, so he cast the train of thought aside and withdrew all of the time-attribute artifacts back into his own body.

After that, he flipped a hand over to take a restorative pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

Using Purple Sun Warm Jade would definitely speed up his recovery, and he had just obtained a large supply from Shi Zhanfeng, but given Weeping Soul's current condition, he decided that it was best to save all of the Purple Sun Warm Jade for her.

……

Inside the Naraka Area, there was a large garden that was filled with a series of extremely beautiful and opulent buildings.

One of them was a resplendent palace with a conical roof, and at this moment, there was a handsome young man with a head of silver hair seated on a large golden chair inside the palace.

Standing before him was a tall man with a set of angular features, clad in a suit of black devilish armor. At this moment, the man was bowed down while delivering a report.

"Is this information reliable, Du Yuan?" the silver-haired young man asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Most definitely, Your Highness. I'm willing to vouch for this information with my life," Du Yuan replied.

"I've been searching for so long, and I never thought it would be in that accursed place. Having said that, I suppose that makes sense. If it was in any other place, it wouldn't have taken me so long to find it," the young man mused.

"Your Highness, I came back to deliver this report in the hope that you can mobilize some more people to come with me to recover the item," Du Yuan said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"You've already done a very good job uncovering this information, I'll take care of the rest myself," the young man replied.

"Your Highness, may I ask if you're planning to venture into that place yourself? There's no telling what perils could be lurking in that place, so I strongly advise you not to take the risk," Du Yuan said in a solemn manner.

The young man waved a hand to dismiss Du Yuan's concerns as he said, "This matter concerns my Great Dao, and it'll decide whether I can reach the Great Encompassment Stage before all of my siblings, so it must be regarded with the utmost priority. Set aside everything else for now and focus on this matter as the top priority."

"Yes, Your Highness," Du Yuan replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

……

Several more years flew by in a flash.

Han Li was cultivating in his secret chamber, and the five time-attribute artifacts were hovering in the air around him, with all of them having already recovered a decent number of Time Dao Runes.

The rate of recovery seemed to have become even faster.

The golden ring remained firmly attached to his finger, appearing no different from a mundane accessory.

During this period of seclusion, he had already completely recovered from his injuries and spiritual overexertion, and he had also made some strides in his cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

At the same time, he had developed better control over his ring of time and could now avoid triggering the ring while cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

He was making sure to keep the ring in check as the alternative would be involuntary transmigration.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open, and he emerged from his secret chamber into the hall outside.

There was a buzzing ball of white light that was flying around the hall like a lost bird, and Han Li drew the ball of white light into his grasp to discover that it was a voice transmission talisman.

He crushed the talisman in his hand, and a message was transmitted into his mind.

After hearing the message, Han Li made his way out of the Long Garden Pavilion, where Shi Chuankong was already waiting for him.

"Your dedication to cultivation is truly unmatched, Fellow Daoist Li."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Shi. Please come in," Han Li replied with a smile as he made an inviting hand gesture.

The two of them entered the guest hall together, then sat down in front of a round stone table.

"Why have you come to visit me instead of traveling to the Heavenly Rainbow Region?"

"I've never managed an entire region before, and I was completely blindsided by all of the work involved. On top of that, Zhanfeng and the others are constantly getting in my way, so I'll have my work set out for me for the foreseeable future. Let's not talk about that for now. I've come here today to deliver two pieces of news to you," Shi Chuankong said with a serious expression.

"What is it?" Han Li asked as he set down his teacup.

"The first piece of news pertains to the Scalptia Spatial Domain that you asked me to track down," Shi Chuankong replied as he took a sip of tea.

"Have you found some leads?" Han Li asked.

"Kind of. I'd never heard of the place before this, and only consulting many records and asking Pokong was I able to find out some information about it. Just like the Night Sun Domain, the Scalptia Spatial Domain is an independent domain in our Holy Realm, and it's also what's called a desolate domain," Shi Chuankong replied.

"What's a desolate domain?" Han Li asked.

"It means that the domain has no spiritual qi or devilish qi. There are no records detailing exactly what the environment is like in there, but in any case, it's a very special place. Many years ago, it used to be where criminals were sent into exile, but it's already been abandoned for hundreds of thousands of years," Shi Chuankong explained.

"Have you found out its location?" Han Li asked.

"I knew you would ask that," Shi Chuankong chuckled as he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip that contained a map.

Han Li took a moment to inspect the map, following which Shi Chuankong said in a solemn manner, "Fellow Daoist Li, I don't know why you're searching for this Scalptia Spatial Domain, but it's a very dangerous place, so I strongly advise you not to go there."

"I'll be sure to keep that in mind, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li replied with a smile. "By the way, what's the second piece of news that you have for me?"

Chapter 843: News on Violet Spirit

"The second thing I want to tell you is that I've managed to dig up some information on that ascended cultivator by the name of Violet Spirit," Shi Chuankong said as a suggestive look appeared in his eyes.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

Even though he had asked Shi Chuankong to find Violet Spirit for him, he actually wasn't optimistic at all. After all, it hadn't been that long since he ascended to the True Immortal Realm, and at Violet Spirit's rate of cultivation progression, there was no guarantee that she would've already ascended.

He had really only told Shi Chuankong about Violet Spirit so that he would look out for her if she were to ascend to the Devil Realm in the future, so it was a very pleasant surprise that he had actually managed to find her.

"Pokong has been diligent in this matter, and he sent out people to investigate all of the cultivators who had recently ascended to our Holy Realm. In the process, he found a female cultivator who ascended to the Black Water Region over a hundred years ago, and she matched your description of this Violet Spirit. I have to say that she really is quite a beauty," Shi Chuankong said as he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized azure bead.

A burst of gentle azure light appeared within the bead at his behest, and the image of a woman in a black dress emerged. She had waist-length black hair, and just as Shi Chuankong had said, she was a stunning beauty. There was a cold demeanor about her, but that only further added to her appeal, and it was none other than Violet Spirit.

Han Li shuddered slightly at the sight of this familiar figure, and he was lost in thought for a long while before finally returning to his senses.

"Looks like we've got the right person. In all the time that we've been together, I've never seen you like that. How about you tell me some stories about you and her? I'm sure they must be very exciting," Shi Chuankong jibed.

Han Li remained unflustered despite Shi Chuankong's jibes, and he immediately asked, "Where is she right now?"

"Calm down, Brother Li. The thing with ascended cultivators is that all of them possess tremendous potential, so they'll be invited to join the nearby powers following their ascension. Not only is Violet Spirit a stunning beauty, I've heard that she also possesses remarkable aptitude. As a result, she caught the eye of a Great Encompassment cultivator of the Black Water Region," Shi Chuankong said as a peculiar look appeared on his face.

"There must be some type of problem with this Great Encompassment cultivator, right?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"The Great Encompassment cultivator in question is Daoist Master Black River, and he's very renowned in our Holy Realm. He's a relatively normal man, but..."

Shi Chuankong's voice trailed off into an awkward silence here.

"But what?" Han Li asked as a sense of foreboding welled up in his heart.

"You know how us men are... Even though he's already reached the Great Encompassment Stage, he still has basic desires, and on top of that, Celestial Maiden Violet Spirit is truly a very beautiful woman, so..."

Once again, Shi Chuankong's voice trailed off into an awkward silence.

Han Li's expression instantly darkened significantly upon hearing this, and he immediately began making his way out of the room.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, Daoist Master Black River is on very good terms with Pokong. As soon as we found out this information, Pokong immediately sent a warning to Daoist Master Black River, but we're still yet to receive a response," Shi Chuankong informed.

Han Li remained silent as he made his way out of the manor, and there was already a beast-drawn carriage waiting for him, clearly arranged in advance by Shi Chuankong.

"I recall that there are teleportation arrays in Night Sun City, right? Is there one that leads to the Black Water Region?" Han Li asked.

"There is. Come with me," Shi Chuankong sighed, then made his way onto the carriage.

It only took the carriage about an hour to reach a giant palace in the Naraka Area, one that was over a thousand feet tall and took up an area of over ten acres.

The entire building was black in color, and hanging above its entrance was a golden plaque that read "High Profound Palace".

It was a very lively and bustling place, and there were many other carriages parked near the entrance, as well as many people entering and exiting the palace.

"There are two teleportation halls in Night Sun City, one of which is this High Profound Palace, which is reserved for nobility, while the other one is the High Moon Palace in the Maha Area, which is accessible to normal cultivators, merchants, or travelers. The High Profound Palace is the slightly larger one of the two," Shi Chuankong introduced.

On the way here, Han Li had been silent this entire time, and Shi Chuankong was intentionally trying to find some topics of conversation to lighten the mood.

"Don't worry about me, Fellow Daoist Shi, I'm fine," Han Li said as he took a deep breath, and at this point, he was looking a lot more composed than before.

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, and the two of them made their way into the High Profound Palace with the crowd.

The floor inside the palace was paved with opulent white jade bricks, while a series of white crystals had been embedded into the palace's ceiling and walls, releasing gentle white light that illuminated the entire place.

The ceiling was supported by stone pillars, and there were over a hundred white stone platforms laid out across the palace, each of which was carrying a teleportation array, accompanied by a stone plaque that marked out the teleportation array's destination.

This teleportation hall was quite similar to ones that Han Li had seen in the past, except all of the teleportation arrays in here were very complex.

Shi Chuankong seemed to be very familiar with this place, and he led Han Li straight to a teleportation array deep in the palace, one that led to Black River City.

At this moment, the teleportation array was completely empty, and Han Li immediately began to make his way into it.

However, he was stopped in his tracks by a purple-robed man, who said, "Is this your first time using a teleportation array in the High Profound Hall, Fellow Daoist? You have to purchase a teleportation talisman first."

Shi Chuankong flipped a hand over upon seeing this, summoning a golden badge that was emblazoned with the words "Heavenly Merchant Marquis".

The purple-robed man's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly stepped out of Han Li's way as he apologized, "Ah, please forgive me, Your Highness, I didn't know it was you."

Han Li paid no heed to the purple-robed man as he stepped onto the teleportation array, followed closely by Shi Chuankong.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, you have a lot on your plate right now, so there's no need for you to accompany me on this trip. I'll come and find you once I'm back," Han Li said.

"Don't worry about it, Fellow Daoist Li. I won't be making any inroads into the Heavenly Rainbow Region anytime soon, and I've become quite weary of all of the politics in Night Sun City, so it'd do me a world of good to go out do some sightseeing," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said with a grateful expression.

Daoist Master Black River was a Great Encompassment cultivator, so he had no confidence in his own ability to take Violet Spirit and escape safely. However, with Shi Chuankong in accompaniment, things were most likely going to be a lot easier.

"Your Highness, that marquis badge of yours grants you three free teleportation opportunities per century. You're teleporting two people on this occasion, so you'll be using up two of the three opportunities here," the purple-robed man informed in a respectful manner as he pulled out a purple copper mirror.

"I'm aware of that, hurry up and activate the array," Shi Chuankong urged in an impatient manner, and the purple-robed man immediately nodded in response before doing as he was told.

Before long, the teleportation array was up and running, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong vanished from within it amid a flash of white light.

After their vision was restored, the two of them discovered that they had arrived in another teleportation hall.

This one was only less than two hundred feet in size, and it only contained three teleportation arrays.

There were very few other people in the hall, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong quickly made their way outside to discover a small city constructed by a black river.

The water in the river was so turbulent that it was rumbling with sufficient ferocity to be clearly audible even in the city.

The city didn't appear to be very vibrant at all, and it was severely lacking even compared with Preeminent City.

"The Black Water Region derives its name from the many rivers and lakes in the region. However, it's a very secluded place, and it doesn't have any valuable resources or demon beasts to be hunted, so it's one of the barren regions in our Holy Realm," Shi Chuankong introduced.

Han Li nodded in response. The spiritual qi and devilish qi here were indeed far less abundant than they were in Night Sun City.

The one good thing about this place was that the city had no flight restrictions, so the two of them were quickly able to fly into the city.

Shi Chuankong summoned his flying carriage, and it sped off in a certain direction.

"Daoist Master Black River resides in one of the lakes of the Black Water Region, and it'll take close to three months to get there. I have to warn you now that Daoist Master Black River is... a bit of a petty man, so this trip may not go very smoothly," Shi Chuankong said with slightly furrowed brows, and Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Due to his recent physical transmigration, only a small portion of his Time Dao Runes were currently active, so his time-attribute abilities weren't going to be as potent as usual.

However, in any case, there was no way that he could back down.

With that in mind, he took a deep breath, then sat down with his legs crossed.

Meanwhile, a purple talisman flew out of Shi Chuankong's sleeve, then imploded into countless purple runes that fused into his flying carriage.

The front of the flying carriage instantly took on the form of a bird's head, while two large purple wings that were each over a hundred feet in length emerged from its midsection, transforming the entire carriage into a giant purple bird.

In the wake of this transformation, the flying carriage sped up drastically, hurtling through the air as a long streak of purple light.

Chapter 844: Offense

Two months later, Han Li and Shi Chuankong appeared in the air above a giant lake.

The lake stretched as far as the eyes could see in all directions, and it looked no different from the vast sea.

"This lake is called Thousand Wave Lake, and Daoist Master Black River resides in the water palace on the lakebed. Fellow Daoist Li, I think we should aim for a peaceful resolution first, then only resort to violence if necessary," Shi Chuankong said.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi, we're dealing with a Great Encompassment cultivator and also an ally to His Highness, so I won't rush in recklessly," Han Li replied in a calm manner, and Shi Chuankong was very relieved to see this.

"Come to think of it, we're already very close to the border of the Black Water Region. Beyond this lake is the Black Savage Region, right?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"That's right," Shi Chuankong replied.

The Black Savage Region was home to the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't speak any further on the subject.

The two of them flew into the lake, then began a descent.

The lake was extremely deep, and even after descending for hundreds of thousands of feet, the lakebed was still nowhere in sight.

At this point, there was tremendous water pressure from all directions, and even Han Li was feeling a little uncomfortable.

Shi Chuankong opened his mouth to release a blue bead, which, in turn, released a hug ball of blue light that enveloped the two of them, upon which the surrounding water pressure completely abated.

After descending several more tens of thousands of feet, the two of them finally reached the lakebed, which had an undulating terrain, much like an underwater mountain range.

There were also many giant, immeasurably deep chasms on the lakebed that looked as if they led straight into the depths of hell.

Under Shi Chuankong's guidance, the two of them made their way into one of these chasms before continuing their descent.

"You seem to be very familiar with this place, Fellow Daoist Shi. Have you been here before?" Han Li asked.

"No, but I did make some contributions to the alliance that was formed between Pokong and Daoist Master Black River, so I conducted some research into his place of dwelling in the past," Shi Chuankong explained with a smile.

"I see," Han Li replied.

The water in the chasms on the lakebed was a little different from the water elsewhere in the lake. The deeper they descended, the more viscous and darker in color the water became, and it almost resembled heavy water.

At this point, it was so dark that visibility was extremely limited, but after descending for a short while longer, the chasm suddenly opened up into an enormous underground cave, at the center of which was an enormous island that was tens of thousands of acres in size.

The island consisted of an entire chunk of black crystalline material, and there were countless pavilions, pagodas, and palaces that had been constructed upon it.

The largest of the palaces had a plaque that was several hundred feet in size hanging above the entrance, and the words "Black River Water Palace" could be seen on the plaque.

The entire island was giving off rippling light that was black in color, but somehow still had a glittering and translucent quality to it, giving this place the appearance of an underwater crystal palace. It was an extremely spectacular sight to behold, and the island was also encompassed within a giant black light barrier that kept the surrounding lake water at bay.

Countless runes could be seen on the black light barrier, giving off formidable energy fluctuations.

Han Li was certain that if anyone were to try and attack the light barrier by force, the restrictions on it would be capable of instantly killing even a High Zenith cultivator.

"We're finally here. This entire island is actually an enormous piece of Yin Zenith Water Jade, and it's been refined by Daoist Master Black River for countless years, so the island is essentially an enormous devilish treasure. Hence, unless we've exhausted all other options, it would be best for us to avoid a conflict," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li remained silent as a look of resolve flashed through his eyes.

Shi Chuankong heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this, and he knew that his advice had fallen onto deaf ears. Hence, he didn't bother to say anything further, and he flipped a hand over to produce a blue jade badge before tossing it forward.

The jade badge flew through the black light barrier as a streak of blue light, then vanished into thin air.

Moments later, a slightly wary female voice rang out from the island.

"Who has come to visit our Black River Water Palace?"

"I am Shi Chuankong, and I've come to meet Daoist Master Black River," Shi Chuankong replied as he stepped forward to present his purple badge.

The female voice was silent for a moment before ringing out again.

"Welcome, Your Highness. Forgive me for not coming out to greet you sooner."

At the same time, the section of the black light barrier directly in front of Han Li's duo parted to create a passageway that was several dozen feet in size.

Once again, a sense of gratitude toward Shi Chuankong welled up in Han Li's heart. It was only thanks to his status as a prince that they had been granted entry so easily. Otherwise, given how cautious the woman appeared, just entering the Black River Water Palace alone would've been a difficult task for Han Li.

The two of them exchanged a glance before flying into the opening together, and as soon as they did so, they were immediately enveloped by bursts of black light.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't put up any resistance, and in the next instant, they appeared in a spacious hall.

The walls and the ground of the hall were all a translucent black color, and even the furniture in the room was directly connected to the floor. As it turned out, everything in the entire hall had been carved out, so it was all tightly interconnected.

The sound of footsteps rang out from within the hall, and a beautiful woman in a light blue robe with three golden hairpins in her hair emerged, followed by four maidservants.

The woman appeared to be in her thirties with fair skin and gorgeous features, but there was a slightly cold and domineering aura about her.

Han Li could see that she was at the early-High Zenith Stage, and given her disposition, it seemed that she was an important figure in this Black River Water Palace.

"Please forgive me for not arranging a more elaborate welcome, Your Highness," the woman said as she extended a curtsey.

"Don't worry about it, we're the ones to blame for arriving unannounced," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

The woman took a glance at Han Li, and her brows furrowed ever so slightly, but she didn't say anything.

Shi Chuankong could see the apprehension in the woman's eyes, so he delivered an introduction for both sides. "Fellow Daoist Li, this is Lady Ju, Senior Black River's dao partner. This is Fellow Daoist Li, and even though he comes from the Immortal Realm, he's a very close friend of mine."

"It's a pleasure to meet you, Lady Ju," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Lady Ju's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and she extended a slight curtsey in return.

Lady Ju invited Han Li's duo to sit down, then ordered the maidservants behind her to bring out some tea and fruits before asking, "To what does our Black River Water Palace owe this honor, Your Highness?"

"I've come here today to speak to Senior Black River about something. Is he in the palace right now?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"That's unfortunate. My husband went into seclusion to cultivate a powerful secret technique many years ago, so I'm afraid he won't be able to come out to see you," Lady Ju replied, and Han Li was internally quite relieved to see this.

"I see, that is indeed rather unfortunate timing," Shi Chuankong said as he took a subtle glance at Han Li out of the corner of his eye.

"Prior to going into seclusion, my husband assigned me with the task of taking care of all of the Black River Water Palace's affairs. May I ask the purpose of your visit today? As long as it doesn't require any major decision-making, I should be able to help you," Lady Ju said with a smile.

Even though she was doing her best to disguise it, there was still a hint of pride and haughtiness in her eyes.

"It's nothing overly important. I heard that your Black River Water Palace recruited an ascended cultivator by the name of Violet Spirit about a century ago, is that correct?" Shi Chuankong asked.

The smile on Lady Ju's face instantly vanished upon hearing this, and a cold look of envy flashed through her eyes.

However, the change in her expression only lingered for a moment before she regained her composure, and she replied, "That's correct. Why do you ask about her, Your Highness?"

Even though the change in Lady Ju's expression was only for an instant, it failed to escape the notice of Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and Han Li's heart sank slightly upon seeing this.

"Violet Spirit just so happens to be a friend of Fellow Daoist Li's from the time when they were both in the lower realm, and Fellow Daoist Li has decided to pay her a visit after learning that she's ascended. Would you be able to invite her out to meet him?" Shi Chuankong requested.

"You two were friends, you say? More like lovers, am I right? I knew she was a slutty vixen, seducing men everywhere she goes!" Lady Ju sneered as she took a cold glance at Han Li.

"Violet Spirit has only recently ascended to the Holy Realm, so she's still quite unfamiliar with everything here. If she's caused you any offense, please allow me to apologize on her behalf," Han Li said as he rose to his feet before cupping his fist in a salute.

Lady Ju merely harrumphed coldly and offered no response.

"As a show of my sincerity, I would like to offer a few gifts," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light over the table beside him.

The azure light then faded to reveal four objects, namely a blue flag, a purple seal, a piece of blue crystal, and a length of black wood.

The blue flag and the purple seal were both graded devilish treasures, while the blue crystal and the black wood were both materials that harbored tremendous law powers, giving off law power fluctuations that were even more formidable than the pair of devilish treasures.

These four items were all from Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage tool, and even Shi Chuankong couldn't help but be drawn in by them.

Lady Ju's eyes also lit up at the sight of the items, but she then harrumphed coldly as she turned away, clearly refusing the offering.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

"Lady Ju, would it be possible for you to do me a favor and allow them to meet just this once?" Shi Chuankong asked.

Chapter 845: Exiled

"Of course I can't deny a request from you, Your Highness, but the problem is that Violet Spirit currently isn't in the Black River Water Palace, so I can't call on her even if I wanted to," Lady Ju replied as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Where is she?" Han Li immediately asked.

"Our Black River Water Palace is home to many cultivators, and that slut was granted special privileges by my husband, allowing her to enter and exit the water palace as she pleases, so how am I supposed to know where she's gone?" Lady Ju snapped in a cold voice.

Lady Ju's scathing words and haughty attitude were really beginning to get on Han Li's nerves, and he said, "You just said that you were assigned with the task of overseeing the Black River Water Palace's affairs during Senior Black River's seclusion, so surely you at least have some idea of where Violet Spirit has gone."

"Who the hell do you think you are? I only allowed an Immortal Realm scoundrel like you into our Black River Water Palace because you're accompanying His Highness, yet you dare to interrogate me now? Our Black River Water Palace doesn't welcome uncivilized guests like you!"

Lady Ju abruptly flared up with rage and swept both sleeves through the air she spoke.

Two bursts of black light immediately erupted out of the walls on either side of the hall, then swept up Han Li in a flash before forming a black vortex, attempting to teleport him out of the palace.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis instantly appeared behind him before revolving rapidly on the spot, releasing countless golden ripples that encompassed the black vortex, which fell completely still.

Lady Ju's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she made a rapid string of hand seals to try and spur the black vortex back into action, but to no avail.

"Lady Ju, I have no intention of opposing you. All I want to know is Violet Spirit's whereabouts, and I'm willing to compensate you handsomely for this information," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Insolent scoundrel! Do you really think I'm powerless to do anything to you? Come to me, Black River Water Palace!" Lady Ju yelled as she continued to make more hand seals, and the entire Black River Water Palace began to tremble.

Countless rays of black light converged from all directions, forming a miniature Black River Water Palace projection that was several feet in size over the palm of her hand.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to do anything, Lady Ju thrust both palms forward, sending the Black River Water Palace projection flying into the golden ripples around Han Li.

The golden ripples were instantly torn apart without being able to pose any resistance, and as a result, the black vortex was restored to its normal state, instantly devouring Han Li like a giant black mouth.

In the next instant, Han Li found himself outside the Black River Water Palace.

Only a small portion of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had recovered, so its powers were greatly diminished.

However, for Violet Spirit's sake, there was no way that he could back down.

He took a deep breath, then activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to inspect the restrictions on the black light barrier before him, and at the same time, his Mantra Treasured Axis released a wave of golden ripples that descended upon the light barrier.

Right at this moment, a familiar voice suddenly rang out from beside him.

"I knew I'd find you here, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li hurriedly swung around to discover Shi Pokong standing not far away.

"What are you doing here, Your Highness?" Han Li asked in a surprised voice as he stopped what he was doing.

A faint smile appeared on Shi Pokong's face, and he was just about to respond when a black vortex suddenly took shape nearby amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

The black vortex only lingered for a moment before fading away to reveal Shi Chuankong, and it seemed that he had also been thrown out by Lady Ju.

"Pokong? What are you doing here?" Shi Chuankong asked with a surprised expression.

"I heard that the two of you left Night Sun City for the Black Water Region, so I knew that you had to have come for Celestial Maiden Violet Spirit. Even now, the matter concerning Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul hasn't been resolved, and that's constantly been weighing on my mind, so to make up for that, I wanted to do whatever I could to help Fellow Daoist Li save Violet Spirit," Shi Pokong replied with an apologetic expression.

"You can count on Pokong, Fellow Daoist Li! He'll definitely be able to save Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit!" Shi Chuankong said with an ecstatic expression.

"Thank you, Your Highness," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"What's the situation like now? It looks like things haven't gone very smoothly for the two of you," Shi Pokong remarked.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he gave Shi Pokong a recount of what had happened in the Black River Water Palace.

"Lady Ju is Daoist Master Black River's dao partner, but while she possesses quite a lofty cultivation base, she's also a very petty woman, so she must've been very jealous of Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit. You're a friend of Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit's so her resentment must've extended to you as well," Shi Pokong mused after hearing Han Li's recount.

"I figured that was the case. I'm going to make her tell me Violet Spirit's whereabouts whether she likes it or not, even if I have to do it by force," Han Li said as a cold look flashed through his eyes.

Violet Spirit wasn't his dao partner, but in his heart, he was just as important as Nangong Wan, and there was no way that he could simply back down, knowing full well that she was potentially in a state of peril.

Shi Pokong hurriedly stopped him as he said, "I can understand that you urgently wish to save your friend, but resolving this matter by force is not a wise option. Daoist Master Black River is a Great Encompassment cultivator, and even though he's in seclusion right now, you'll be in a lot of trouble if he comes after you after emerging from seclusion."

"I know this isn't a wise option, but I have no other choice," Han Li replied with furrowed brows.

"If you trust me, then leave this matter to me. Daoist Master Black River and I are allies at the moment, so Lady Ju can't just kick me out as she pleases, and perhaps I'll be able to get some information out of her," Shi Pokong said.

"Pokong's right, Fellow Daoist Li. Let him go first, and if that doesn't work, then we'll think of somehting else," Shi Chuankong chimed in.

"Alright, in that case, I'll be counting on you, Your Highness," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Get back a little," Shi Pokong said to Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and the two of them exchanged a glance before flying back into the distance, following which Shi Pokong began to approach the Black River Water Palace.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to observe the Black River Water Palace from afar, while Shi Pokong summoned a blue talisman before sending it flying into the black light barrier.

Moments later, an opening appeared on the black light barrier, and Shi Pokong immediately flew inside.

"You can rest assured now, Fellow Daoist Li. Pokong will definitely be able to find out Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit's whereabouts for you," Shi Chuankong assured with a confident smile.

"I certainly hope so," Han Li sighed.

Close to two hours flew by in a flash.

Han Li was still relatively calm and collected, but Shi Chuankong was beginning to grow a little uneasy, and he opened his mouth on multiple occasions to say something, but didn't know what to say.

Right at this moment, an opening reappeared on the black light barrier, and Shi Pokong flew out from within.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong immediately approached him before the former asked, "How did it go, Your Highness?"

"I was able to find out Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit's current whereabouts, as well as some information about the time that she spent in the Black River Water Palace," Shi Pokong replied with a faint smile, and Han Li was ecstatic to hear this.

"I knew we could count on you, Pokong!" Shi Chuankong said with a wide smile.

"Thank you, Your Highness. How has Violet Spirit been faring after coming to the Black River Water Palace?" Han Li asked.

"After she ascended to the Holy Realm, Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit caught Daoist Master Black River's eye for her looks and her aptitude, and he wanted to make her his concubine, but she desperately refused, threatening to take her own life.

“Daoist Master Black River didn't want to subdue her by force, and he was also in a hurry to go into seclusion at the time, so he could only leave Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit under the supervision of Lady Ju," Shi Pokong replied.

Han Li was quite relieved to hear this, and Shi Chuankong slapped him firmly on the shoulder as he exulted, "That's great! Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit's purity still remains, so you can rest assured now, Fellow Daoist Li."

"What are you saying, Chuankong?" Shi Pokong scolded with a stern glare.

Only then did Shi Chuankong realize that he had misspoken, and he scratched his own head with an awkward look on his face.

Han Li remained completely unflustered as he said, "Violet Spirit is all on her own, so even if something had happened, it wouldn't be her fault. What happened after that? Is Violet Spirit still in the Black River Water Palace?"

"After Daoist Master Black River went into seclusion, Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit attempted to escape from the Black River Water Palace, and not only did Lady Ju not stop her, she intentionally let her go, so she's not in the Black River Water Palace right now," Shi Pokong sighed.

"That's good news, is it not? The Holy Realm is a big place, but it won't be difficult for us to track someone down. Once we get back, I'll make some arrangements, and..."

Shi Chuankong's voice gradually trailed off as he spoke, and he seemed to have realized that something wasn't quite right.

Han Li's brows were also tightly furrowed in concern.

It made sense for Lady Ju to intentionally allow Violet Spirit to escape from the Black River Water Palace, and even if Daoist Master Black River were to ask her about the matter after coming out of seclusion, he wouldn't be able to blame her.

However, given how petty she was, there was no way that she would simply allow Violet Spirit to leave.

Shi Pokong took a glance at Han Li, then confirmed his suspicions as he said, "Not long after Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit left the Black River Water Palace, Lady Ju sent people to capture her before exiling her into the Scalptia Spatial Domain."

Chapter 846: Taking a Risk

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this, while Shi Chuankong hesitated momentarily before remarking, "The Scalptia Spatial Domain is not a safe place, and Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit only recently ascended, so she's most likely still only at the True Immortal Stage..."

"Aside from his dao partner in Lady Ju, Daoist Master Black River also has around a dozen concubines, and there's been constantly infighting among them over the years, so the fact that Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit has been able to remain safe here for so many years indicates that she's a very smart woman.

“On top of that, I'm assuming Daoist Master Black River must've given her a few powerful devilish treasures for her protection, so even if she's been cast into exile in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, she should be able to keep herself safe," Shi Pokong said.

"I certainly hope that's the case. I must thank you again, Your Highness. It's very impressive that you were able to uncover so much information in such a short time. You've put me to shame in this regard," Han Li sighed.

"I agree. How did you manage to get all of this information out of that petty wench?" Shi Chuankong asked with a curious expression.

"I've been dealing with Lady Ju for many years, so I know her very well. Before I went in, I already had a rough idea of how she would've treated Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit, and it wasn't difficult to find out all of this by asking some leading questions," Shi Pokong replied calmly, as if he had just done something very simple.

"It may not have been difficult for you, but it was an impossible task for the two of us," Han Li said with a hint of admiration in his eyes.

"It's really not that impressive," Shi Pokong chuckled in a modest fashion. "What do you plan to do from here, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"This isn't the place to be talking, so let's leave this place first," Han Li replied.

Half a month later, in a courtyard in the city lord's manor of Black River City.

There was a round ebony table in an elegant and refined hall, atop which sat a red clay stove with a fire burning inside. Large amounts of steam were surging out of the purple clay teapot on top of the stove, causing the teapot's lid to clatter incessantly.

At this moment, Shi Pokong was standing beside the table, and he lifted the teapot before pouring some of its contents into another teapot to wash the tea leaves inside, then poured the water away before replacing it with some new water.

Only after that did he pour the tea out into three intricate teacups on the table before pushing two of them toward Shi Chuankong and Han Li, who were also seated at the table.

"Fellow Daoist Li, perhaps you're still unaware of just how perilous the Scalptia Spatial Domain is. Are you sure you want to go in?" Shi Pokong asked.

"There's no point in trying to dissuade him, Pokong. Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit is extremely important to Brother Li, and if it were possible to dissuade him, I would've already done so," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"In that case, I won't speak any further on this matter. What are your plans then? When are you going to travel to the Heavenly Rainbow Region?" Shi Pokong asked as he turned to Shi Chuankong.

An awkward smile appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he replied, "As you're aware, Brother Li has done a lot for me, so I plan to accompany him on this trip to the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Hence, I'll have to trouble you to look after the Heavenly Rainbow Realm in my stead during my absence."

"That's ridiculous! Father granted you the Heavenly Rainbow Region, not me. On top of that, I can't let you venture into such a dangerous place!" Shi Pokong scolded with a stern expression.

"His Highness is right, Brother Shi, I can make the trip to the Scalptia Spatial Domain on my own," Han Li chimed in.

A serious look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he protested, "Pokong, you've always taught me to repay the kindness of others. Brother Li has saved my life on multiple occasions, so how can I abandon him in his time of need?"

The disapproval on Shi Pokong's face didn't wane in the slightest upon hearing this, but in the end, he could only heave a faint sigh.

"Fine, I knew I wouldn't be able to stop you. If I weren't so busy, I would come with you."

"The city will be fine even if I'm absent for a million years, but it can't go even a single day without you, Pokong!" Shi Chuankong said in an elated manner.

"Alright, that's enough from you. I know some things about the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but I've never been there before myself, so I only have limited information to impart onto the two of you," Shi Pokong sighed.

"Please enlighten us, Your Highness," Han Li requested in an earnest manner.

A few minutes later, Shi Pokong had divulged everything that he knew about the Scalptia Spatial Domain, following which he summoned a pair of items before handing one each to Shi Chuankong and Han Li.

Han Li accepted the item handed to him to discover that it was a piece of beat hide with a rough map drawn on it, with some annotations littered throughout the map.

"This is a map of the Scalptia Spatial Domain that I was able to find from a set of unofficial historic records. It's unclear how old this map is, so it may or may not be able to help you, but take it with you anyway," Shi Pokong said.

Han Li nodded in response, then examined the map briefly before stowing it away.

As for Shi Chuankong, he was holding what appeared to be a pendant, and he asked, "What's this, Pokong?"

Han Li turned to discover that the pendant had been crafted into the form of an intricate cage, and there were numerous ferocious-looking beasts scratching at the cage from inside.

"Wear this on your body at all times, and throw it out if you encounter some insurmountable peril. There's no need to inject any spiritual qi or devilish qi to activate it, and perhaps it could save your lives," Shi Pokong said in a serious manner.

Shi Chuankong did as he was told and put on the pendant.

"Remember that in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, not only is there a complete absence of spiritual and devilish, you won't be able to access your storage tools, either, so if you need something, you'll have to carry it on your body, and once you get in there, your physical bodies will be just about all that you can rely on," Shi Pokong cautioned.

"If the Scalptia Spatial Domain has already been sealed, then how can we return from it?" Han Li asked.

"There's a special teleportation array in the Black Water Region that can teleport one straight out of the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but it hasn't been used for over a hundred thousand years, so it'll most likely take a lot of time and effort to restore. Having said that, I'll take care of it, so there's no need for you to be concerned.

“These two tokens will be vital for the teleportation array to ascertain your locations, so make sure to keep them safe," Shi Pokong replied as he handed a pair of leaf-shaped jade tokens to Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"How do we use these things?" Shi Chuankong asked as he carefully examined his jade token.

"When you want to come back, just shed a drop of blood essence onto the token, and the array on this side will be able to teleport you directly out of the Scalptia Spatial Domain. As for Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit, as long as she's with Fellow Daoist Li, they'll be able to teleport back together," Shi Pokong replied.

"Alright, got it," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"On top of that, I also have two Blood Tide Pills here that can temporarily stimulate the latent potential of your bodies. Of course, the aftereffects from consuming the pill are quite severe, and you'll experience a period of feebleness, perhaps even complete immobility after the pill's effects wear off, so only use it as a last resort," Shi Pokong continued.

"There's no need to be so worried about us, Pokong. We can look after ourselves," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"How could I not be worried? That godforsaken place has been sealed for hundreds of thousands of years! In any case, that's all I have to say, the rest is up to you. Make sure you come back alive and well," Shi Pokong said as he patted Shi Chuankong on the shoulder.

"I will," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile, and a faint smile also appeared on Han Li's face at this show of brotherly affection.

Shortly thereafter, Shi Pokong departed, and after taking a brief rest, Han Li and Sh Chuankong also left the Black Water Region.

Inside the Black Water Region, there was a dark green mountain range that was dotted with brown sand hills that appeared very much out of place, and at this moment, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were hovering in the air above this mountain range.

Even from close to a hundred kilometers away, they were able to detect the strange spatial fluctuations coming from the area.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and he spotted a near-transparent hemispherical restriction that encompassed the entire area up ahead like a giant bowl, with all of the brown hills contained within.

"This must be the entrance to the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Han Li said.

"That's right. I recall that this place was sealed and declared a restricted area by Father a very long time ago," Shi Chuankong replied.

"That must be to prevent the people in exile from escaping," Han Li speculated.

"That's part of the reason, but I think he was more concerned about people from our Holy Realm inadvertently stumbling onto those sand hills before being sucked into the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Shi Chuankong replied.

"I see," Han Li mused with a nod.

"Let's go," Shi Chuankong said, and the two of them descended in front of a hall situated outside the sand hills.

The guards stationed outside the building immediately stopped them in their tracks, and one of them declared, "This is a restricted area, turn back now."

After Shi Chuankong revealed his identity, a Golden Immortal stationed in the hall immediately emerged to greet them.

It was a short and stocky elderly man with some stripes all over his face, and he immediately extended a respectful bow toward Shi Chuankong as he greeted, "Xu Fu pays his respects to His Highness."

Chapter 847: No Return

"No need for formalities, Elder Xu," Shi Chuankong said.

"What brings you here today, Your Highness?" Xu Fu asked with a puzzled expression as he took a glance at Han Li.

"We have some matters to attend to here today," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In that case, please come in, and we'll talk inside," Xu Fu said as he stepped to the side before making an inviting hand gesture.

Shi Chuankong and Han Li exchanged a glance with each other, then entered the hall together.

Upon learning that Han Li and Shi Chuankong intended to enter the Scalptia Spatial Domain, Xu Fu immediately attempted to dissuade them in an alarmed manner.

In response, Shi Chuankong pulled out an handwritten edict prepared by Shi Pokong, claiming that the two of them were carrying out an urgent mission that required them to enter the Scalptia Spatial Domain right away.

"Your Highness, the Scalptia Spatial Domain has already been sealed for many years, and no one knows what things are like in there right now. As for the teleportation array that you mentioned, that hasn't been used for a very long time," Xu Fu said with tightly furrowed brows.

"The Balance Fall Duke has already made arrangements for us, so you can rest assured, Elder Xu," Shi Chuankong replied with a dismissive wave.

"In that case, I won't try to dissuade you any further. Please come with me," Xu Fu said, then led Han Li and Shi Chuankong to the rear hall.

There was a backdoor in the rear hall that led to the sand hills outside, and it clearly served at the entrance to the spatial restriction.

"Once you go in there, just step onto the sand hills, and you'll automatically sink into the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Do keep in mind that this is a one-way entrance, so you can't exit from it," Xu Fu cautioned in a solemn manner.

"We'll be sure to remember that," Han Li replied.

Xu Fu flipped a hand over to summon a black seal, which he pressed into a slot above the door frame, following which the restriction on the back door was opened at his behest.

"I wish you a safe and smooth journey, Your Highness," Xu Fu said.

"Thank you for the well wishes," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

After emerging from the hall, the two of them quickly made their way to the edge of the first hill before stopping in their tracks.

Han Li examined the hill briefly, but wasn't able to detect anything abnormal from it. It wasn't giving off any spatial fluctuations, and it looked no different from a normal hill.

Shi Chuankong flipped a hand over to produce a long black saber, which he strapped to his waist, and in response to Han Li's inquisitive gaze, he explained, "Seeing as we can't use any treasures, surely carrying a weapon will be better than going in empty-handed."

Han Li offered no response as he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, from within which Daoist Xie emerged.

Shi Pokong had told them that storage tools couldn't be accessed, and even though he hadn't made any mention of domain treasures, Han Li still decided that it would be best to release Daoist Xie in advance as a safety precaution.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at the two sabers strapped to Daoist Xie's waist, and he was very pleased to see that someone had the same idea as him.

After some contemplation, Han Li didn't summon any of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords. Instead, he placed all of his storage tools into his domain treasure, and all that remained was the ring of time on his ring finger.

With their preparations complete, the trio exchanged a glance with each other before jumping onto the hill in unison.

As soon as the three of them landed on the hill, a burst of hazy silver light instantly emerged to sweep up the trio, following which they slowly sank downward before vanishing out of sight.

"How strange. No one has even come near this place for so many years, yet recently..."

Xu Fu's voice trailed off there as he watched the trio vanish with a thoughtful look on his face.

"Forget it, who am I to be worrying myself with the affairs of the nobility?"

With that, he closed the restriction, then turned and made his way back to the front of the hall.

……

Inside the Scalptia Spatial Domain was a deserted island with plumes of smoke rising up everywhere.

A giant lizard and a massive centipede were rushing at each other from two opposing ends of the island before crashing into each other with tremendous force.

The force of the clash immediately sent both of them flying backward, and the resulting shockwaves scattered all of the surrounding smoke.

Both the lizard and the centipede were sent tumbling over the ground, but as soon as they steadied themselves, their eyes immediately met once again, and they were clearly preparing for a second clash.

Right at this moment, the sound of blowing wind suddenly rang out from the ground right in between the two giant beasts, and a geyser of sand rose up from the ground, following which Han Li's trio emerged.

The sand around the trio quickly dissipated, and the three of them were immediately struck by a sense of tremendous spatial pressure that was coming from all directions.

Han Li could feel his own internal organs being compressed by some type of external force, and his limbs were also feeling quite heavy, but not enough to impact his movement.

The most jarring change of all was that his immortal spiritual power circulation had instantly drawn to a grinding halt.

However, before they even had a chance to examine their surroundings, the ground beneath them suddenly began to tremble violently as the two giant beasts came charging straight at them.

"Look out!" Han Li yelled, and he swept a sleeve through the air, but nothing happened.

Only then did he recall that it was impossible to use any treasures, law powers, or spirit domains in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Despite this slight hiccup, he adapted very quickly, and all of his profound acupoints lit up as he threw a fist at the oncoming giant lizard.

At the same time, Shi Chuankong gripped onto his black saber with both hands, then launched himself up into the air before swinging the saber down upon the black centipede.

A resounding boom rang out as Han Li's fist struck the lizard's forehead, causing its head to cave in slightly, and it was sent flying back through the air before tumbling end over end along the ground.

As for Han Li himself, he was also knocked by several steps from the force of the clash before steadying himself.

He was quite surprised by this as the giant lizard didn't appear to be all that different from the ones that he had seen in the Immortal Realm, but it possessed far superior power and physical prowess to any similar creature that he had encountered before.

In the face of a punch thrown by Han Li after activating his Great Universe Origin Arts, a normal giant lizard would've had its head completely smashed open, yet this one remained largely unharmed, and that was nothing short of incredible.

At the same time, a sharp clang rang out as Shi Chuankong's saber struck the giant centipede on the head, then slid all the way down its body, leaving a bright trail of sparks in its wake, but the saber only left a mark on its body and couldn't even slice through its scales.

"Pokong was telling us that the creatures in here are all vastly different from those in the outside world, I can see now that he wasn't kidding," Shi Chuankong grumbled.

"The spatial pressure in here is at least twice as potent as it is in the outside world, so the creatures in here would've had to adapt, thereby making them physically stronger than their counterparts in the outside world," Han Li said in a grim voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the giant lizard was already charging at him once again.

Han Li clenched his right fist tightly, then launched himself toward the oncoming giant lizard, creating a deep crater each time his foot landed on the ground.

The distance between the two was rapidly shrinking, and right as they were about to clash, Han Li suddenly sprang up into the air before hurtling directly toward the giant lizard like a flying spear.

At the same time, he unclenched his fist and extended his fingers so that his hand resembled a flat blade, and he plunged it down toward the lizard's head.

The two fingers formed by the Flower Branch domain were flashing with a jade-like glow, and they struck the exact spot on the lizard's head where Han Li's fist had struck just a moment ago.

A huge geyser of yellowish-brown blood erupted forth as Han Li's hand pierced into the giant lizard's head, and his momentum propelled him forward until his entire arm was embedded inside.

The lizard let loose an agonized roar before collapsing to the ground.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the pungent odor of blood in the air, and he was just about to withdraw his arm when he felt something inside the giant lizard's head.

After some digging, he withdrew his hand with a palm-sized fleshy object held in his grasp, inside of which was a longan-sized yellowish-brown crystal that appeared to be the lizard's beast core.

On the other side, Shi Chuankong was keeping the giant centipede occupied, while Daoist Xie seized an opportunity to rush into its mouth, then slashed Thunderslash and Heavenslash through the air in unison to slice it apart from within its oral cavity.

Han Li then strode over and took one of Daoist Xie's sabers before forcing it into a gap between two of the scales on the centipede's head, then forcibly pried off one of the scales.

After exposing the flesh of the giant centipede, Han Li plunged the saber into its head, then dug around momentarily before pulling out another beast core.

Chapter 848: Long Road Ahead

"What are you doing with these beast cores, Brother Li? Surely they don't have much tool refinement value," Shi Chuankong asked with a puzzled expression.

"Why don't you take a look at it first?" Han Li replied with a smile, then tossed the beast core in his hand at Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong caught the beast core, then examined it momentarily before a hint of a surprise flashed through his eyes.

"This beast core contains a tremendous physical aura! Consuming it will definitely enhance one's physical constitution," Shi Chuankong said.

"That's right. Even though spiritual qi and devilish qi are completely absent in this place, it seems to have its own unique energy system," Han Li replied with a nod.

"This environment is most likely how these beasts were able to develop such formidable physical bodies," Shi Chuankong mused.

"The residents of this domain must be aware of the properties of these beast cores, and perhaps they'll collect these beast cores to use as a type of bodily refinement resource. In any case, it certainly couldn't hurt to collect them, and they could prove to be useful in the future," Han Li said.

"Exceptional foresight as usual, Brother Li. I wonder what the residents of this domain are like now that this place has been abandoned for so long," Shi Chuankong mused.

"Compared with the Immortal Realm, the people of the Holy Realm generally possess superior aptitude in bodily refinement. Given that one's cultivation base is useless here, I'm assuming all of the residents of this domain must place their focus solely on bodily refinement," Han Li speculated.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he released his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area.

In doing so, he discovered that while he could still use his spiritual sense here, it was also suppressed by the innate pressure in this domain, so his spiritual sensory range was reduced to only several dozen kilometers.

Moments later, he pulled out the sheet of beast hide that contained the map of the domain given to him by Shi Pokong, and Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie also gathered around to inspect the map together.

"I've just examined the surrounding area with my spiritual sense, and it seems like we're in this area on the map," Han Li said as he pointed at a loose scattering of islands on the edge of the map.

"The Gray Scale Islands... Looks like it's quite a secluded area," Daoist Xie remarked.

At the same time, Han Li's voice suddenly rang out in his mind, "Have you recalled anything now that we're in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, Brother Xie?"

"I'm sensing something, but it's all very indistinct, perhaps because we're still too far away, and I can't tell whether what I'm sensing is positive or negative," Daoist Xie replied through voice transmission.

"It looks like this place most likely has something to do with your amnesia. Are you getting a sense of which direction we should go in?" Han Li asked.

"According to what I can see on the map, I seem to be getting drawn to the central region of the domain, but I can't be sure," Daoist Xie replied.

"Right now, we still don't know where Violet Spirit is, so let's just go in that direction for now. If there are still residents in this domain, then they'll most likely also be gathered in the central region," Han Li said.

"Fellow Daoist Li, there's no spiritual qi in this place, and even though I have active Immortal Origin Stones in my body, I can only unleash some normal attacks and none of my lightning-attribute abilities. Once the immortal spiritual power in the Immortal Origin Stones run out, I'll fall into hibernation," Daoist Xie suddenly said.

"I figured that you would also be affected by the laws of this place. Whatever happens from here onward, try to stay out of battle as much as possible to avoid immortal spiritual power expenditure. Storage tools can't be used here, and I'm only carrying several mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones on me," Han Li said.

"I suppose that's all we can do for now. Thankfully, these Immortal Origin Stones will be enough to support me for some time," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

Right at this moment, Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly as he yelled, "Something's coming!"

Daoist Xie and Shi Chuankong immediately tensed up upon hearing this, and before long, the sound of rustling began to ring out from afar.

Three of them turned to that direction to find that a white line had appeared on the distant horizon, and it was slowly approaching them.

As it drew closer, the white line grew wider and wider, and it didn't take long before it had spread over the entire horizon.

"What the hell are those things?" Shi Chuankong murmured in an apprehensive voice.

Han Li focused his gaze on the white line to discover that it was a wave of countless fist-sized white crabs, all of which were eagerly scrambling over each other as they rushed toward the carcass of the giant lizard.

Just a single one of these crabs would've actually been rather adorable in appearance, but so many of them gathered in one place presented a harrowing sight to behold, and before long, it appeared as if the giant lizard's carcass had been covered in a moving white mat.

Some of the crabs had even burrowed their way into the carcass through the hole on its head, and no more than twenty seconds later, all of the flesh had been stripped from the giant lizard's carcass, leaving behind an impeccably clean skeleton.

If it weren't for the large volumes of yellowish-brown blood that had seeped into the ground, Han Li would've easily mistaken the carcass as one that had already been here for many years and been stripped down to its bones due to erosion.

A grim look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he reflexively tried to leap high up into the air, but he was instantly forced back down onto the ground by the spatial pressure in this place.

Clearly, it was going to take some time for them to grow accustomed to their inability to use immortal spiritual power and devilish power.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi, these White Armor Crabs are only scavengers, so they pose no threat to us," Daoist Xie suddenly said.

Sure enough, the white crabs were giving the three of them a wide berth, scurrying around them en route to the giant centipede carcass.

Once again, in the span of no more than twenty seconds, the entire carcass was also devoured.

"How do you know what these things are, Fellow Daoist Xie?" Shi Chuankong asked with a puzzled expression.

Daoist Xie faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "I'm not sure, I feel like I've seen them before."

Shi Chuankong was rendered speechless upon hearing this.

"Let's get out of here. Let's try and find some residents of this domain to see if we can gather any leads on Violet Spirit," Han Li said.

Shi Chuankong could see the concern on Han Li's face, and he consoled, "Don't be so worried, Brother Li. Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit was able to ascend from a lower realm just like you, and that's a reflection of her power and resourcefulness, so I'm sure she'll be fine even in this Scalptia Spatial Domain."

Shi Chuankong's words didn't offer much reassurance to Han Li, but he still nodded as he said, "Thank you Fellow Daoist Shi. If it wasn't for you, even getting into this place would've been a very difficult task for me."

"There's no need to thank me, think about how many times you've saved my life in the past! Even back in the Gray Realm, I've never seen you look so concerned, it looks like Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit really is extremely important to you. Let's just set off right away, I don't need any rest," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"We do indeed need to make haste. Right now, Weeping Soul is still laying unconscious in my domain treasure, and even though I've placed many pieces of Purple Sun Warm Jade in there and arranged for puppets to look after her, I won't be able to enter the domain as long as I'm in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so I won't know if something goes wrong or if the supply of Purple Sun Warm Jade runs out," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

"That's even more reason to remain calm and focused, Brother Li. This place is not like other places, and you won't be able to use the majority of your abilities here, so we have to proceed with caution," Shi Chuankong said.

"Let's keep going," Han Li replied with a nod, and with that, the three of them continued onward.

After crossing over a nearby ridge, a plain that was slanted slightly downward appeared. The terrain was relatively flat, and it stretched onward for hundreds of kilometers.

However, the earth was riddled with enormous cracks, and there wasn't any vegetation in sight. Occasionally, some dust would be thrown up into the air by a passing gust of wind, only to be instantly forced back down to the ground by the ever-present spatial pressure.

Han Li's trio made their way down from the ridge, then strode over the cracked earth, leaving three long trails of footsteps behind them.

Even though they couldn't fly, they were still traveling quite quickly on foot.

Along the way, they occasionally encountered some strange scaled beasts, but none of them took the initiative to attack them, so Han Li's trio left them alone.

At around dusk, the three of them arrived on the edge of an island.

At this point, the sun had already most likely set, and its dying rays basked the entire earth in an orange glow, while the sound of beastly roars began to ring out over the plain.

Han Li turned back to take a glance at the plain that they had just crossed over, then turned his gaze back forward with his brows tightly furrowed.

Beyond the edge of the island was a layer of indistinct black mist that resembled a cloud of smoke, separating the island that they were on from the neighboring one.

Chapter 849: Bird-hunting Trio

"It looks like it's not going to be easy to pass through here," Han Li remarked.

"The other island is only several thousand feet away, can we really not just jump across?" Shi Chuankong asked.

In response, Daoist Xie merely picked up a rock from the ground, then hurled it at the opposing island.

The rock sped through the air, but as soon as it flew into the air above the black mist, it abruptly stopped cold in its tracks.

Immediately thereafter, it was as if it had suddenly been slapped down by an invisible hand, and it was sent plummeting down into the mist.

Han Li's trio listened intently for a while, but they couldn't hear the sound of the rock landing, and Shi Chuankong looked down as he remarked, "It seems like whatever's down there, it's extremely deep."

"My guess is that there's nothing but boundless space beneath this black mist. If we fall into it, we'll plummet perpetually through space, and there's no telling when we'll reach the bottom. In fact, there's a very good chance that there is no bottom," Han Li speculated as he peered into the black mist.

"Doesn't that mean that we're trapped on this island? It seems like the beasts on the island are even more active at night, so things will only get more dangerous from here onward," Shi Chuankong said with tightly furrowed brows.

Han Li was just about to respond when the sound of flapping wings suddenly rang out form the opposing island, and he hurriedly cast his gaze in that direction to find a strange bird that was around twenty feet tall flying toward them over the black mist.

The bird had a bulky body that was covered in stiff azure feathers, with a long neck and a disproportionately large head, and its wingspan was around ten feet wide.

It was flying in a very strange fashion in that not only was it flapping its wings with all its might, it was also frantically stepping down onto the space beneath it with its talons, looking extremely awkward and uncoordinated.

However, its methods were clearly effective, and with each step that it took, the air beneath its talons would explode to create a burst of upward propulsion force that counteracted the spatial pressure above the black mist, thereby allowing it to fly over the area.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he yelled, "Those azure feathers on this bird's body seem to be able to drastically reduce the spatial pressure exerted upon it, thereby allowing it to fly over the black mist. If we can capture it, perhaps we can ride it to the other side."

As soon as his voice trailed off, hundreds of the same birds flew out of the black mist, and all of them were flying in the same frantic and uncoordinated manner toward the island that Han Li's trio was on.

The birds paid no heed to the trio, displaying no fear at all, and they were galloping toward the mountain ridge at the center of the island.

Han Li's trio hurriedly ducked and weaved from side to side to evade the flock of birds, and before long, all of the birds had flown past them.

"With that many of them, there will definitely be enough for us to use!" Shi Chuankong said with an exultant smile.

"Let's go after them," Han Li said, and the three of them immediately set off after the flock of birds.

Even as the birds were galloping along the ground, the same explosions of air were erupting beneath their talons with every single step, propelling them forward at an extraordinary speed.

In contrast, Han Li's trio were only able to rely on their own physical prowess, and they were being outsped.

Han Li was still able to somewhat keep up, but at this point, Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie had already been left close to ten kilometers behind.

Over the course of the chase, the sun completely set, and stars began to appear in the sky.

Even as Han Li continued to gallop along, he was constantly scouring his surroundings in a wary fashion.

On a barren plain, one dark shadow after another popped up, seemingly out of nowhere, and they came in all shapes, forms, and sizes, but all of them were laying quietly on the ground, seemingly waiting for something.

Han Li was rather bewildered to see this, but he continued his pursuit of the flock of birds without pause.

By the time the pursuit reached the mountain range, night had already completely fallen. There wasn't a single cloud in the sky, and a lone moon was hanging high up above, surrounded by countless bright stars.

Under the moonlight night sky, Han Li's trio was treated to an astonishing sight.

Countless White Armor Crabs had appeared all over the entire mountain ridge from top to bottom, and they even spilled out onto the flatter areas outside of the ridge.

At this moment, all of their shells were gleaming with specks of hazy white light that resembled tiny lamp flames, and it was as if a starry night sky had appeared on the plain to mirror the one up above, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

Han Li was standing on the ridge as he observed the surrounding area, and he discovered that all of the creatures on the island were also glowing with the same specks of white light, except most of them were concentrated on their heads.

At the same time, he could sense a faint yet familiar power from the light.

It was none other than the starpower that he had drawn upon while cultivating the Great Universe Origin Arts.

The more Han Li saw, the more bewildered he became. Could it be that this starpower was what allowed all of these creatures to survive and cultivate in the bleak environment of the Scalptia Spatial Domain?

Right at this moment, a string of loud cracks rang out, and Han Li hurriedly turned to discover the flock of strange birds that had flown to this area preying on the White Armor Crabs on the ground with their long beaks.

A small disturbance ran through the cluster of White Armor Crabs, but they didn't flee en masse, nor did they retaliate against the flock of birds.

More commotion was also ringing out further away, and Han Li could see that some of the larger beasts had begun preying on the smaller beasts present.

"So they're here to feed on the White Armor Crabs. Should we go after them now?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Let's wait for a bit longer. If we strike now, we could attract a lot of unnecessary trouble. Let's approach them slowly, then find a suitable location to strike from," Han Li said.

With that, the three of them each snuck over to a vantage point before hiding behind some cover so that they were out of sight.

Around an hour later, the flock of birds seemed to have had their fill, and they began galloping back in the same direction that they had come from.

Han Li immediately made a hand signal to Shi Chuankong upon seeing this, and the latter instantly sprang into action, springing up into the air to pursue the flock of birds.

Right as one of the birds ran past him, he attempted to pounce onto its back, but the bird suddenly dodged to the side, then raised one of its thick and strong legs before aiming a kick at Shi Chuankong's chest.

Despite the bird's rather dumb and bulky appearance, it was extraordinarily fast and agile, and Shi Chuankong was caught completely off guard, taking a kick straight to the chest.

A series of profound acupoints instantly lit up over his chest, and his entire body seemed to have been enshrouded in a layer of hazy light.

Right as the ninth acupoint on his chest lit up, a loud explosion rang out, and a burst of invisible force erupted out of a small hole on the underside of the bird's food before exploding right in front of Shi Chuankong's chest.

Shi Chuankong felt a burst of tremendous force crash into his chest, striking him with a sense of asphyxiation, and he was launched back through the air before crashing heavily down onto the ground, only drawing to a halt after rolling end over end around a dozen times in a row.

On the other side, Han Li was also just about to jump onto a bird's back, but upon seeing what had happened to Shi Chuankong, he immediately ducked down preemptively. Sure enough, the bird aimed a kick at him as well, but he was able to evade the attack, then slid right along the bird's body before straddling onto its back.

The bird shuddered slightly under his weight, but then immediately stabilized itself and continued to gallop onward.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie rushed over to examine Shi Chuankong's condition, and the latter had already risen to his feet and was dusting himself off.

It appeared that he hadn't sustained any injuries, but there was a slightly awkward look on his face as he said to Daoist Xie, "There's an opening on the underside of these birds' feet that can release bursts of powerful force. No wonder they were able to run over that area with the black mist."

He then turned his attention to Han Li, upon which he discovered that Han Li was straddled atop his bird's back with his arms wound tightly around its long neck.

His body was bobbing up and down in a rather comical fashion as the bird galloped along, but overall, he appeared to be quite stable, and the bird didn't seem to have been down much by his added weight.

However, right at this moment, the bird's head suddenly swiveled around close to 180 degrees, and it pecked down at Han Li's left eye at an extraordinary speed.

Chapter 850: Resourceful Innovation

Han Li was clearly prepared for a sneak attack, and he laid back to evade the bird's beak strike.

However, before he had a chance to stabilize himself, the bird suddenly stomped its talons into the ground and sprang up into the air. As it began its descent, it abruptly spread its wings, thrusting Han Li's legs up into the air, and he almost fell off its back as a result.

In response, Han Li pushed off with both hands against the bird's back, launching himself up into the air before quickly falling back down thanks to the spatial pressure in the environment.

As he did so, Han Li intentionally increased the force of his descent, plummeting heavily down onto the bird's back.

The bird was also in the process of a descent, and with Han Li falling onto its back with such immense force, it let loose an involuntary squawk before crashing to the ground with a loud thump.

A crater that was hundreds of feet in size appeared on the ground, and even with its tremendous leg strength, the bird was unable to remain on its talons, kneeling to the bottom of the crater.

All of the creatures that were basking in starlight in the surrounding area hurriedly dispersed in alarm, while all of the other birds fled in all directions.

Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie rushed over to the edge of the crater to find Han Li straddled atop the bird with one hand pressed against its head and his other hand gently stroking the feathers on its back.

Initially, the bird struggled vehemently, but a few moments later, its struggles ceased, and it began gently rubbing its head against Han Li's hand in an affectionate manner.

Han Li gently patted the bird on the back, and it stood up again, then bent its legs slightly, following which a loud explosion of air rang out as it leaped out of the crater with Han Li on its back.

After jumping out of the crater, the bird galloped over the plain with Han Li on its back for a while, and it was even faster than before. While it galloped along, it flapped its wings while blasting air out of the holes on the underside of its feet, and it was able to fly about a foot above the ground.

After briefly testing out the bird's abilities, Han Li instructed it to land in between Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie, following which he jumped down from its back and said, "This bird doesn't seem to have a name, so I'll call it a Hover Flight Bird. It's extremely difficult to tame, and once captured, it must immediately be subdued using spiritual sense."

"No wonder you were stroking its head earlier, you were brainwashing it!" Shi Chuankong jibed.

"As you just saw, this bird is capable of flying with one person on its back, and it should be able to reach the other island just fine, even with the added load. On top of that, it's also quite fast, so it makes for a very good steed," Han Li said.

"That's great! In that case, we're killing two birds with one stone," Shi Chuankong said with an elated smile.

"Brother Shi, I saw some profound acupoints light upon your chest earlier when you were being kicked by one of the other birds. Are you also using some type of bodily refinement cultivation art?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Beings of our holy race are born with powerful bodies, so we don't have to focus as much on bodily refinement as humans. However, the laws of space that I'm cultivating are quite special, and it required me to further strengthen my body. On top of that, my physical constitution was enhanced even further thanks to my breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage," Shi Chuankong explained.

"That's good to hear. I presume you must be very confident in your own physical body, given you were willing to come on this trip with me," Han Li said with a smile.

As for exactly how many profound acupoints Shi Chuankong had opened up, Han Li didn't pry as the subject potentially concerned secrets of Shi Chuankong's cultivation.

"I wouldn't dare to say I'm very confident, but I should be able to lend you some assistance here and there," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"Right now, we only have one Hover Flight Bird. Are we going to take turns riding it to the other island?" Daoist Xie asked.

"Let's not do anything else for tonight. Even though the creatures on the island are very active at night, it appears that they've only come out to absorb starpower, so they shouldn't pose much of a threat. We don't know what things are like on the other island, so let's rest here for tonight," Han Li decided after some contemplation.

"That does sound like a safer course of action," Shi Chuankong agreed with a nod.

Thus, the three of them sat down with their legs crossed on the slightly slanted ground at the foot of the mountain ridge before closing their eyes to cultivate.

Han Li attempted to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, only to discover that he was unable to draw upon his own immortal spiritual power, as if it had congealed within his body.

A wry smile appeared on his face as he opened his eyes, then turned to take a glance at Daoist Xie and Shi Chuankong, only to discover that they weren't giving off any spiritual power fluctuations, either.

Han Li closed his eyes again and continued to meditate, and the night steadily wore on.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open as he took a glance up at the sky above.

All of the stars in the sky were glowing extremely brightly, to the point that the island was illuminated to be as bright as day, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

After looking up at the stars for some time, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he began to channel his Great Universe Origin Arts.

As soon as he did this, a series of profound acupoints lit up over his body one after another, and they were also glowing just as radiantly as the stars up above.

Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie both opened their eyes to look at Han Li upon sensing this, and the former was looking on with keen interest, while the latter closed his eyes in a disinterested manner.

Some time later, Han Li heaved a forlorn sigh before opening his eyes.

He had already achieved full mastery of the Great Universe Origin Arts, so he was unable to channel the cultivation art to absorb any more starpower.

The profound acupoints all over his body faded at his behest, with the exception of a single one on his chest.

After some contemplation, Han Li pulled out a longan-sized yellowish-brown crystal, and it was none other than the giant lizard's beast core.

Compared with back when it had first been pulled out of the lizard's body, the beast core's aura had already abated significantly, but the starpower flashing within it was only growing brighter and brighter.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he held the beast core in his hand and attempted to refine it, only to recall that without any immortal spiritual power, this was an impossible task.

He slapped a hand to his own forehead with a self-deprecating smile, and right as he was about to stow the beast core away again, he caught a glimpse of the Hover Flight Bird out of the corner of his eye, and he suddenly recalled the scene of the birds feeding on the White Armor Crabs.

After a brief hesitation, he tossed the beast core into his own mouth before swallowing it.

As soon as the beast core entered his stomach, he immediately felt a burst of heat begin to travel through his lower abdomen before transforming into a faint burst of power that began to travel toward his leg.

He hurriedly looked down to discover that a slight change was taking place within a brand new acupoint on the inside of his leg.

It was only a minute change, but Han Li was ecstatic to see this as he could sense that a brand new profound acupoint was showing signs of opening up in his body, and most importantly, this change didn't appear to be accompanied by any negative side effects.

A hint of surprise flashed through Shi Chuankong's face as he watched Han Li swallow the beast core, and he approached Han Li before asking, "What are you doing, Brother Li?"

"Do you still have the beast core that I gave you earlier?" Han Li asked with an eager expression.

"I do," Shi Chuankong replied as he hurriedly pulled out the centipede's beast core before handing it to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the beast core before examining it momentarily, then swallowed this one as well.

Immediately thereafter, the same burst of heat reappeared in his lower abdomen, then also transformed into a faint burst of power that surged toward the new acupoint in his leg.

"It's not enough, I need more!" Han Li said in an excited manner.

"What's going on, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked with slightly furrowed brows

"Those two beast cores contain starpower and can open up profound acupoints! We won't be able to refine them, but we can absorb the starpower within them by directly devouring them," Han Li explained.

"Is that true?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed as a hint of excitement appeared on his face as well.

"All of these creatures have clearly come out at night to absorb starpower. Just capture one of them and harvest their beast core, and you'll be able to see for yourself," Han Li replied with a smile.

Shi Chuankong immediately rushed away into the distance upon hearing this, and before long, he returned with the carcass of a scaled feline creature that was around ten feet in length.

Shi Chuankong tossed the carcass onto the ground, then split its head open with his black saber before pulling out a tiny core around the size of a pea.

"These small guys only have tiny beast cores in their heads, while the larger ones are quite rare and extremely fast, so I wasn't able to catch any of them," Shi Chuankong complained.

"It's fine, give this one a try first," Han Li said with a smile.

Chapter 851: Without a Trace

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, then sat down with his legs crossed, and he swallowed the beast core after rubbing it clean before closing his eyes.

Moments later, he reopened his eyes as he asked with slightly furrowed brows, "Did I do something wrong just now, Brother Li? Why can't I sense anything happening in my body?"

"The beast core that you just swallowed was far smaller than the other two. It appears that the more fearsome a beast is, the larger its beast core would be," Han Li analyzed.

"That's probably a reasonable guess. However, looking at the creatures on this island, it appears that the lizard and the centipede that we killed may be the two most powerful beasts here," Shi Chuankong remarked.

"It's fine. Right now, our priority is to cover more ground, and we can just try again when another opportunity arises in the future," Han Li replied with a nod.

"If any powerful beasts try to get in our way from here onward, then I'm not going to spare it!" Shi Chuankong chuckled as he eagerly rubbed his hands together.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before returning to seated meditation.

The next morning.

Han Li was riding the Hover Flight Bird on the edge of the island, and it was rushing toward the area filled with black mist with a run-up of roughly a hundred meters.

With each step the bid took, a loud explosion would ring out beneath its talons, sending dust erupting in all directions.

The more it accelerated, the larger its strides became, and upon reaching the edge of the island, it abruptly sprang up into the air, launching itself into the air above the black mist, where it spread its massive wings.

The surrounding space was filled with a burst of spatial pressure that was far more pronounced than before, and it seemed to only be growing stronger.

Blasts of air were constantly erupting out of the holes on the underside of the bird's feet, and it was also flapping its wings incessantly as it galloped forward with much difficulty.

Flying over this area was quite difficult to begin with, and with the added burden of Han Li on its back, the bird was clearly flying at a lower altitude than before, only just barely staying above the black mist.

Han Li pressed his own body tightly against the bird's back, doing his best to hide himself beneath its wings, and at the same time, his entire body was tensed up as he looked forward in a wary fashion.

Thankfully, the distance between the two islands was very short, and the Hover Flight Bird was very familiar with this trip, clearly having already made it countless times before, so it quickly arrived on the opposing island with Han Li.

Han Li jumped down from the bird's back upon reaching the island, and as soon as he landed on the ground, he could immediately sense that the spatial pressure here was stronger than before.

After taking a moment to acclimate himself to these new conditions, he patted the Hover Flight Bird, sending it back to the other side to transport Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie across as well.

After reaching the island, the two of them also detected this increase in spatial pressure, much to their dismay.

"This island is a lot larger than the previous one, and the spatial pressure on the island also seems to be a lot stronger," Shi Chuankong remarked.

"Indeed. I presume the creatures on the island will only be more formidable, so we're going to have to proceed with caution from here onward," Han Li said in a grim voice as he gently stroked the Hover Flight Bird's head.

"It's all thanks to this little guy that we were able to make it here at all. We should find out where these birds come from and capture two more. We'll be able to travel faster with these birds as our steeds, and that'll allow us to find any potential settlements of residents faster," Shi Chuankong suggested.

"I've already scoured the area with my spiritual sense, and there's a canyon a few dozen kilometers away from here. The Hover Flight Birds from last night are residing there," Han Li said.

Around half a day later, the three of them flew out of the canyon, with each of them rising atop a Hover Flight Bird, pursued by hundreds of other furious Hover Flight Birds.

……

Over two months flew by in a flash.

Three Hover Flight Birds were gathered together in a hilly area, pecking incessantly at the ground.

Under a giant rock not far away laid the carcasses of two scaled sawtooth mammoths that were each over a thousand feet tall, and there was blood still trickling out of their mouths.

Each of them had a large hole on the top of its head, and the beast cores inside their bodies had already been dug out.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were seated on the giant rock several meters apart with their backs facing each other, and all of their profound acupoints were glowing faintly.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie was standing off to the side, looking into the distance in an expressionless manner.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li and Shi Chuankong opened their eyes, and the former exhaled as he said, "It seems like these beast cores really can increase the amount of starpower in our bodies and enhance our physical constitutions, but they're not enough on their own to open up new profound acupoints."

"Indeed. Even so, after devouring so many beast cores up to this point, both of us have benefitted immensely. At the very least, we're far more resistant to the spatial pressure in this domain than before. I must say, devouring beast cores here is a far faster form of physical cultivation than any physical cultivation methods that I can think of in the outside world," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"If we can devour some more beast cores, we'll be better equipped to deal with the spatial pressure once we reach even larger landmasses," Han Li said.

"Fellow Daoist Li, those giant scorpions are catching up to us again. It looks like they'll reach us in more than thirty seconds," Daoist Xie suddenly called out.

"What a pain in the backside! If it isn't for the fact that their beast cores have no value, we should've eradicated all of them long ago," Shi Chuankong spat through gritted teeth.

"Just ignore them. We're about to reach the landmass soon, and they won't be able to get to us there," Han Li said with a smile.

With that, the three of them got on their Hover Flight Birds and continued onward.

……

One morning, several months later.

A scaled panther-like beast was prowling along the edge of a barren desert, tearing at the flesh of a giant lizard that was already long dead.

All of a sudden, its ears perked up as it raised its head in a wary fashion and began peering into the mist on the edge of the wilderness.

A huge shadow was currently making its way through the mist.

The panther-like beast hurriedly ran back close to a thousand feet upon seeing this, then turned back to see what was happening.

Right at this moment, a giant dark green turtle that was over a hundred feet tall flew out of the black mist, then slowly descended onto the edge of the desert.

The turtle's shell had some very peculiar patterns, and it was also giving off a faint sheen, reflecting specks of green light under the morning sun.

There were three men standing on the giant turtle's back, and they were none other than Han Li's trio.

Daoist Xie was scouring the surrounding area with an indifferent gaze, and as soon as he caught sight of the panther-like beast, the latter immediately fled into the distance, abandoning the giant lizard carcass.

After several months of travel, Han Li's trio had finally left the Gray Scale Islands and arrived on the Brown Valley Continent.

During their travels, they had done their best to avoid powerful creatures, but they were still attacked no fewer than a hundred times. On the majority of occasions, they were able to get away and avoid a battle thanks to the Hover Flight Birds' speed, but there had been some unavoidable confrontations that they had no choice but to engage in.

Among them, there had been two particularly grueling battles, one of which was a battle against a pair of giant armadillo-like creatures, which they were able to slay to procure a pair of beast cores the size of an infant's fist.

During the other battle, they were attacked by an earthworm that was over a thousand feet in length, which had suddenly sprung up out of the ground to devour all three Hover Flight Birds.

Not only did the earthworm possess a tremendously powerful body, it was also extremely cunning, immediately burrowing into the ground at the first sign of danger.

In the end, Han Li's trio was finally able to leave its territory after close to half a month of cautious travel.

After that, the three of them had traveled for over a month before encountering this creature, which Han Li had named the "Space Walking Turtle".

Just like Hover Flight Birds, this turtle was somehow able to resist the spatial pressure in this domain thanks to certain special properties of its shell, and it was able to traverse through even the areas enshrouded in black mist.

It was thanks to this Space Walking Turtle that they were able to traverse through the misty area between the final island and this continent, an area that spanned close to ten thousand feet.

At this moment, the three of them were all seated on the turtle's back in silence, not because there was nothing to say, but instead because they were all silently withstanding the spatial pressure on this continent, which was over ten times more potent than before.

Under such immense pressure, Han Li felt as if all of his internal organs had been squished together, and his ears were also ringing every time he took a strained breath.

Scales had already appeared over Shi Chuankong's body as he revealed part of his true devilish form to help him withstand the pressure.

In contrast, Daoist Xie was faring much better than the two of them thanks to his puppet body.

On this continent, Han Li's spiritual sense was being suppressed even further, to the point that his spiritual sensory range was only around thirty to forty kilometers in radius.

Up to this point, they hadn't encountered any residents of this domain, nor any signs left behind by Violet Spirit, and he was beginning to grow a little concerned.

This domain was far more massive than he anticipated, and it also had a terrible environment that rendered one's cultivation base completely useless, so one could only deal with the hazards present in this place with their physical prowess.

It had already been over a century since Violet Spirit was cast into this place, and he couldn't help but fear for her safety.

Right at this moment, he suddenly detected something, and the Space Walking Turtle beneath him also drew to a halt at his behest.

Chapter 852: Leads

"What is it, Brother Li? Are we being attacked?" Shi Chuankong asked, while Daoist Xie also turned to him with an inquisitive look.

Han Li remained silent as he cast his gaze toward a small mountain several kilometers away.

Shi Chuankong also turned his attention to the same mountain, but wasn't able to see anything special about it.

Before Shi Chuankong had a chance to ask any further questions, Han Li suddenly patted the shell of the Space Walking Turtle, and it resumed its flight at his behest, with its feet gliding through the air like oars.

Its speed was inferior to that of the Hover Flight Bird, but not by much.

Around a thousand feet away from the small mountain, Han Li leaped up into the air, then crashed heavily to the ground under the immense spatial pressure.

However, he didn't even take a moment to steady himself before rushing up the small mountain as quickly as he could, and Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie exchanged a perplexed glance with each other before also jumping down from the turtle's back in pursuit of Han Li.

The mountain was no more than a thousand feet tall, and Han Li had rushed all the way to the entrance of an obscure cave that was around half the height of a grown man halfway up the mountain.

Shi Chuankong caught up to him before Daoist Xie, but before he had a chance to say anything, Han Li had already squeezed his way into the hole.

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly also followed along.

After squeezing into the hole and passing through a tight passageway, he emerged into a spacious area around twice the size of the average room.

The ceiling was also extremely tall, and there were several large holes in it, allowing the natural light from outside to filter through and illuminate the entire cave.

Shi Chuankong looked around to discover four strange-looking bodies on the ground in the cave, and Han Li was crouched down beside one of the bodies, seemingly examining something.

Shi Chuankong also began to inspect the bodies himself, and upon closer inspection, he discovered that two of the "bodies" weren't actually bodies. Instead, they were a pair of humanoid puppets, except their heads had been smashed, and large holes had also been punched into their chests.

As for the other two true bodies, their upper bodies were bared to reveal a layer of gray scales, and they appeared rather withered and dried out, perhaps because they had been dead for quite some time, or perhaps it had something to do with their cause of death.

Before long, Daoist Xie had also entered the cave, and he asked in a puzzled manner, "What are these things?"

"They're most likely fugitives that were exiled into this place," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Brother Shi, can you see anything from these bodies?" Han Li asked as he rose to his feet with tightly clenched fists.

"Two of these are bodies, while the other two are puppets, and judging from their injuries, they seemed to have killed each other, indicating that they're most likely from two opposing forces," Shi Chuankong deduced.

"I'm thinking the exact same thing. I think they were fighting over someone here," Han Li said with a grim expression.

A look of realization appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

"You don't mean..."

"That's right, I've found something of Violet Spirit's here," Han Li confirmed as he spread a hand open to reveal a black veil usually worn over a woman's face.

"Are you sure this belongs to Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Her blood is on this veil, and there's no way I'll misidentify her aura. The battle that took place here was most likely over her, so she's probably been abducted by whichever side that came out on top," Han Li said.

"The state of these bodies indicates that they're already long dead. I wonder when Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit was here," Shi Chuankong mused.

"That's impossible to tell for now. On the way here, I didn't discover any trace of her, nor did I detect her aura, so there's a very good chance that she didn't enter the Scalptia Spatial Domain from the entrance in the Black Water Region. Perhaps there are other entrances to this domain in the Devil Realm," Han Li sighed.

"That's definitely a real possibility. I'm sure Lady Ju wasn't willing to tell Pokong exactly where Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit entered the Scalptia Spatial Domain from. If we had known that this was a possibility, we should've asked Xu Fu before we came in here," Shi Chuankong mused with a concerned expression.

"I did consider it, but there wouldn't have been any point. If Violet Spirit really was sent into the Scalptia Spatial Domain through an entrance overseen by him, would he have dared to admit it if he became aware of our objective? He would've either only lied to cover for himself, or even fed us false information," Han Li said.

"Well, the good thing is that we have some leads now. As long as we can track down one of the two forces that were here, we'll be able to find out more information about Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit's whereabouts," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li offered no response. It was clear that Violet Spirit had suffered some form of injury here, and that left him feeling very concerned.

"Let's go. Seeing as we've confirmed that she's on this continent, it's only a matter of time before we find her," Han Li said, then made his way out of the cave.

……

Half a month later.

Han Li's trio arrived in a mountainous area, and it was near impossible for the Space Walking Turtle to make any progress here as it could only hover a few dozen feet above the ground, so Han Li had no choice but to release it and continue on foot.

One day, at around noon, the trio arrived at a long and thin valley, where an elated look suddenly appeared on Han Li's face.

"Have you found something?" Shi Chuankong immediately asked upon noticing Han Li's expression.

Han Li made a quieting gesture, then began to quickly move to his left while also waving for Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie to follow along.

Before long, the three of them had traveled close to ten kilometers and arrived on the summit of a small mountain, where they hid behind a large rock, peering out at a col that was several dozen kilometers away.

There was a fierce battle taking place within the col, and they didn't get any closer for fear of being detected by the combatants.

One one side was a giant tiger-like beast that was over three hundred feet in length and around seventy to eighty feet tall. Its entire body was covered in huge dark brown scales that were giving off a metallic sheen, and its legs were incredibly thick and strong, while its paws were tipped with scythe-like claws that presented a fearsome sight to behold.

What was particularly eye-catching were the nine black bone spikes that resembled giant spears growing on the creature's back.

At this moment, the tiger-like beast was locked in battle against seven or eight men with very dark and coarse skin, and they were incredibly muscular and tall, significantly taller than even Han Li.

They were clad in suits of crude, gray bone armor, and the weapons that they were wielding also appeared to have been fashioned from some type of beast bone.

Despite its enormous frame, the tiger-like beast was remarkably agile, attacking with its fangs, claws, and its tail.

A series of craters had been smashed into the ground, and the shockwaves erupting from the battle had sliced numerous deep gashes into the nearby mountain faces.

The armored men had specks of light glowing all over their bodies, and they were able to move so quickly that they transformed into gray blurs, allowing them to evade all of the tiger-like beast's attacks.

Compared with their movements, the giant beast's attacks were made to look very clumsy and maladroit.

The specks of light on the bodies of those men were none other than profound acupoints, and even the one with the least profound acupoints among them had opened up over ten, while their leader had a total of fifty to sixty profound acupoints distributed over his body.

On top of that, the placement of his profound acupoints were highly specialized, with some on his chest and abdomen, while the rest, consisting of close to half, were gathered in his right arm.

"Are these fugitives that were exiled into the Scalptia Spatial Domain? We've finally run into some! Should we go and meet them?" Shi Chuankong asked in an elated manner.

"The fact that they were exiled here indicates that they're not good people, so I think it's best to stay put and observe for now," Han Li replied, and Shi Chuankong nodded in agreement.

The armorclad men were constantly moving around the tiger-like beast, striking its body with their bone weapons whenever the opportunity arose.

The bone weapons appeared to be quite crude, but were extremely sharp, and they were able to slice through even the scales on the giant beast's body to inflict long gashes.

As more and more gashes were inflicted onto the giant beast's body, its scales were quickly stained red, and it was moving far slower than before.

It attempted to escape on several occasions, but was unable to break out of the encirclement, and it had begun panting heavily.

All of a sudden, the giant beast let loose a thunderous roar, and its eyes began to glow crimson like a pair of red lanterns, while the nine bone spikes on its back began trembling and buzzing incessantly.

"Look out, it's about to use its trump card!" one of the armorclad men warned.

The leader of the ground immediately pounced on this opportunity, rushing over to the tiger-like beast before swinging the giant bone sword that he was wielding down upon the giant beast's shoulder.

A gruesome gash that was dozens of feet in length was instantly sliced into the giant beast's shoulder, and blood came gushing out in a frenzy.

The tiger-like beast howled in agony, then turned to the leader of the group before letting loose a thunderous roar, and the nine bone spikes on its back began vibrating rapidly before collectively hurtling toward him as nine black blurs.

Chapter 853: Daoist Xie's Capture

The nine bone spikes produced a shrieking sound as they hurtled through the air, but the man seemed to have already anticipated this, and he swung his bone sword through the air to deflect the oncoming bone spikes.

A string of loud metallic clangs rang out, and all nine bone spikes were sent flying in different directions, but the giant bone sword in the man's hand was also knocked out of his grasp.

However, the man didn't back down at all, and he stomped a foot down onto the ground, causing the earth to shatter beneath his feet.

The force of the stomp propelled him up into the air, and in the next instant, he had already arrived above the giant tiger's head.

At the same time, the profound acupoints on his right arm began glowing radiantly, and he plunged his arm straight at the giant tiger's forehead.

A loud and gruesome crunch rang out, and his arm was able to pierce straight through the skull of the giant tiger until the entire arm was embedded into the giant beast's head.

The giant tiger let loose an earth-shattering roar, then swayed a few times before finally collapsing to the ground.

Both Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, and they exchanged an astonished glance with each other.

While the two of them were confident that they could've also defeated that giant tiger, there was no way that they would've been able to do so with such ease.

Inside the col, a chorus of cheers rang out as the giant tiger collapsed to the ground.

The man who had dealt the killing blow pulled out his arm, and it was covered in blood and intracranial fluids.

With a swing of his arm, all of that was shaken off, and he spread his hand open to reveal a fist-sized beast core that was giving off radiant white light.

A pleased look appeared on the man's face at the sight of the white beast core, and he placed it into a beast hide pouch hanging from his waist.

A young man with an ox horn tattoo on his face retrieved the man's bone sword, then offered it up with both hands as he said with a fawning smile, "Your War Dagger Profound Arts are becoming more and more fearsome, Brother Chen Yang. Even a Sword Scale Tiger can't withstand a single hit from you now. At this rate, it won't be long before you accumulate enough accolade points for a four-star badge. I hope you won't forget us when that time comes."

The other men in the group collected the nine bone spikes, then also began flattering their leader.

"As long as you serve me well, all of you will be rewarded for your efforts," Chen Yang promised as he took his sword back, and everyone else hurriedly expressed their gratitude.

"Alright, hurry up and dissect this Sword Scale Tiger and pull out all of the usable star bones, then return to the stronghold. Our hunting trip ends here for today," Chen Yang instructed.

"What about you, Brother Chen?" one of the man asked.

"I still have some matters to take care of, so just go ahead without me," Chen Yang replied as he turned his gaze to the spot where Han Li's trio was hiding.

"He's spotted us! Run!" Han Li immediately said before rushing away into the distance as quickly as he could, followed closely by Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie.

The three of them were rushing toward a mountain range up ahead, hoping that the complex terrain inside the mountain range would deter Chen Yang from giving chase.

Chen Yang gave a cold harrumph as he set off in pursuit of Han Li's trio, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye, while the other men in the col looked on with perplexed expressions.

However, they did as they were told, dissecting the Sword Scale Tiger carcass before quickly pulling out four bones that were glowing faintly with white light.

One of the men pulled out a large pouch that he used to store the four bones and the nine bone spikes, following which the group of men departed.

……

Han Li's trio was traversing through the mountain range in an extremely agile fashion, but Chen Yang was significantly faster than them, and the gap between them was rapidly shrinking.

Before long, the two parties were separated by only several kilometers.

Han Li could sense Chen Yang rapidly getting closer, but he remained calm and composed as he said, "It looks like we won't be able to get away."

After exchanging a glance with Shi Chuankong, the two of them suddenly drew to a halt in a clearing.

Shortly thereafter, a gray shadow rushed onto the scene, then stopped not far away from them to reveal Chen Yang.

"Keep going! Why did you stop?" Chen Yang jeered with a mocking sneer on his face.

"We have no intention of causing any offense. We heard the sounds of your battle from earlier, so we were curious and decided to take a look," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Puppet City scoundrels! At least put that puppet away before you try and lie to me!" Chen Yang sneered as he took a glance at Daoist Xie, then pounced forward as he made a grabbing motion with his right hand.

All of the air within a radius of several hundred feet rumbled violently, forming white air currents that were visible even to the naked eye.

The white air currents converged to form a giant white hand that was over a hundred feet in size, and it came swooping down upon Han Li's trio.

Han Li was rather perplexed about what Chen Yang had just said, but in this situation, he had no choice but to retaliate, and all thirty-six of his profound acupoints lit up as he threw a punch up at the giant white hand.

At the same time, Shi Chuankong drew his black saber before slashing it upward, instantly releasing a black saber projection amid an ear-piercing screech.

Two resounding booms rang out as a huge hole and a long gash were inflicted upon the giant white hand, causing most of it to explode, but a small part of it still survived and grabbed onto Daoist Xie before returning to Chen Yang's side like lightning.

Chen Yang was rather surprised to see Daoist Xie being captured by him without putting up any resistance, while Han Li pounced at Chen Yang before launching both fists at his chest.

Shi Chuankong also sprang forward through the air, arriving on the other side of Chen Yang before slashing his saber down toward Chen Yang's shoulder like lightning.

In the face of their attacks, Chen Yang remained completely unfazed as he lashed out with both arms like lightning, with his left hand meeting Han Li's fists, while his right swept toward Shi Chuankong's black saber.

Two bursts of tremendous force erupted out of his arms, and a thunderous boom rang out as Chen Yang's left arm clashed against Han Li's fists.

Han Li immediately felt a burst of searing pain shoot through his fists, as if the bones in his hands were about to break, and at the same time, he was sent flying back like a cannonball.

Simultaneously, all of the profound acupoints on Chen Yang's right fist began glowing radiantly, making his arm resemble a divine weapon, and as soon as his right arm clashed against Shi Chuankong's black saber, the latter was instantly snapped into two with a faint crack.

Shi Chuankong was astonished to see this. The black saber was a graded devilish treasure that had been refined using exceptional materials, yet it had been snapped as if it were nothing more than a twig!

Chen Yang's right arm continued to sweep from left to right, swinging toward Shi Chuankong's chest as fast as lightning.

Shi Chuankong let loose a loud roar as he stomped a foot down onto the ground to send himself shooting back in retreat, and at the same time, over forty silver profound acupoints emerged over his chest and abdomen, while a thick silver film of light appeared over his entire body.

This was none other than this True Extreme Film, and in contrast with Han Li's smooth True Extreme Film, this one was riddled with spikes like a hedgehog.

Chen Yang paid no heed to Shi Chuankong's spiky True Extreme Film as he slammed his right arm into Shi Chuankong's chest, and the True Extreme Film was torn apart with ease, while Chen Yang's arm remained completely unscathed.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding boom rang out as Shi Chuankong was sent flying back through the air, then slammed heavily into a nearby mountain face to create a huge crater.

A long gash had been sliced into the True Extreme Film in front of his chest, and a wound so deep that bone was visible through it had also been inflicted onto his chest.

This wasn't a particularly severe injury for Shi Chuankong, so he was able to instantly spring back to his feet, but there was an alarmed look in his eyes, and he didn't dare to unleash any further attacks.

Han Li's expression also darkened slightly upon seeing this.

Even though he had only made contact with Chen Yang's left arm, the force of the clash had left his entire body feeling numb, and even now, he was still feeling a little dizzy.

After forcing back Han Li and Shi Chuankong, Chen Yang took a glance at the snapped black saber in Shi Chuankong's hand, then turned his gaze to Daoist Xie before finally turning his attention to the blood on his right hand.

He briefly sniffed at the blood on his hand, upon which a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

Han Li took a glance at Daoist Xie to discover that the latter was laying on the ground in a completely still manner, seemingly having had some type of restriction placed upon his body by Chen Yang.

A determined look appeared in his eyes as he took a deep breath.

No matter how formidable Chen Yang was, he couldn't leave Daoist Xie behind.

He clenched his fists tightly as the thirty-six profound acupoints on his body began to glow radiantly, and at the same time, a giant golden ape projection appeared around him before fusing into his body.

A layer of thick golden fur instantly appeared over his skin, and at the same time, he transformed into a giant golden ape that was several dozen feet tall in the blink of an eye.

Chapter 854: From Foes to Friends

Chen Yang raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he grinned as he beckoned to Han Li.

A sharp gleam flashed through the giant golden ape's eyes, and it let loose a low roar before launching its fists through the air in a rapidfire barrage.

Golden fist projections erupted toward Chen Yang like shooting stars, causing the space in their wake to rumble violently.

However, Chen Yang remained completely unfazed as he thrust his left hand forward, and all of the golden fist projections instantly drew to a halt in front of him, as if they had encountered an unbreakable wall.

Immediately thereafter, all of the golden fist projections exploded, sending shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions, while the giant golden ape had already vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, the golden ape reappeared in a wraith-like manner behind Chen Yang, then lashed out with its giant fists at Chen Yang's back.

Chen Yang reacted very quickly, swiveling around as he swung his glowing right arm toward the oncoming giant fists.

All of a sudden, the profound acupoints on the golden ape's body flashed momentarily, and its enormous body shrank down to the size of the average grown man as it crouched down to lower its center of gravity.

Chen Yang was caught completely off guard, and his right arm struck nothing but empty air, while his body also swayed involuntarily from the momentum generated by his arm swing.

Han Li pounced on this opportunity to spring forward like an agile monkey, darting past him before picking up Daoist Xie from the ground.

"Get back here!" Chen Yang roared with a furious expression as he reached out with both hands, and his arms abruptly elongated to around twice their original length, allowing him to grab onto Han Li's waist.

Bursts of white finger projections erupted out of his fingertips, and in particular, the ones that had erupted out of the fingers on Chen Yang's right hand were extremely bright, causing the nearby space to ripple and warp.

Due to the extreme spatial pressure in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, the space here was extremely stable, so it was very remarkable that Chen Yang was able to make the space ripple with his right hand.

In response, Han Li conjured up his True Extreme Film, but it stood no chance against Chen Yang's fingers and was torn apart with ease.

However, right at this moment, seven or eight true spirit projections suddenly sprang out of Han Li's body, and seven or eight layers of light of different colors also surfaced around him.

In the instant that Chen Yang's fingers grabbed onto Han Li's waist, he suddenly felt Han Li's skin become extremely slick, causing his fingers to slide off his body.

As a result, Han Li was able to escape, and he instantly flew to several hundred feet away, then turned to look at Chen Yang with a wary expression.

At this point, he had already reverted back to his human form, and he was looking a little pale.

The Twelve Awakening Transformations was an ability that was supposed to be unleashed using a combination of one's bloodline power and spiritual power.

Given that he currently had no access to immortal spiritual power, Han Li could only forcibly draw upon his bloodline power to unleash the Twelve Awakening Transformations, and that was extremely taxing on him.

Instead of giving chase, Chen Yang remained standing on the spot as he observed Han Li with a surprised expression.

"Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked as he rushed over to Han Li's side with a hint of embarrassment in his eyes.

Thanks to the boundless resources of the devilish imperial family, he had managed to open over forty profound acupoints, but when it came to mental fortitude and tenacity, he was far inferior to Han Li.

"I'm fine," Han Li replied as he rubbed a hand over his waist, and the palm of his hand was instantly stained with blood.

At this moment, there were five long gashes on his waist that were bleeding profusely, but things could've been much worse.

"I didn't think the fugitives in this domain would be so strong. What do we do now? Should we use the trump card given to us by Pokong to kill this man?" Shi Chuankong asked through voice transmission.

Han Li offered no response. He had his Spirit Refinement Technique as a trump card, so he wasn't afraid of Chen Yang.

"You two are new guys from the outside, right?" Chen Yang suddenly asked, and the profound acupoints all over his body quickly faded away.

"That's right. We were only just cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain by the Night Sun Empire. Who are you, and why did you attack us?" Han Li asked.

"I knew it. This is all a misunderstanding. I didn't recognize you two, and I saw a puppet by your side, so I attacked you on the assumption that you were from Puppet City," Chen Yang explained.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance upon hearing this, and they remained cautious and apprehensive.

"Don't worry. If you two are new here, then we're not enemies," Chen Yang said with a smile, suddenly displaying a friendly demeanor.

After communicating briefly with Shi Chuankong through voice transmission, Han Li cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Seeing as this was all a misunderstanding, then let's end things here and let bygones be bygones."

"My name is Chen Yang. May I ask your names, fellow daoists?" Chen Yang asked.

"Li Feiyu."

"Shi Kong."

Due to his sensitive status, Shi Chuankong had given a false alias.

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Li, Fellow Daoist Shi," Chen Yang said with a wide smile, and the tense atmosphere was significantly alleviated.

"What is this Puppet City that you spoke of earlier, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"That's a long story. To give you a summary, the survivors in the Scalptia Spatial Domain are currently split up into two major powers. My companions and I come from Profound City, while Puppet City represents the opposing major power, which is why I attacked you just now," Chen Yang explained with a smile.

"I see," Han Li replied as he nodded with a contemplative expression.

"Profound City and Puppet City... Those are two rather interesting names," Shi Chuankong remarked.

"As I'm sure you've figured out by now, it's impossible to use devilish qi and spiritual qi in the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Hence, in order to contend against all of the native beasts of the domain, the only options are to pursue bodily refinement or rely on puppets. Our Profound City is filled with bodily refinement cultivators, while those Puppet City specialize in puppeteering," Chen Yang explained with a smile.

"I see," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"The environment in the Scalptia Spatial Domain is extremely unforgiving, and it's very difficult to survive here in small groups. Would you be interested in joining our Profound City? I can see that both of you have already opened up many profound acupoints, so you would be perfect additions to our city," Chen Yang invited.

Han Li was internally quite excited to hear this.

He was just considering joining Profound City or Puppet City to find more leads on Violet Spirit, so this offer from Chen Yang had come at the perfect time.

Despite this, his expression remained unchanged, and he pretended to be contemplating the offer while also giving Shi Chuankong a subtle look.

Shi Chuankong immediately caught on to his intentions, and he asked, "Would you be able to tell us more about Profound City, Fellow Daoist Chen?"

"As I just said, our Profound City is primarily inhabited by bodily refinement cultivators, and our city lord is Master E Kuai. He's an unfathomably powerful bodily refinement cultivator who's opened over a thousand profound acupoints, and it's all thanks to his protection that we're able to live safely in this Scalptia Spatial Domain," Chen Yang introduced as a hint of admiration surfaced in his eyes.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were both astonished to hear this.

Bodily refinement was extremely difficult, yet even devilish beings were blessed with many physical advantages and also had access to an abundance of resources in the Devil Realm, Shi Chuankong had only ever heard of a few cultivators who had opened eight hundred profound acupoints.

"Master E Kuai is far above what the likes of us can hope to reach, but I can see that both of you also possess remarkable aptitude when it comes to bodily refinement, so why not come to our Profound City to further yourselves?" Chen Yang invited once again.

"Would you be able to give us some time to consider this matter, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked, but he received no response, and as he turned his gaze to Chen Yang, he discovered that the latter had suddenly begun looking up at the sky with a grim expression.

Han Li also looked up at the sky upon seeing this, and he discovered that some dark clouds had suddenly appeared up above.

"Is there a problem, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Shi Chuankong asked.

However, Chen Yang didn't appear to have heard him at all, and he murmured to himself, "Why has it come so early this year?"

"Fellow Daoist Chen, are you alright?" Han Li asked in a louder voice, and only then did Chen Yang snap back to his senses.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he repeated his request from earlier.

"Of course you can take some time to consider my offer, but we have to leave this place right away," Chen Yang replied in an urgent manner.

"Is there something wrong with the clouds in the sky, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Shi Chuankong asked with slightly furrowed brows.

Chapter 855: Joining Profound City?

"Those aren't just normal clouds. Instead, they're a precursor to the furious wind natural disaster of the Scalptia Spatial Domain. It happens every year, but I didn't think it would come so early this year. This wind is too powerful to resist through one's individual power. My companions and I have an underground stronghold nearby, and we have to go there right now," Chen Yang urged.

Shi Chuankong's expression changed slightly upon hearing this.

"Have you heard of this furious wind, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked through voice transmission upon noticing his reaction.

"I've seen some records of this natural disaster in an ancient book in Pokong's study, but the records weren't very detailed, only referring to it as a devastating wind-based natural disaster. Judging from Chen Yang's reaction, it must be very devastating indeed," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In that case, we'll have to trouble you to lead the way," Han Li said to Chen Yang.

"All of us were exiled into this place by the Night Sun Empire, so we should be looking out for each other. Please come with me, fellow daoists," Chen Yang replied as he turned to leave.

"Before that, please undo the restrictions that you've placed on this puppet of mine, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li suddenly said.

"Of course! I completely forgot," Chen Yang said as he slapped a hand to his own forehead, then pulled out a golden needle from Daoist Xie's elbow.

The needle was several inches in length and as thin as a hair, and there were tiny patterns visible on its surface.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of the golden needle.

Chen Yang continued to pull more golden needles out of Daoist Xie's joints as he explained, "These are dragon whisker needles, and they were developed by a powerful figure in our Profound City to be used specifically on puppets."

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

After the ninth golden needle was pulled out, Daoist Xie immediately returned to his feet, much to Chen Yang's surprise.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked.

"Generally speaking, puppets restricted by dragon whisker needles require a period of recuperation to recover after the needles are pulled out, so this puppet of yours must be quite remarkable to have been able to stand up right away," Chen Yang explained.

"Perhaps it's because it wasn't sealed for all that long," Han Li replied, giving an ambiguous excuse.

Chen Yang was in a hurry to leave, so he didn't dwell on this topic, and he stowed the golden needles away as he said, "Let's go."

Around two hours later, the four of them arrived in a valley that was surrounded by mountains in three directions, making it a very obscure location.

At this point, the dark clouds in the sky had already become quite heavy, and arcs of black lightning could be seen flashing deep within them.

At the same time, gusts of fierce wind had already begun to blow through the area, and even though the wind wasn't powerful enough to pose a threat to Han Li and the others, it carried bursts of bone-chilling glacial qi that infiltrated their bodies, constantly robbing them of their body heat.

Thankfully, they had already arrived at their destination, and Chen Yang led Han Li's trio to a mountain face in the deepest point of the valley, where there was a giant gray rock pressed tightly against the mountain face.

Chen Yang pushed the giant rock aside to reveal a cave that led underground, and an armorclad man with a head of red hair immediately rushed out from within.

"You're finally back, Brother Chen! Who're these three?"

"These two are Fellow Daoist Li and Fellow Daoist Shi. They've only recently been exiled here, and I've taken them here to shelter them from the furious wind," Chen Yang explained.

"I see. It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, fellow daoists. Come in. Right now, the furious wind is only in the approaching phase, the true furious wind is more than ten times as fearsome as what we're currently experiencing," the red-haired man said as he made an inviting hand gesture.

Han Li was quite astonished to hear this.

The current furious winds were already quite a struggle for him to deal with. If they were to become ten times more powerful, then even if he could survive them, the outcome would not be pretty.

With that in mind, he entered the cave behind Chen Yang.

As soon as he entered the cave, the howling wind instantly subsided, and there was still some glacial qi in the air, but it was far less pronounced inside.

"Fang Bei, seal the entrance shut and come down with us. If you let the glacial qi of the furious wind infiltrate your body, it'll be very difficult to expel," Chen Yang said.

The red-haired man seemed to be very touched to hear this, and he immediately gave an affirmative response before springing into action.

Chen Yang led Han Li's trio deeper into the cave, which extended in a downward direction.

It appeared to be a naturally formed cave that was later renovated, and even after walking for several thousand feet, there was still no end in sight.

However, at this point, the glacial qi in the air had already significantly abated, allowing everyone to heave a collective sigh of relief.

"Thank you for inviting us here, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

If it weren't for Chen Yang's invitation, he and Shi Chuankong would truly be in some peril.

"It's fine, don't worry about it, Fellow Daoist Li. Us exiles have to look out for each other," Chen Yang said in a nonchalant manner.

The four of them walked onward for another fifteen minutes before finally reaching the bottom of the tunnel, where they arrived in a cave that was over a hundred feet in size.

The ground was quite level, and at the very center of the cave was a large ovular stone table, around which were seven or eight stone chairs.

A series of crude stone rooms had been carved into the walls of the cave, and at this moment, the cave was completely empty, while the doors of all of the stone rooms were tightly shut, indicating that everyone was in their rooms, taking shelter from the furious winds.

"The furious winds will blow for about a month or so before subsiding. In the meantime, you can stay here and consider the matter of joining our Profound City," Chen Yang said.

Both Han Li and Shi Chuankong nodded in response.

Virtually all of the stone rooms were currently occupied, so the two of them sat down in the cave.

Chen Yang took a glance at the two of them, then also sat down in the cave instead of entering any of the stone rooms.

Even through the mountain, the three of them could still hear the wind howling outside, and the ground was also gently trembling, while loose rocks were falling incessantly from the ceiling of the cave.

At the same time, loud crashing noises were ringing out incessantly, as if even the entire continent itself were trembling in the face of the furious winds.

Over the past few months, Han Li and Shi Chuankong had been attacked by some of the scaled beasts in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but none of them had posed a true threat to them, so they were beginning to think that the supposed dangers of the Scalptia Spatial Domain were rather exaggerated. However, they now knew just how wrong they had been.

"Should we join Profound City, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked through voice transmission.

"What do you think?" Han Li asked.

"It looks like the Scalptia Spatial Domain is far more dangerous than we anticipated. As opposed to searching aimlessly for Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit, I think it's a good idea to join Profound City. Having said that, it sounds like Profound City and Puppet City are sworn enemies, so if we can't find Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit in Profound City, then it'll be difficult for us to go to Puppet City to continue our search," Shi Chuankong said.

"That's true, but right now, we can only choose one out of Profound City or Puppet City, and judging from the current circumstances, choosing Profound City appears to be more beneficial to us," Han Li said.

"It sounds like you've already made a decision. Honestly, I also really want to go and see what this Profound City is all about," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"If Chen Yang is to be believed, then City Lord E Kuai of Profound City has opened over a thousand profound acupoints, so there must be many bodily refinement cultivation arts in the city. Such cultivation arts are priceless treasures, and there aren't that many of them even in our imperial family's military vault.

“If we can get our hands on those cultivation arts, not only will we be able to enhance our own powers, Pokong will also be able to make use of them once we get out of here," Shi Chuankong said.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

This was actually also one of the factors that had influenced his decision to join Profound City.

He was very much in awe of Chen Yang's incredibly powerful right arm, and it showed him just how powerful bodily refinement cultivators could become.

He had always possessed decent aptitude in this field, but his progress had been hampered by a lack of suitable bodily refinement cultivation arts.

After some further discussion, the two of them quickly arrived at a consensus, following which Han Li rose to his feet and began making his way toward Chen Yang.

Chen Yang had already noticed the secret conversation taking place between the two of them, and he immediately rose to his feet as well.

"Fellow Daoist Shi and I have decided to join Profound City, but before that, we have a few questions that we would like to have answered," Han Li said.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li," Chen Yang immediately prompted.

"Is there any type of cost to joining Profound City, or do we have to follow any rules?" Han Li asked.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li. Master E Kuai founded Profound City for the sake of everyone's safety, so no cost is required to join our city. As for rules, there's only one, which is that once you've joined Profound City, you cannot betray the city," Chen Yang replied.

"I see," Han Li replied. "Also, I have one more question."

"Go ahead," Chen Yang prompted once again.

"I have a companion by the name of Violet Spirit. She's a female cultivator who was cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain several decades ago. Have you heard of her before?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid not," Chen Yang replied after a brief moment of contemplation, and Han Li's heart sank slightly upon hearing this.

Chen Yang could see the disappointment on Han Li's face, and he consoled, "Don't be disheartened, Fellow Daoist Li. Our Profound City has more than one city. Aside from the main city, there are also several subsidiary cities, and I'm from one of them, a city by the name of Green Goat City.

“Communication arrays can't be used in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so information isn't easily shared between the cities. Perhaps your friend has gone to one of them."

Chapter 856: If I Can't Beat Them, I Can At Least Run

"I see. Thank you for answering my questions, Fellow Daoist Chen. Fellow Daoist Shi and I would like to join Profound City," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute, and Shi Chuankong also stood up to join him.

"Great! From this day forth, you two will be fellow brothers of our Profound City, and I'll take you to Green Goat City as soon as the furious winds subside," Chen Yang replied in an elated manner.

Right at this moment, the red-haired man also arrived in the cave, and he immediately chimed in, "Welcome, fellow daoists."

With Han Li and Shi Chuankong agreeing to join Profound City, the atmosphere instantly became much more relaxed and harmonious, but there were still bursts of glacial qi seeping into the cave, so everyone quickly sat down again to ward off the glacial qi.

Thankfully, most of the glacial qi had been kept out by the mountain, and what little managed to sneak through posed no threat for powerful Profound Immortals like Han Li and the others.

As soon as Han Li sat down onto the ground, Daoist Xie's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Are you alright, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked through voice transmission as he turned to Daoist Xie, who was seated not far away.

Ever since his body was sealed by the dragon whisker needles, Daoist Xie had remained silent, even when Han Li had tried to communicate with him, and that had left him feeling rather concerned.

"I'm fine. In fact, those needles have stimulated my memories and allowed him to recollect some things," Daoist Xie replied.

"Are these memories pertaining to the Scalptia Spatial Domain?" Han Li asked.

"Some are, while some aren't. A lot of information flooded into my mind at once this time, and it's taken me quite some time to make sense of everything," Daoist Xie replied.

"What exactly have you recalled?" Han Li asked.

"The most important things that I've recalled are that there's a place called the Carefree Palace, and also two names, E Kuai and Sha Xin," Daoist Xie replied.

"E Kuai? That's the city lord of Profound City! Are you somehow related to him?" Han Li asked in a surprised manner.

"I don't know. The memories are too hazy. I've only recalled their names, while the rest is a complete blur," Daoist Xie replied in a frustrated voice.

"Don't worry too much about it. I'll find a way to look into things once we reach Profound City," Han Li said.

"Aside from that, I also recalled something else that may be of help to you," Daoist Xie said as a faint smile appeared on his face.

"Oh? What is it?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Daoist Xie offered no response as he rose to his feet and made his way over to Han Li's side, then pointed a finger at his glabella.

A beam of golden light flew out of his fingertip before fusing into Han Li's mind, where it exploded into countless tiny golden characters.

Han Li's eyes instantly widened as an ecstatic look appeared on his face, following which he immediately closed his eyes again.

The passage of tiny golden text was a bodily refinement cultivation art called the Wingform Ascension Arts. The cultivation art contained eighteen profound acupoints, all of which were on the legs, and mastering the cultivation art not only enhanced one's physical prowess, but also allowed one to take flight by treading air using the power of their legs alone.

The entirety of Han Li's attention was captured by the cultivation art, and only after a long while did he reopen his eyes, then said through voice transmission, "Thank you, Brother Xie. This is exactly what I need."

He didn't know much about bodily refinement cultivation arts, but he could still sense that even though the Wingform Ascension Arts couldn't allow one to open that many profound acupoints, it would still significantly enhance the power of one's legs, and it was particularly valuable given that he was currently unable to fly in this domain.

If I can't beat them, I can at least run.

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then sat down with his legs crossed and paid no further heed to Han Li.

As for Han Li, he immediately began cultivating the Wingform Ascension Arts.

Just like the Great Universe Origin Arts, the Wingform Ascension Arts used starpower to refine the physical body and open profound acupoints, making it perfect for the starpower-rich environment of the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Even though he was currently underground and sheltered from the stars, he had devoured many beast cores on the way here, and the starpower from those beast cores had been stored in his body up to this point.

After carefully examining the entirety of the Wingform Ascension Arts again, he commenced his cultivation, and the starpower accumulated in his body immediately surged into a profound acupoint on his leg.

The profound acupoint greedily devoured the starpower, and a feeling of extreme relaxation spread through his leg, almost making him moan with pleasure.

The profound acupoint slowly began to open as it absorbed more and more starpower, and close to an entire month flew by in a flash.

Han Li had remained seated with his legs crossed this entire time, but a speck of starlight had appeared on his calf, and it was flashing incessantly.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open, and a faint crack rang out from the profound acupoint on his calf as the starlight radiating from it abruptly brightened significantly.

After close to a month of arduous cultivation, he had finally opened up the profound acupoint.

An excited look appeared in his eyes, and as he looked around, he discovered that Chen Yang and the red-haired man had entered their stone rooms to cultivate, while Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie were also cultivating far away and didn't seem to have noticed what had happened to him.

The starlight emanating from the profound acupoint on his calf slowly dissipated, and a perplexed look appeared in his eyes.

According to the Wingform Ascension Arts, opening these profound acupoints was supposed to be a very difficult and time-consuming process.

Even though he had accumulated a great deal of starpower in his body from consuming beast cores, opening an acupoint in less then twenty days was still progress that was far faster than expected.

Han Li speculated internally about the potential contributing factors for a while, then shook his head and rid himself of that train of thought.

In any case, faster cultivation progress was definitely a good thing.

There was still a thunderous commotion ringing out outside, clearly indicating that the furious winds were still raging.

The glacial qi within the cave had become more pronounced than before, but not by much.

Han Li had been immersed in his cultivation this entire time, so he hadn't detected this change in the environment.

He took a glance at Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie to verify that both of them also remained unaffected by the glacial qi, then closed his eyes and began working on opening his next profound acupoint.

Another week passed by in a flash.

On this day, Han Li slowly exhaled as he opened his eyes, having exhausted the last of the starpower in his body.

Without starpower, no further progression could be made.

At this point, the furious winds were already on the wane, and the glacial qi within them had faded away.

Chen Yang and the others had also emerged from their stone rooms and were ready to set off.

Many of them were quite curious about the three new recruits, but they quickly accepted Han Li's trio after hearing Chen Yang's explanation.

Everyone quickly emerged from the underground cave into the valley above, and even though the glacial qi had faded away, the winds outside were still strong enough to cause everyone to sway unsteadily.

At this point, the valley outside had already taken on a completely different appearance. A thick layer of the ground had been stripped away, while the nearby mountains were also clearly shorter than before, reflecting just how fearsome the furious winds had been.

"Let's go," Chen Yang said.

"Fellow Daoist Chen, why don't we wait a few more days until the winds have completely subsided?" Han Li asked.

"The furious winds may be a natural disaster, but they also present an opportunity. Whenever the furious winds pass through, many scaled beasts will fall to their deaths or freeze to death, and we have to go out early to find them. Otherwise, their carcasses could be eaten by other scaled beasts," Chen Yang explained.

"I see. Risk and reward really do come hand in hand," Han Li replied with an enlightened expression.

With that, the group set off into the distance, quickly vanishing out of sight.

……

The bright sun was hanging high up in the sky, while howling winds were blowing over a desert.

A hunting party was trudging arduously through the wind, and there were several giant scaled beasts blocking the way ahead, with roughly ten men walking among them.

All of the men had thick clothes over their faces that covered even their necks, yet that still wasn't able to keep out the coarse sand being blown into their faces by the fierce winds.

Due to the spatial pressure in this domain, even these sand particles packed immense power, making their advance quite difficult.

There was an azure-robed man in the group, and he peered through a gap between the giant beast to see what appeared to be a giant shadow in the distance.

"How much longer until we reach Green Goat City, Fellow Daoist Chen?" the azure-robed man asked.

"It's just up ahead," Chen Yang replied with a hint of elation in his voice.

"Finally! Rest assured, Brother Li, we'll definitely be able to find out some information about Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit once we reach the city. There's no way anyone can forget someone so beautiful as long as they've laid eyes on her," Shi Chuankong jibed.

"I certainly hope so," Han Li replied.

Chapter 857: Green Goat City

After that brief conversation, the group continued onward in silence, and only after walking for several thousand more feet did the wind gradually begin to subside.

At the same time, the giant shadow that Han Li had spotted in the distance earlier was revealed to be a pair of black mountains that were situated right next to each other.

The mountains were riddled with pits and craters, all of which were the result of wind erosion.

There was a massive canyon nestled in between the two mountains, and at the center of the canyon was a black fortress that was thousands of feet tall.

The fortress was quite rugged in appearance, with three huge forts up above, while down below were the tall and sturdy black city walls.

Inside the canyon, all of the wind was kept out by the mountains and the fortress, so the conditions were far more forgiving.

Upon arriving at the gates of the fortress, Chen Yang removed the cloth from his face and shook off the sand in his clothes before making his way over to a stone platform outside the gates, then slammed a hand down onto a large gong hanging above the platform.

After the gong was struck, an opening suddenly appeared above the fortress gates, and several figures peeked out of the opening before someone yelled, "Open the gates, Captain Chen Yang's back."

This was followed by a burst of rumbling and some mechanical clicking, and the black fortress gates slowly opened inward.

The group entered the fortress, following which the stone gates swung shut behind them.

Upon entering the fortress, Han Li immediately discovered that the interior was quite different from what he had imagined.

The area inside the fortress was quite large, several thousand feet in size, and there was a giant brazier hanging on the walls every few dozen feet. Some type of beast fat was being burned in the braziers, and it wasn't giving off any smoke, but it did release a faint rank odor.

Significant parts of the fortress's interior was taken up by all types of gears and mechanical structures, and at the center of the fortress were three giant stone pillars around each of which was a winding stone staircase that led to the three forts up above.

There were quite a few people in the fortress, all of whom were busy carrying out various tasks, and Chen Yang's subordinates were leading various types of beasts toward the right side of the fortress, while Chen Yang and Han Li's trio remained standing in the hall.

Before long, they were approached by two crimson-robed scribes, each of whom was holding a thick book in one hand and a brush dipped in red ink in the other.

Chen Yang seemed to be very familiar with these two, and one of them, a round-faced man with a small horn on his glabella, smiled and remarked, "It looks like you made quite a bountiful trip, Captain Chen Yang."

"Indeed, we were very fortunate not to have come back empty-handed"

The other scribe was a man with long ears and a square face, and there was a cold look on his face as he took a glance at Han Li's trio before asking, "What category do these three fall into?"

A slightly awkward look appeared on Chen Yang's face as he replied, "They're guests of mine, and they wish to join our Green Goat City. As for which category they fall into, that'll have to be decided when I meet with the city lord."

"I'm afraid that's inappropriate, Captain Chen Yang. According to the rules, newcomers must be categorized as soon as they enter the city," the square-faced scribe said as his brows furrowed slightly.

The other scribe hurriedly began playing the role of mediator, tugging on his colleague's sleeve as he said, "Surely we can trust Captain Chen Yang. He's one of the city lord's most trusted hunting captains, and it's not like he's outright refusing to categorize these three newcomers, so let's just wait until he meets the city lord."

The square-faced scribe hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then nodded in response.

"I suppose it can't hurt."

A grateful smile appeared on Chen Yang's face as he said, "You have my thanks. I'll have to trouble the two of you to tally the spoils of our hunting trip, please accept these as a small gift."

He reached out and subtly handed the two scribes a pair of beast cores as he spoke, an offering that the two scribes naturally gladly accepted.

Following their departure, Chen Yang turned to Han Li's trio as he said, "I have to go and meet with the city lord later, so I'll arrange a place for the three of you to stay first."

"Who were those two?" Han Li asked.

"They're the two scribes of our Green Goat City, and they're responsible for tallying the spoils from hunting trips and registering newcomers," Chen Yang replied.

"What are the categories that he was talking about?" Han Li asked.

"There are two categories that all newcomers fall into upon arriving in our city, namely acquired citizens and defected citizens. Acquired citizens are higher in status, able to join the city guards or hunting parties, and they'll also receive more resources, whereas defected citizens are lower in status and can only serve as manual laborers and receive lesser resources," Chen Yang explained.

"These categories are used to determine the social hierarchy, right?" Han Li asked.

"Come with me, I'll tell you more about it as we walk," Chen Yang said with a smile, then began to lead the way toward the left side of the fortress.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other before following along.

"According to the rules of our city, all newcomers must undergo an appraisal before being registered, following which roles will be arranged. However, I've seen your power with my own eyes, so I wanted to request the city lord to skip that process and have the two of you become my subordinates. I'm assuming the two of you would prefer to stay together, right?" Chen Yang asked.

"Isn't that against the rules?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Rules are made by people, are they not? If I follow the regular procedure, only for the two of you to be assigned elsewhere, then I'll be kicking myself. Having said that, as for whether you'll be undergoing an appraisal, that'll be up to the city lord," Chen Yang said.

Han Li nodded in response.

"With your powers, I don't think it'll take very long at all before both of you become captains of new hunting parties. When that time comes, I hope you won't forget about me," Chen Yang chuckled.

As the conversation continued, the four of them passed through three stone archways to arrive before a cave that had been carved into a mountain.

Only then did Han Li discover that Green Goat City had actually been constructed within artificial cavities inside the two mountains.

Directly across from the cave was a humanoid stone statue, the subject of which resembled a human with no devilish features, but their facial features were very blurry and indistinct.

"Is this a statue of the city lord?" Han Li asked.

"No. This is an extremely old statue, even older than Green Goat City, and even our city lord doesn't know who created this statue. Perhaps only City Lord E Kuai of Profound City knows how this statue came into existence," Chen Yang replied.

"I see," Han Li said.

"The left peak of Green Goat City is split up into four levels. The level we're on right now is the refinement level, and it's where all of the city's armor and weapons are produced, as well as all of our pills are refined. Most of the armor and pills that are produced go straight to the city lord for him to distribute as he sees fit, while only a small portion are released to be sold in the few shops in the city," Chen Yang introduced.

"What about the other levels?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"The level above this one is where the defected citizens reside, while the level above that one is where the acquired citizens live, and the top level is where the city lord's manor is situated. You can take a rest in my manor while I go to see the city lord," Chen Yang replied.

After that, Chen Yang led Han Li's trio on a brief tour of the bottom level, then led them up a spiral staircase to the third level.

This level was far smaller than the bottom level, and it was also clearly less populated. There was a wide road that stretched into the heart of the level, and the road was lined with entrances to cave abodes.

Chen Yang's cave abode was situated near the middle of the path, and it was one of the better and more spacious cave abodes in the area.

Han Li's trio followed Chen Yang into the cave abode, upon which they were immediately greeted by a woman and three men.

Among them, the three men were dressed in servant attire, while the woman's clothes were also a drab gray color, but they had been tailored to fit her extremely well and perfectly accentuate her curves.

However, her looks could only be described as ordinary, and she was not particularly beautiful.

"These are also technically defected citizens, but they're also my personal property. If you're interested, you can have some fun with this maidservant of mine. Women are a precious resource here, and not everyone gets to have one," Chen Yang said in a direct and straightforward manner.

"I'm a little weary from our journey, so I think I'll take a rest first," Han Li replied, turning down the offer in a tactful manner.

"In that case, you can go and make yourselves at home in the guest rooms while I go and meet with the city lord," Chen Yang said.

He then turned to the four servants and instructed, "Make sure to look after my guests well."

After that, he departed from the cave abode.

The woman stepped forward and extended a slight curtsey, then led Han Li's trio down a passageway to the guest rooms in the cave abode.

Following her departure, both Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie left their guest rooms to gather in Han Li's room.

After the door was closed, the three of them sat down around a stone table.

Chapter 858: Appraisal

"Do you think they'll restrict our freedom now that we've joined Profound City, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"I don't think so. We'll most likely be assigned missions that'll take up some of our time. After all, given the inhospitable conditions in this domain, we'll inevitably have to make certain contributions and follow the rules," Han Li said.

"I hope things won't get too hectic. Honestly, I have no interest in becoming an acquired citizen or whatever," Shi Chuankong said as he pursed his lips in disdain.

"We don't really have much of a choice in the matter, we just have to be on our guard," Han Li said.

"Do you think they're going to try to plot against us, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"These are all fugitives who've been cast into exile, so they're certainly not good people. If they were kind and benevolent people, then I don't think they would've been able to survive until now," Han Li replied.

"That's true, it's definitely better to be safe than sorry," Shi Chuankong mused.

"What do you think of Chen Yang?" Daoist Xie suddenly asked.

"We haven't known him for very long, but he seems like a decent person, judging from his words and actions and the way that he treats his subordinates," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Have you noticed something amiss about him, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Like Fellow Daoist Shi just said, we haven't known him for very long at all, so it feels a little strange that he's willing to break the rules of Profound City for our sake," Daoist Xie mused.

"I don't think that's anything out of the ordinary, he's clearly just trying to win us over," Shi Chuankong said in a nonchalant manner.

"Perhaps so, but we definitely can't let our guards down, nevertheless," Han Li said.

……

Meanwhile, in a giant hall on the top level of the left wing of Green Goat City.

There were a series of huge braziers that appeared to have been fashioned from beast skulls hanging from the walls of the hall, and the flames burning inside illuminated the entire hall.

At the back of the hall was a massive stone table engraved with many complex designs depicting the stars that appeared at night.

Behind the table was a large black stone chair with a sheet of beast hide draped over it, upon which sat a physically imposing black-robed man.

One half of his face was covered in black scales, while the other half was severely mutilated as if it had been burned before. On top of that, he was twice the height of the average grown man, and his physique was almost comically muscular, presenting an extremely fearsome sight to behold.

Furthermore, his eyes were very unique, with tiny pupils that had a glowing silver ring around the outer edge.

Chen Yang was standing not far from the other side of the table in a bowed position, delivering a report.

The man on the chair was none other than City Lord Du Qingyang of Green Goat City, and after hearing Chen Yang's report, an intrigued look appeared on his face as he mused, "A human, a devil, and a sentient puppet... That's quite an interesting trio. No one has heard about them yet, right?"

"Rest assured, City Lord Du, I've already instructed my subordinates to keep their mouths shut," Chen Yang hurriedly assured.

"I heard that Profound City and Puppet City had recently fought over someone from the outside, and Puppet City won out on that occasion, much to Master E Kuai's dismay. Now, we've picked up two people from the outside at once. If Profound City hears about this, there's no way we'll be allowed to keep them," Du Qingyang said.

"That man from the devil race isn't all that important, but we absolutely cannot hand over that human. He has a true spirit bloodline in his body, and it would be a massive loss if he fell into someone else's hands," Chen Yang said.

"I'll leave the rest to you. Make sure you don't screw this up," Du Qingyang instructed as he leaned back in a lazy fashion.

"You can count on me, City Lord Du!" Chen Yang assured as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

……

That night.

Han Li was cultivating the Wingform Ascension Arts in his room when the sound of door-knocking suddenly rang out.

He opened the door to discover Chen Yang standing outside with an apologetic expression.

Han Li invited him into the room, upon which he said, "I must apologize, Brother Li. I was thinking that the city lord would be willing to agree to my request to exempt the three of you from undergoing the appraisal process, but to my surprise, he turned me down and scolded me for not upholding the rules of the city."

"It's fine, we should be following the rules in the first place, and we're happy to participate in the appraisal," Han Li replied.

"Even though the city lord turned down my request, he did agree to let both of you join my hunting party as long as you can fulfill the prerequisites to become acquired citizens," Chen Yang said.

"What are these prerequisites?" Han Li asked.

"The appraisal assesses the power of one's physical body. To be more specific, it assesses the number of profound acupoints one has opened up, and those who've opened sixteen or more profound acupoints will be categorized as acquired citizens, while those below that standard will become defected citizens.

“Those who've opened more than fifty-four profound acupoints can serve as the captain of a city guard team, while those with more than seventy-two profound acupoints can lead their own hunting party," Chen Yang explained.

Han Li recalled that during their battle, Chen Yang had only revealed around fifty to sixty profound acupoints, yet he was the captain of a hunting party, so it was clear that he hadn't displayed his full power back then.

"I see. When will the appraisal be carried out? If I recall correctly, the two scribes seemed to have said that it was the first thing that we were supposed to have done after entering the city," Han Li said.

"There's no hurry. You and Brother Shi must be quite wary from the long journey, so have a good rest today, and we'll carry out the appraisal tomorrow," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

"Alright. You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Please don't thank me, Brother Li. I'm still feeling quite guilty that I wasn't able to exempt the two of you from the appraisal process altogether," Chen Yang replied with a faint sigh.

"You have nothing to feel guilty about, Brother Chen," Han Li assured with a smile, and the two of them chatted for a while longer before Chen Yang departed.

Following Chen Yang's departure, Han Li sat back down in his room with his legs crossed, then devoured a beast core before continuing his cultivation.

The next morning.

Han Li's trio followed Chen Yang all the way to the bottom level of Green Goat City, then made their way through the black fortress to the city's right peak.

Just like the left peak, the right peak was also divided into four levels.

Upon entering the right peak, Han Li spotted a series of giant pens that were separated by stone walls, within which all types of massive beasts were being kept, among which were the giant beasts that Chen Yang's hunting party had captured.

There were also many gray-robed defected citizens in the pens, carrying out tasks like feeding and cleaning the beasts.

Han Li's trio continued onward without pause, going straight up to the second level, which was slightly smaller than the first level, but was also filled with a series of massive pens.

Compared with the beasts on the first level, the ones on the second level were clearly not as obedient, and they were either baring their fangs and growling, or slamming their bodies against their enclosures.

The majority of the people overseeing these pens were still defected citizens, but there were also some acquired citizen city guards among them that occasionally stepped in to discipline the unruly beasts.

Chen Yang led Han Li's trio to the third floor, and as soon as they arrived, they immediately encountered two familiar faces, namely the two crimson-robed scribes that they had encountered the day before.

Chen Yang exchanged some small talk with the two scribes, following which the two of them led Han Li's group into an individual stone chamber.

The stone chamber was quite large, significantly larger than Chen Yang's cave abode, but it was completely empty, giving it the appearance of an indoor plaza.

"The puppet doesn't need to be appraised. Which one of the two of you wants to go first?" the square-faced scribe asked.

"I'll go first," Shi Chuankong volunteered.

"Alright, please come this way, Fellow Daoist Shi," the round-faced scribe instructed.

In the center of the room was a black stone platform that was several hundred feet in radius and only no more than two feet tall. There seemed to be a layer of glittering white powder on its surface, which was reflecting the light of the lamps in the room.

Shi Chuankong stepped onto the stone platform as instructed, and the round-faced scribe said, "There's no need to do anything complex, Fellow Daoist Shi. Just activate all of your profound acupoints for us to see."

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, then clenched his fists as he let loose a loud roar, immediately following which a series of profound acupoints lit up all over his body.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over the black stone platform and the glittering white power to ensure that nothing was amiss, then turned his gaze to Shi Chuankong.

As more and more profound acupoints lit up over Shi Chuankong's body, it occurred to Han Li that Shi Chuankong had opened up far more profound acupoints than he had.

Sure enough, Shi Chuankong's profound acupoints quickly surpassed Han Li's tally of thirty-seven, only stopping after the forty-fifth one had lit up.

At the same time, a burst of energy erupted out of his body, causing the glittering white powder around him to rise up into the air.

A faint smile appeared on Shi Chuankong's face, and he was just about to step down from the stone platform when the white powder that had been thrown up into the air suddenly began to converge toward him.

Due to the close proximity, Shi Chuankong didn't have any time to react before the white powder made contact with his body, and in the next instant, three more profound acupoints lit up over his body, bringing the total tally to forty-eight.

Chapter 859: Alternative Arrangements

"What's the meaning of this?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Don't be alarmed, Brother Li. The white powder on the platform is a type of ground beast bone that is used as a pill refinement ingredient, and it's able to stimulate one's profound acupoints, so it's being used here to ensure that the subject is revealing their true number of profound acupoints," Chen Yang reassured.

Shi Chuankong was initially rather apprehensive, but it seemed that the powder was entirely harmless. After hearing Chen Yang's words of reassurance, he was still feeling a little displeased, but he allowed the powder to cling to his body, and before long, fifty-two profound acupoints had been revealed.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

Daoist Xie had been staring at this white powder intently this entire time, and it seemed that he had some recollection of what this powder was, but wasn't quite able to remember exactly what it did.

Shi Chuankong had originally intended to hide some of his profound acupoints, but he had been forced to reveal everything, and he stepped down from the stone platform in a rather displeased manner.

"Don't be angry, Brother Shi. While the main function of the powder on the platform is to force one to reveal all of their profound acupoints, it also has a beneficial effect on one's cultivation base, and this is the only chance you'll get to use it," Chen Yang hurriedly consoled.

Shi Chuankong took a moment to examine his own internal condition upon hearing this, and only then did his expression ease slightly.

"Shi Kong, fifty-two profound acupoints," the round-faced scribe declared, while the square-faced scribe made records in his book.

"It's your turn now, Fellow Daoist Li," the round-faced scribe said as he turned to Han Li.

Han Li nodded in response before stepping onto the stone platform, then took a deep breath as he channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts.

Once all of his thirty-seven profound acupoints had been revealed, the white powder on the stone platform rose up once again before clinging to his body, but no further profound acupoints appeared.

A hint of surprise flashed through Chen Yang's face upon seeing this, clearly taken aback by the fact that Han Li had far fewer profound acupoints than Shi Chuankong.

"Li Feiyu, thirty-seven profound acupoints," the round-faced scribe declared.

The square-faced scribe recorded this result, then gave Chen Yang a nod, while Han Li stepped down from the stone platform.

"Both fellow daoist have fulfilled the prerequisites to become acquired citizens and can join Fellow Daoist Chen Yang's hunting party. Congratulations," the round-faced scribe said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Our city is very pleased to have you, fellow daoists."

Right as Chen Yang's voice trailed off, a resounding boom suddenly rang out overhead, and the entire stone chamber shuddered violently.

Han Li's trio were rather alarmed by this, but Chen Yang and the two scribes displayed no reaction.

"No need to be alarmed," Chen Yang reassured with a smile. "The top floor of the right peak above us is our city's arena, and there must be a battle taking place right now."

"There's an arena here?" Shi Chuankong asked as a hint of excitement appeared in his eyes.

He had always been very interested in arena battles. In fact, he and Han Li had first met back in an arena in Primordial Origin City.

He was just about to ask some questions about the arena when he was struck by a sense of lightheadedness, and he began to involuntarily tip forward.

Right as he was about to fall onto Chen Yang, the latter smiled and took a step back, allowing him to crash to the ground.

Han Li immediately realized that something wasn't right, but before he had a chance to say anything, he also began to feel lightheaded.

He hurriedly bit down onto the tip of his own tongue while attempting to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique, only to discover that his consciousness had become extremely dull and lifeless, and all of the strength seemed to have been sapped from his body.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, he also fell unconscious, and the last thing that he saw before his vision faded to black was the sight of a hideous and imposing figure making his way into the room.

Chen Yang's trio immediately extended a respectful salute toward the figure, who was none other than Du Qingyang.

"You did well, Chen Yang," Du Qingyang remarked as he took a glance at Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"It was all thanks to the White Profound Beast bone powder that you gave me, City Lord Du," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

A look of realization immediately appeared on Daoist Xie's face upon hearing the term "White Profound Beast", and he knew that this bone powder was what had knocked Han Li and Shi Chuankong unconscious, but the realization had come far too late.

"Should I take them to your secret chamber, City Lord Du?" Chen Yang asked.

"There's no hurry, I have some other plans for him," Du Qingyang replied, and the two of them weren't making any effort to keep their conversation secret from Daoist Xie, who remained standing off to the side instead of making any rash moves.

All of a sudden, Chen Yang seemed to have recalled Daoist Xie's existence, and he asked, "What should we do with this puppet?"

"Lock up those two for now. As for this puppet, it has some sentience, but it's of no use to me, so you can do with it as you see fit," Du Qingyang replied, then turned to depart.

"Become my servant or be disassembled into a pile of scrap metal right now. It's your choice," Chen Yang declared in a cold voice.

Daoist Xie took a glance at Han Li, then cupped his fist in a submissive salute toward Chen Yang.

"You're not very useful in battle, but it seems like you're pretty smart. This place is boring as hell, so having a puppet around will certainly liven things up a little," Chen Yang chuckled.

He then crouched down and fished a pair of black stone vials out of his sleeve, then placed one each onto Han Li and Shi Chuankong's arm before removing the stoppers.

Two black centipedes that were each around three inches in length scurried out of the vials, and after crawling along Han Li and Shi Chuankong's arms momentarily, they dug through their skin with ease before burrowing inside.

Daoist Xie could see a bulge moving along the sleeves of both of their arms before stopping at their hearts, where the bulges took on the form of rings.

"Congratulations, Captain Chen Yang. With such a significant contribution, your claim over the spot of deputy city lord is all but assured," the round-faced scribe congratulated with a warm smile, and Chen Yang was very pleased to hear this.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie's gaze fell upon Han Li and Shi Chuankong as a grim look appeared in his eyes.

……

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li woke up in a dark stone chamber that was only around forty to fifty feet in size, and the room was completely empty aside from a stone bed at the center.

At this moment, he was laying on the ground with sets of bone shackles attached to his arms and legs.

Han Li tugged on the shackles with all his might, but they refused to budge.

"Save your energy. All of these shackles were specially made so that even someone who's opened more than a hundred profound acupoints wouldn't be able to snap them."

Right at this moment, Chen Yang made his way into the room, and he was followed by a gray-robed young man who was trailing along behind him in a respectful manner.

Han Li wasn't surprised to see Chen Yang here, and he said, "Chen Yang, I haven't done anything to harm your interests, and I've already agreed to join Profound City, so why have you still done this to me?"

"It's very impressive that you're able to remain so calm in this situation, but what you just said is laughably naive. Do I need a reason to do this to you? The entire Scalptia Spatial Domain is a prison, and we're all fugitives. Were you expecting to see fairness and justice here?" Chen Yang scoffed in a disdainful manner.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he remained composed as he asked, "What do you plan to do with me?"

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, we may be fugitives, but we're not senseless killers. Truth be told, life is very boring in this place, and the only form of entertainment available to us is watching and betting on arena battles.

“The arena is a money-making machine for the city lord, and a human like you is an extremely rare sight in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so if you were to feature in the arena battles, I'm sure you'll generate a lot of interest," Chen Yang replied with a chilling grin.

"That's why you've captured me?" Han Li asked as his eyes narrowed slightly.

"We don't keep useless people around in Profound City. If you want to live, then fight and prove your worth. Perhaps you'll even be able to earn back your freedom," Chen Yang replied.

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, Chen Yang turned to the gray-robed young man behind him and said, "I'll leave him to you."

"Rest assured, Master Chen, I'll make sure to discipline him well," the gray-robed young man hurriedly assured.

Chen Yang nodded in response, then turned to leave.

"Fellow Daoist Chen, where are Fellow Daoist Shi and Fellow Daoist Xie right now?" Han Li hurriedly asked, but Chen Yang offered no response and quickly vanished out of sight.

Chapter 860: Arena

Following Chen Yang's departure, the gray-robed young man turned back to face Han Li with a cold sneer on his face.

All of a sudden, he grabbed onto Han Li's shackles to hoist him to his feet, then slammed his other fist into Han Li's lower abdomen with a dull thump.

His fist was extremely powerful, and Han Li felt as if a steel knife had been driven into his stomach.

His internal organs instantly began to twist and churn, and his face turned bright red, then deathly pale, as sweat began to pour down his forehead.

"Did that feel good?" the gray-robed young man chuckled.

Han Li's head remained lowered, and he offered no response.

The gray-robed young man was very pleased with Han Li's submissive demeanor, and he pulled out a key to unlock Han Li's shackles as he said, "Good boy. No matter who you are, if you end up in here, you have to follow my orders. Otherwise, that punch will only be an appetizer for what's to come."

Han Li was very much taken aback by this, and he slowly rose to his feet with a perplexed expression.

"Are you thinking about running away? Why don't you take a look at your own chest first?" the gray-robed young man chuckled coldly.

Han Li looked down upon hearing this, and only then did he notice the slight bulge on his chest. He hurriedly inspected the bulge with his spiritual sense to discover a black centipede pressed tightly against his heart.

"That is a Black Tribulation Centipede that's unique to our Green Goat City. If you dare to run away or try to expel the centipede from your body, it'll immediately tear your heart to shreds," the gray-robed young man said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but to the gray-robed young man's disappointment, he didn't appear particularly fazed.

The young man harrumphed coldly as he tossed a black badge at Han Li and continued, "This is your number badge. Come with me, I'll give you a tour of this place."

Han Li caught the badge to find that his name, "Li Feiyu", was inscribed on one side, while on the other side was a large "9" followed by the number "332" in slightly smaller text.

After that, the gray-robed young man led him out of the stone chamber, and even though the young man had his back facing him, Han Li didn't consider a sneak attack.

Judging from the force of that punch from earlier, the young man was quite strong, and at the very least, he had most likely opened roughly the same number of profound acupoints as Han Li.

The two of them quickly emerged from the stone chamber, then made their way down a long corridor before arriving in a spacious hall that was over ten thousand feet in size, and the walls were constructed from some type of black stone material with black patterns engraved upon them.

The walls were also giving off a faint black sheen that gave them an indestructible appearance.

The front of the hall was connected to the outside, and waves of cheers could be heard ringing out from beyond the wall.

At the very back of the hall was a white stone table that was several dozen feet in length, seated behind which were seven or eight crimson-robed figures who appeared to be employees of the arena.

At this moment, there were many people gathered in a line in front of the stone table, all of whom wore the same attire, consisting of a wide cape and knee-length shorts.

The walls on the right and the left of the hall were lined with doors, beyond which were passageways that led to certain places.

"Remember this place. This is the main hall of the arena, and it's the most important place for you. The battles take place on the platforms outside, and all of these people are gladiators, just like you," the gray-robed man said.

"There seem to be quite a few gladiators here," Han Li remarked.

"Of course. There are many gladiators in our arena, some of whom are slaves like you, while others are residents of Profound City looking to hone their abilities. All of the gladiators are split up into ten areas, and you're in the ninth one," the gray-robed young man replied.

"I see. Why are all of these people lined up here?" Han Li asked.

"Take a look at your badge, what do you see under your name?" the gray-robed young man replied with a question of his own.

Han Li pulled out his badge, and under his own name, he saw a small number: "10".

"What's this?"

"That's your profound points total. You receive compensation for participating in arena battles regardless of the outcome. Of course, if you win, then you'll earn far more profound points. All newbies like yourself receive ten free profound points, and you can use these points to exchange for things like weapons, beast cores, and pills here.

“As for what the prices of certain items are, you can find them on the list over there," the gray-robed young man introduced as he pointed at a list on the wall next to the white stone table.

Han Li turned his gaze to the list on the wall, and his eyes instantly lit up slightly.

Weapons and pills weren't of particular interest to him, but beast cores were certainly very appealing to him.

The gray-robed young man was very pleased with Han Li's reaction, and he continued, "On top of that, you can also exchange your profound points for chances to enter the star pond to cultivate."

"What's the star pond?" Han Li asked.

"It's a pond that was constructed by City Lord Du through special means, and it can harness the power of the stars in the sky. The star pond is extremely rich with starpower, and cultivating inside it is far more effective for opening profound acupoints than devouring beast cores," the gray-robed young man replied.

However, a mocking sneer then appeared on his face as he continued, "Having said that, it costs a hundred profound points to enter the star pond, so you're not even close."

Han Li was unbothered by the young man's mockery, and he began to contemplate his current circumstances.

It seemed that he wasn't in a particularly terrible situation at the moment, as long as he could obtain more beast cores, he would be able to continue to grow stronger.

As for the problems concerning the Black Tribulation Centipede, Violet Spirit, Shi Chuankong, and Daoist Xie, he would just have to think of solutions later.

If Chen Yang were telling the truth, then he was confident in his ability to resolve all of those problems as long as he could prove himself to be of sufficient value.

For now, his top priority was to survive in this arena.

The gray-robed young man seemed to have gleaned his thoughts, and he encouraged, "All of the weapons, beast cores, and other items here are of a higher quality than what you'll find outside, and that's not even to mention the star pond, so as long as you have what it takes, you can live a far better life in the arena than outside."

Han Li nodded in response.

"That's about all I have to show you, you can familiarize yourself with this place in your own time. This passageway leads to the lobby for the ninth area, and you'll have your own room there. If you have to fight in an arena battle, your badge will inform you," the young man said as he pointed at a passageway on the left side of the hall.

Han Li turned to discover a large "9" inscribed above the entrance of the passageway.

The other passageways were also marked with numbers, as well as some other special symbols, one of which was none other than the star pond.

However, that passageway was tightly shut.

All of a sudden, the gray-robed young man leaned in closer to Han Li, then threatened in a cold voice, "I brought you here, so just fight your battles and don't try and funny business. Otherwise, you're going to regret it!"

Han Li lowered his head and nodded in response, and the gray-robed young man's expression eased slightly upon seeing this.

Following the young man's departure, Han Li remained standing on the spot for a moment, then made his way out of the hall.

As it turned out, the hall was suspended in mid-air, while down below as a massive plaza, at the center of which were three ovular platforms arranged in a triangular formation.

Around the three platforms was a wide and deep trench with smooth walls that were hundreds of feet tall and directly perpendicular to the ground. A row of black railing was present on top of the wall, and it was constructed from the same indestructible-looking material as the walls of the hall.

Behind the railing were rows upon rows of spectator stands that were filled with countless seats.

At the very center of the stands was a wide platform where bets were submitted, and above the platform was a huge board that displayed the names of the gladiators and their odds.

"I'll put fifty profound coins on Cai Zheng!"

"I'll put seventy profound coins on the Scaled Wolf Beast!"

There were many people gathered around the betting platform, placing their bets.

At this moment, three arena battles were taking place, two of which were battles between gladiators and scaled beasts, while the third one was between two gladiators.

Before long, one of the battles had concluded with a gladiator being torn to shreds by his scaled beast opponent, and his blood and scraps of his body were strewn all over the platform.

The spectators in the stands were extremely excited to see this, and some were even looking a little deranged as a chaotic crescendo of thunderous voices rang out in response to the outcome.

The gray-robed young man had told Han Li that one would earn profound points for participating in arena battles regardless of whether they won or lost, but he had failed to mention that a loss very likely entailed death.

Han Li observed the arena battles for a short while, then made his way back into the hall to look at the list on the wall.

Just as the gray-robed young man had said, profound points could be exchanged for many things here.

"Five-hundred-year-old Fierce Head Beast Core, five profound points."

"Eight-hundred-year-old Titan Bear Scaled Beast Core, ten profound points."

"Pig-faced Beast Core..."

"Wyrm Scale Pill refined using a thousand-year-old Wyrm Scale Beast Core as the primary ingredient, eighteen profound points."

"Golden Edge Tiger Bone Blade refined from the bones of a two-thousand-year-old Golden Edge Scaled Tiger, thirty-eight profound acupoints."

Chapter 861: Conversion and Absorption

As Han Li's gaze roamed down the list, the prices of the items continued to increase.

While traveling to Green Goat City with Chen Yang and the others, Han Li had learned some things about the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and while he now knew in retrospect that Chen Yang was not to be trusted, there was no reason for Chen Yang to lie to him about the scaled beasts in this domain.

Hence, he had a rough idea of the value of the items on the points exchange list.

The scaled beasts of the Scalptia Spatial Domain were formidable creatures that were born with Spatial Tempering Stage power at a minimum, and they could absorb starpower to further enhance their own powers. Hence, the older a scaled beast was, the more powerful it was considered to be, and the more starpower its beast core would contain.

For all of the gladiators here, regardless of whether they had come here of their own volition or been enslaved like Han Li, all of them had a shared objective, which was to earn profound points so that they could exchange for items on the list to enhance their own powers.

As long as one had sufficient profound points, even beast cores of scaled beasts that were tens of thousands of years old could be purchased, but of course, the price was extremely steep.

At the moment, he only had ten profound points, so he would have to bide his time for now.

Han Li shook his head as he heaved a faint sigh, then continued to survey the list.

All of a sudden, his attention was drawn to a certain item on the list.

"Two-thousand-year-old Tarot Beast Core, three profound points."

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he made his way over to the stone table, then handed over his badge to one of the crimson-robed employees as he declared, "I would like three two-thousand-year-old Tarot Beast Cores."

Many of the nearby gladiators faltered slightly upon hearing this, then turned to Han Li with undisguised mockery in their eyes.

"Are you new here? Tarot Beast Cores contain a lot of starpower, but due to the special physical constitution of these beasts, the starpower in their beast cores is very chaotic, making it very difficult to absorb, and there's a very good chance that most of it will be wasted," the crimson-robed employee said.

"I see," Han Li mused with an enlightened expression.

No wonder these beast cores were so cheap.

"Thank you for informing me of this, but I would still like to exchange for these beast cores," Han Li said with a smile.

With only ten profound acupoints at his disposal, he really couldn't afford anything else.

The crimson-robed employee didn't speak any further on the matter, and he pulled out a short silver rod before waving it over Han Li's badge, upon which his ten profound points were instantly reduced to one.

After that, he pulled out three egg-sized beast cores before handing them to Han Li.

Han Li stowed the beast cores away, then began to make his way toward the ninth area.

After passing through a dark passageway, he arrived in a spacious area that resembled a cave.

The cave was hemispherical in shape, and around twenty to thirty stone chambers had been carved into its walls, with a number assigned to each chamber.

Several glowing white stones were embedded into the ceiling of the cave, but they were only able to illuminate a small area, while the rest of the cave remained quite dim.

At this moment, there were around a dozen gladiators seated in the cave, conversing boisterously with one another, and all of them turned to Han Li with surprised expressions.

Han Li paid no heed to them, and he quickly scanned the cave to track down the room that was labeled "332", then began to make his way toward it.

Right at this moment, a tall and imposing man with a scar on his face got in his way and sneered, "You're just going to walk in here without greeting the boss first? You newbies are becoming ruder by the day!"

Han Li turned to the man with an expressionless manner, and the man continued, "You have ten points on you right? Hand them over to me, and I'll pass them onto Boss Toxic Dragon for you. Those are the rules."

Everyone began to gather around, eager to watch the situation unfold.

Han Li took a glance at the bystanders, and he didn't say anything.

"Are you deaf or stupid?" the man roared as he slammed his fist into the door of Han Li's room.

"Get out of my way! A good dog knows not to block its owner's path!" Han Li said in a cold voice.

"Yo Scarface, he's calling you a dog!" a round-faced fatty chortled.

"You can't even get on top of a newbie, Scarface?" another man sneered, and before long, everyone was joining in on the mockery.

The man's face instantly turned bright red, while a furious look appeared in his eyes.

Despite his imposing frame, he was one of the weaker gladiators in the ninth area, and he was often mocked for that.

Hence, he often took out his pent-up rage and frustration on those weaker than him, and bullying weak-looking newbies like Han Li was his favorite pastime, yet he was the one being humiliated here.

"You must have a death wish!" Scarface roared as he chopped a hand down toward Han Li's head, aiming to split Han Li's head into two.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he retaliated with his fist, and a loud crack rang out as Scarface's arm was instantly snapped before being slammed against his chest.

He stumbled back in an unsteady fashion, only coming to a halt after crashing into the wall behind him, following which he threw up a large mouthful of blood.

He stood with his back against the wall, staring blankly at Han Li with an astonished expression, and all of the other gladiators had also fallen into a stunned silence.

Han Li paid no heed to them as he made his way into his room, then slammed the door shut.

The stone chamber was only around thirty to forty feet in size, and it was completely unfurnished with the exception of a stone bed, a table, and a chair.

A length of white tree root could be seen protruding down from the center of the ceiling, giving off a white glow that illuminated the entire room.

To Han Li's surprise, the white light was fueled by starpower!

He immediately released his spiritual sense toward the tree root, trying to find out where the starpower was coming from, but the material that was used to construct the walls of the room were able to keep out spiritual sense, thereby foiling his plans.

Even so, he could clearly see that the tree root didn't innately harbor starpower. Instead, the starpower was being transmitted into it from elsewhere, and the root was only acting as a medium.

However, the root wasn't giving off a lot of starlight, only just enough to support normal cultivation.

Han Li quickly turned his attention away from the tree root and began scouring his room with his spiritual sense. After ensuring that nothing was amiss, he sat down onto the bed, where two sets of gladiator uniforms, consisting of a cape and a pair of shorts, had been prepared for him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the uniforms, but he still took off his clothes and put on one of the sets of uniforms.

After setting down his original clothes onto the bed, he opened his mouth to release his Heaven Controlling Vial, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

Prior to reaching Green Goat City, he had swallowed the Heaven Controlling Vial in case of unforeseen mishaps, and it was extremely fortunate that he had done so. Otherwise, there was a very good chance that the Heaven Controlling Vial would've already fallen into the hands of Chen Yang.

After inspecting the Heaven Controlling Vial momentarily, Han Li swallowed it again before taking a seat under the white tree root.

Given the current circumstances, cultivation was his top priority.

Han Li pulled out a Tarot Beast Core, and sure enough, it did contain a great deal of starpower, but all of it was very chaotic and churning like boiling water.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he still swallowed the beast core before closing his eyes to cultivate.

The beast core quickly melted into a ball of starpower in his stomach, but this burst of starpower was like an untamed wild horse. It immediately began darting in all directions in his body before seeping out into the surrounding air.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts to absorb the starpower, but just as the arena employee had proclaimed, he was only able to absorb a small portion of the starpower, while the rest continued to seep out of his body.

Right at this moment, the Heaven Controlling Vial in his stomach suddenly shuddered, following which a burst of faint light appeared at its opening, and all of the dissipating starpower was instantly sucked back in.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he hurriedly began channeling his Wingform Ascension Arts again, but he wasn't able to absorb much of the starpower before the rest was sucked into the Heaven Controlling Vial.

To that, he could only heave a resigned sigh.

When it came to the ability to absorb starpower, there was no way that he could compete against the Heaven Controlling Vial.

The starpower within the Tarot Beast Core surged into the Heaven Controlling Vial, and a drop of green liquid gradually took shape.

In the instant that the drop of spirit liquid fully took shape, the Heaven Controlling Vial immediately ceased its absorption of starpower, leaving the remaining starpower to swirl around the vial.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then continued to channel his Wingform Ascension Arts to absorb the residual starpower around the vial.

After being drawn back into his body by the Heaven Controlling Vial, the starpower had become far more mellow, allowing him to absorb it with ease, and the starpower emanating from the tree root up above was also fusing into his body.

The starpower surged into the second profound acupoint of the Wingform Ascension Arts, which gradually began to open.

While Han Li was cultivating in his room, Scarface was seated in another stone chamber, seemingly waiting for something.

His mangled arm had already returned to normal, but the skin on the arm was still very purple and bruised.

Occasionally, he would turn to take a resentful glance in the direction of Han Li's stone chamber.

All of the gladiators who had witnessed the incident between Han Li and Scarface quickly departed, with many of them mocking Scarface as they left.

Chapter 862: Boos

Close to a day passed by in a flash.

The door of the stone chamber across from Scarface's slowly swung open, and Scarface immediately sprang to his feet as he rushed out of his own room.

The sound of footsteps rang out as a tall and imposing figure emerged from the stone chamber.

It was a one-eyed giant of a man who was significantly taller than even Scarface, and he was also extremely muscular, resembling a bipedal bear.

There was a large azure bear head tattooed onto the man's chest, giving him an even more fearsome appearance, and his entire body was giving off a mountainous aura.

"Boss, you have to stand up for me!" Scarface immediately yelled as he fell to his knees in front of the giant man.

The man was none other than Toxic Dragon, and his expression instantly darkened slightly at the sight of Scarface's arm.

"What happened to your arm, Scarface?"

"My arm was snapped by a newbie!"

Scarface immediately gave Toxic Dragon a heavily embellished recount of his run-in with Han Li, placing extra emphasis on how Han Li refused to hand over his profound points, even after hearing about how Scarface was going to pass them onto Toxic Dragon.

"Is Scarface telling the truth?" Toxic Dragon asked as he turned to another gladiator of the ninth area who just so happened to be passing by.

"That's pretty much what happened. That newbie really was quite arrogant," the gladiator corroborated.

"Looks like someone needs to be taught a lesson!" Toxic Dragon harrumphed coldly as he began making his way toward Han Li's stone chamber.

However, right at this moment, a burst of black light suddenly flashed over a badge that was hanging from his waist.

Toxic Dragon stopped in his tracks, then took a glance down at the badge with slightly furrowed brows.

"Lucky bastard," he harrumphed coldly as he began making his way back to his own stone chamber.

Before Scarface had a chance to raise a question, Toxic Dragon said, "I have a battle to fight. Rest assured, I'll make sure to teach that newbie a good lesson once I'm back."

Scarface hurriedly nodded in response, and Toxic Dragon took one final glance at Han Li's stone chamber before departing.

"Looks like you'll get to live a little longer," Scarface spat in a resentful manner before also departing.

……

Han Li was naturally completely oblivious to what had just happened outside.

At this moment, he was seated with his legs crossed in his room, holding the final Tarot Beast Core in his hand, and after a brief hesitation, he swallowed the beast core before channeling his Wingform Ascension Arts.

Moments later, the second profound acupoint on his leg lit up, and as time passed, it became brighter and brighter.

Some time later, the light emanating from the profound acupoint abruptly brightened significantly, then immediately dimmed again.

An ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Thanks to the three Tarot Beast Cores, he was finally able to open a second profound acupoint.

He pushed off against the ground with one hand to launch himself up into the air, then began to walk around in his room at a far faster speed than before, and the heavy sensation that he felt in his body was also significantly alleviated.

The more progress he made in the Wingform Ascension Arts, the higher the regard that he held it in, particularly in this environment, where flight was impossible.

However, he only had one profound point left, so he had to earn some more.

Right at this moment, the badge that was sitting on his bed suddenly began to glow and buzz.

Han Li picked up the badge to find that a line of small text had appeared upon it.

A pleased smile appeared on his face upon seeing this, and he made his way out of his room.

At this moment, there were around a dozen gladiators gathered in the ninth area, and all of them turned to look at Han Li with peculiar expressions.

Han Li paid no heed to them as he made his way out of the lobby to arrive in the exchange hall, then continued down another passageway without pause.

Inside the passageway was a staircase that led downward, and upon arriving at the foot of the staircase, Han Li found himself in another hall that was similar in size to the exchange hall above, but this place was rather dimly lit.

At the front of the hall was a giant stone gate that was tightly shut, and at this moment, there was no one else in the hall with the exception of a man with a single horn on his head.

"You're Li Feiyu?" the horned man asked with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

"That's right," Han Li replied.

"You're here right on time. You have a battle coming up soon," the horned man said, then strode over to the stone gate before slapping it with the palm of his hand.

A small opening that was only large enough to fit a single person appeared on the stone gate, and the horned man gestured for Han Li to wait, then stepped into the opening.

"We have a truly exciting match lined up for everyone today! On one side, we have a Tiger Scaled Beast that's over 3,500 years old. This will be its fourth battle, and prior to this, it's already defeated three gladiators and devoured two of them on the spot!" the horned man declared in an enthusiastic voice, and a chorus of excited cheers rang out from the spectator stands in response.

At this moment, there were no battles taking place on the other two platforms, perhaps to highlight Han Li's first battle.

"On the other side, we have an extremely rare human gladiator from the Immortal Realm, Li Feiyu!" the horned man continued.

The spectators in the stands instantly erupted into thunderous cheers upon hearing this.

"A human gladiator? I can't even remember the last time I saw one!"

"This really is a rare treat!"

"If I recall correctly, the last human gladiator that showed up was over a thousand years ago, and he was torn to shreds. Humans are just too weak."

The horned man was very pleased to see the reaction garnered by Han Li, and he declared, "The battle between the Tiger Scaled Beast and Li Feiyu is about to commence soon, so place your bets now, and no further bets will be taken once the battle begins."

The initial odds for the battle between Han Li and the Tiger Scaled Beast were listed as 5:1.

"I'll put a hundred profound coins on the Tiger Scaled Beast!"

"I'll put a hundred and fifty profound coins on the Tiger Scaled Beast!"

"I'll put three hundred profound coins on the Tiger Scaled Beast!"

"You only have three hundred profound coins left, are you going to bet it all on one battle?"

"Before I was cast into exile here, one of my good friends was killed by a human cultivator from the Immortal Realm, so I have to bet everything I have against this human bastard in honor of my friend!"

Han Li's identity as a human cultivator had completely riled up the crowd, and not only were there far more bets being placed than on average, most of them were against Han Li.

As more and more bets were placed, the odds gradually shifted from 5:1 to 12:1, which meant that if someone bet on Han Li and he came out on top, then their winnings would be twelve times their initial bet, whereas the winnings for a successful bet on the Tiger Scaled Beast would only be one twelfth of the initial bet.

Even so, the vast majority of bets were still placed on the Tiger Scaled Beast. After all, this was essentially free money.

"Time's up! Let the battle begin!" the horned man roared, and the stone gate that separated the arena from the hall that Han Li was in was slowly lifted.

The commotion ringing out within the arena instantly crescendoed to a peak, and the excitement in the air was almost palpable as Han Li was revealed.

Han Li slowly rose to his feet, then made his way into the massive arena.

As he did so, his head was slightly lowered, and he was carefully examining the ground, which was riddled with dark red stains from all of the blood that had seeped into it over the years.

"That's the human? He looks way too frail!"

"What a snoozefest! He won't even be able to withstand a single attack from the scaled beast."

"And he's not even equipped with any armor or weapons! Is he asking to be killed?"

"What's the point in a battle like this? It's nothing more than a gimmick. No wonder the odds are so skewed."

……

On the spectator stands, a muscular green-skinned man was pointing at a horned man sitting beside him as he chortled with derision, "You're betting on that human to win? You must be crazy! If he actually wins, I'll kneel down and call you my father!"

"Anything's possible! There could always be a miracle..." the horned man protested, but it was clear that he wasn't very confident at all.

He had bet on the human after being drawn in by the alluring odds, but as soon as he caught sight of Han Li, his heart was filled with despair.

"A miracle? How can you still be so naive after staying in this godforsaken place for so long?" the green-skinned man chortled with mirth.

The horned man offered no response as a grim look appeared on his face.

In his mind, it was already beyond a shadow of a doubt that the human was going to lose.

A wave of boos instantly rang out across the spectator stands, and no one believed that this frail-looking human would be able to oppose a fearsome 3,500-year-old scaled beast.

At this point, the only thing that they had to look forward to was seeing the human being torn to shreds.

Chapter 863: Stop the Battle

At the center of the spectator stands.

There was an independent VIP booth, within which was a pair of long stone chairs that were covered in sheets of beast hide. In front of the stone chairs was a stone table, upon which were placed two huge stone cups that were filled with some type of fresh beast blood.

Seated on one of the chairs was a muscular man with a dark complexion, and there was a woman with a curvaceous body beside him, massaging his arm with her delicate hands.

On the other chair sat another man with dark green skin, clad in a suit of white bone armor. There was a layer of gray scales on his face, as well as three long scars left behind by a claw swipe from a scaled beast, giving him a fearsome appearance.

The armorclad man was staring intently at the woman's seductive body, with his gaze roaming over her voluptuous chest, down to her supple backside, then to her exquisite legs, and he was making no effort to conceal the lust in his eyes.

"How about we raise the stakes even further, Hu Bi?" the muscular man proposed with a smile.

"You want to raise the stakes? Did you hit your head recently or something, Chen Yang? Can you not see how frail that human is?" the armorclad man asked in a surprised manner.

"Risk and reward come hand in hand. It doesn't matter if I lose the bet, it's all about the thrill," Chen Yang replied in a nonchalant manner.

"If you want to give me free money, then I'm certainly not going to turn you down. What do you want from me?" Hu Bi asked with a wide grin.

"I want that Thorn Scaled Beast Core that the city lord gave you last time," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

A hesitant look appeared on Hu Bi's face upon hearing this, and for some reason, as he turned to look at Han Li in the arena, a sense of unease welled up in his heart.

However, he then immediately brushed off this inexplicable sense of unease. The Tiger Scaled Beast in the arena was over 3,500 years old, so there was no way it would be defeated by that human.

The environment in the Scalptia Spatial Domain was extremely inhospitable, so for most scaled beasts, it was already an achievement just to live to a thousand years of age.

For a scaled beast that was able to live 3,500 years, that was both a reflection of their power and their luck.

"Alright, I'll take you up on that bet, but if I win, then I'm taking your woman!" Hu Bi said as he took a lustful glance at the woman beside Chen Yang.

"Deal," Chen Yang agreed as he patted the woman on the backside.

The woman turned to take a seductive glance at Hu Bi, and the latter immediately felt a rush of heat surge through his lower abdomen.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar suddenly rang out in the arena, instantly drawing everyone's attention.

A giant tiger-like beast that was over a hundred feet tall and covered in black and white scales had just been released from its cage.

The beast had a mouthful of gleaming sharp fangs, two of which were particularly long and sharp, resembling a pair of jagged spears. As it raised its head to roar up at the heavens, its eyes were filled with rage and resentment.

The commotion in the spectator stands instantly died down in the wake of its furious roar, but a thunderous chorus of cheers then immediately rang out once again.

……

Excited and frenetic voices were ringing out from all parts of the spectator stands, and the atmosphere in the arena had become more heated than ever.

However, as one of the centers of attention, Han Li remained completely unaffected by the frenzied atmosphere around him.

He was observing the scaled beast with a cold look in his eyes, and there weren't any aura fluctuations emanating from his body at all, giving him the appearance of a harmless mortal.

After letting loose its furious roar, the Tiger Scaled Beast finally lowered its head and turned its attention to the tiny human before it.

Immediately thereafter, it lowered its center of gravity slightly as a low snarl began to build in its throat, and in the next instant, it sprang forward at an incredible speed, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

Han Li immediately took a step backward upon seeing this, and at the same time, he arched back and aimed a kick up at the Tiger Scaled Beast's jaw while all thirty-eight of the profound acupoints on his body lit up in unison.

A loud thump rang out as the scaled beast was stopped cold in its tracks, and its head was also knocked back violently by the force of Han Li's kick.

All of the spectators in the stands were stunned into silence upon seeing this. They were expecting to see the human die to a single blow from the scaled beast, yet things had taken a completely unexpected turn.

Hu Bi was also stunned to see this, and he leaned forward slightly as he stared intently at Han Li from afar.

Right at this moment, the scaled beast's head abruptly snapped back down again before slamming onto the ground like a fallen mountain.

The platform was shattered, sending loose rocks and dust flying in all directions, and it was impossible to see Han Li through the debris.

A loud roar rang out as the Tiger Scaled Beast charged out of the cloud of dust, and pressed tightly against one of its giant fangs was none other than Han Li.

At this moment, Han Li was resisting the scaled beast's fang with both hands, while his feet were digging into the ground, but he was still pushed back by the fearsome beast. His feet dug a pair of deep trenches into the ground, and before long, he had crashed into the wall behind him.

The material that the wall was constructed from was extremely resilient, and it felt slightly cool against Han Li's back.

Han Li's chest was heaving violently as he abruptly pressed down with both hands, forcing the Tiger Scaled Beast's head downard.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the fang of the Tiger Scaled Beast was diverted downward before plunging into the ground, and all of a sudden, it was as if its head had been nailed firmly into place.

Han Li seized this opportunity to spring up into the air, stepping onto the Tiger Scaled Beast's before launching himself onto its head.

The Tiger Scaled Beast shook its head violently, trying to shake him off, but Han Li merely lowered his center of gravity slightly before throwing an almighty punch into the scaled beast's head.

A burst of powerful shockwaves erupted forth in all directions as the Tiger Scaled Beast's head was slammed down from above, and its two protruding fangs pierced even deeper into the ground.

Han Li didn't grow complacent just because he had managed to control the Tiger Scaled Beast, and he continued to rain down one punch after another.

The Tiger Scaled Beast's head shuddered over and over again as the cracks on the platform beneath it widened further and further, and several streams of blood were flowing down from its head.

All of the spectators were looking on in a stunned silence.

It had only been several minutes since the commencement of the battle, yet this frail-looking human had already established complete dominance over the Tiger Scaled Beast.

After withstanding over ten punches in a row, the Tiger Scaled Beast was laying on the ground in a limp fashion, and its body was only twitching slightly in response to each successive punch, indicating that it was on the brink of death.

At this point, Han Li's fists were already completely drenched in blood, and it was unclear whether the blood belonged to the Tiger Scaled Beast or himself.

The stunned silence wore on for a little longer before everyone erupted into cheers, and on this occasion, all of the cheers were directed at Han Li.

"Li Feiyu, Li Feiyu, Li Feiyu..."

"I won... I won!" the horned man that had bet on Han Li screamed in excitement, and tears were beginning to well up in his eyes.

Up in the VIP booth, Hu Bi spat onto the ground in disgust, while Chen Yang continued to observe the battle with a calm smile on his face, seemingly completely unsurprised by Han Li's performance.

Hu Bi finally realized that he had been tricked upon seeing Chen Yang's expression, and his brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "You have some insider information on this match, don't you?"

"What insider information could I possibly have? I was simply lucky to have picked out a dark horse. Besides, the battle still isn't decided yet," Chen Yang replied in a lazy manner.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a thunderous roar suddenly rang out within the arena, and all of the scales on the Tiger Scaled Beast's body abruptly stood up on end like countless sharp blades, forcing Han Li to jump down from its head.

Just a moment ago, the Tiger Scaled Beast had been clinging onto life by a thread, but in this instant, its eyes suddenly rolled back, and its original black pupils were replaced by a second set of pupils that were purple and green in color.

Chen Yang's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he instantly sprang to his feet, throwing off the woman who was clinging to his body in the process.

"Haha! It's a dual pupil scaled beast! With this mutation, it can no longer be considered a D tier scaled beast. Looks like I'll be having the last laugh, Chen Yang," Hu Bi chortled with glee.

Chen Yang paid no heed to Hu Bi as he murmured to himself with a grim expression, "A mutated dual pupil Tiger Scaled Beast is a C tier scaled beast. I have to put an end to this battle."

He then turned to depart from the VIP booth, but he was stopped in his tracks by Hu Bi.

"Where are you going, Brother Chen?"

Chapter 864: Unexpected

"You don't know what's going on here, we can't allow this battle to continue!" Chen Yang said in an urgent voice as he pressed Hu Bi's arm down and attempted to leave by force.

"Don't forget the rules! Once an arena battle commences, it can't be ended prematurely under any circumstances! Are you trying to go against the city lord’s rules just because you don't want to lose your woman to me?" Hu Bi countered in an enraged voice.

Chen Yang calmed down slightly upon hearing this, and he brushed Hu Bi's arm aside as he said in a cold voice, "I'm going to see the city lord right now."

"You can do whatever please, but the city lord isn't going to break his own rules for anyone," Hu Ni said with a cold sneer as he withdrew his arm.

Chen Yang paid no heed to him as he rushed out of the VIP booth.

At this point, some of the spectators in the stands had finally identified the fact that they were seeing a dual pupil Tiger Scaled Beast.

Everyone was left feeling rather flabbergasted by this unexpected turn of events, and they weren't sure if they should continue cheering for the human or jump ship to support the Tiger Scaled Beast.

At the same time, some people were beginning to feel a little sympathetic toward Han Li.

The horned man that had bet on Han Li had already fallen onto his backside with a despairing look on his face, while the green-skinned man who had been mocking him this entire time had a wide smile on his face, feeling very much vindicated.

As for Han Li himself, he was observing his opponent with an apprehensive look on his face.

As soon as this second set of pupils appeared, the Tiger Scaled Beast's aura was instantly elevated to a whole new level.

Han Li leaned forward slightly while stepping back to adopt a simple fist stance as he stared intently at the dual pupil Tiger Scaled Beast.

Having already been beaten to within an inch of its life earlier, the Tiger Scaled Beast had learned not to charge recklessly at Han Li. Instead, it was baring its fangs as it snarled menacingly at him.

Right at this moment, the Tiger Scaled Beast suddenly shrugged its shoulders forward, and a string of cracks and pops rang out as countless scales flew off its body before hurtling toward Han Li like a volley of arrows.

In response, Han Li dug his rear foot into the ground, and he instantly vanished from the spot, only to reappear to the left of the storm of scales an instant later.

However, the Tiger Scaled Beast seemed to have already anticipated this, and it appeared before Han Li in the blink of an eye before biting down toward his head.

Han Li immediately crouched down to just barely duck under the scaled beast's cavernous mouth.

Immediately thereafter, he sprang up into the air before throwing a vicious punch upward.

A dull thump rang out as the Tiger Scaled Beast was thrown to the side by the force of Han Li's punch, but after delivering the blow, Han Li's fist was trembling incessantly, and all of his fingers aside from his middle and index fingers were riddled with bleeding gashes.

However, he didn't seem to have noticed this at all, and he continued to stare intently at the Tiger Scaled Beast while rushing after it in pursuit, aiming to land a lethal blow, but before he could reach the Tiger Scaled Beast, it had already recovered from the punch.

After taking a moment to steady itself, it unleashed another barrage of scales at Han Li, forcing him to roll to the side to evade the attack.

Immediately thereafter, all of the profound acupoints on his legs lit up in unison, and he launched himself at the Tiger Scaled Beast's head from the side.

The scaled beast didn't back down in the slightest as it opened its mouth to bite down at Han Li, but this time, Han Li took no evasive measures.

Instead, he raised a fist before slamming it forcefully into the ground.

Thanks to the impact that his fist made against the ground, Han Li was able to launch himself several dozen feet into the air, thereby allowing him to evade the Tiger Scaled Beast's spear-like fangs.

He then stepped onto the Tiger Scaled Beast's nose and attempted to charge at its glabella once again, but as soon as his foot left the scaled beast's nose, it suddenly ducked its head to the side, forcing a misstep from Han Li.

Unable to fly, Han Li couldn't change directions in mid-air, so he could only step down toward the Tiger Scaled Beast's cheek.

However, before his foot was able to land on the scaled beast's face, three of its whiskers suddenly began sweeping toward him like a set of sharp longswords.

The whiskers seemed to be enveloped in a layer of starlight, making them incredibly sharp, and they were threatening to tear Han Li's body to shreds.

In this dire situation, Han Li joined the index and middle fingers of his right hand, then reached out to press them against the Tiger Scaled Beast's uppermost whisker, causing the whisker to bend downward.

Before the other two whiskers could reach him, he pushed down onto the uppermost whisker to propel himself further up into the air.

The spectators in the stands instantly erupted into raucous cheers upon seeing this, but Han Li paid no heed to their thunderous voices as he swiveled around in mid-air, ultimately landing beside the Tiger Scaled Beast's left ear as opposed to on top of its glabella.

He immediately grabbed onto the Tiger Scaled Beast's ear, then aimed a kick right into its earhole.

At the same time, he channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts and Wingform Ascension Arts in unison and focused all of his power into that single kick.

A loud thump rang out as the Tiger Scaled Beast's head snapped to the right, causing its entire body to sway in the same direction.

Han Li fell out of the scaled beast's ear with half of his body drenched in blood, and after landing on the ground, he stumbled momentarily before falling backward.

As for the Tiger Scaled Beast, it swayed from side to side momentarily in an unsteady fashion before also falling to the ground.

Blood was gushing out of his left ear and his eye sockets, and his aura had become even more feeble than before.

"What the hell? Both of them are down, who wins here?"

The spectator stands had erupted into a thunderous commotion, but only a small number of people were cheering for Li Feiyu, while the rest were urging the Tiger Scaled Beast to devour its opponent.

Even though Han Li had put on a spectacular show for them, most of the spectators had bet on the Tiger Scaled Beast, so they were still rooting for it to emerge victorious.

Amid the chorus of raucous cheers, the Tiger Scaled Beast was the first to get up from the ground, and even though its vision was already blurry with blood, it still began trudging unsteadily toward Han Li.

However, it was only able to stagger three steps forward before collapsing to the ground once again, and its head landed directly in front of Han Li.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and he fought back the excruciating pain in his leg as he struggled to his feet, then trudged arduously onto the Tiger Scaled Beast's head.

He sat down on top of the scaled beast's glabella, then injected what little power he had left into the two fingers that his Flower Branch domain had been refined into before plunging them down into the Tiger Scaled Beast's head.

After a series of repeated blows, a fist-sized hole was smashed into the Tiger Scaled Beast's glabella, and Han Li reached inside before pulling out a fist-sized purple beast core.

A pleased smile appeared on his face as he felt the abundant starpower within the beast core, and he didn't even bother to wipe the blood from it before swallowing it whole.

The spectator stands were silent for a moment, immediately following which a wave of thunderous cheers rang out.

The horned man was chortling with glee as he turned to the green-skinned man beside him and yelled, "I did it, son! I'm rich!"

……

Inside the city lord's manor.

Du Qingyang was standing in front of his desk with one hand clasped behind his back while massaging a pair of beast bones in his other hand.

After a brief silence, he turned around to face Chen Yang and said, "It's fine, I'm already aware of all of this. In fact, I personally issued the order for his opponent to be replaced with that Tiger Scaled Beast."

"But City Lord Du, there's no way that Li Feiyu will be able to defeat that dual pupil Tiger Scaled Beast. If he dies in this battle, then his true spirit bloodline will go to waste," Chen Yang said in an urgent manner.

"If he dies, then so be it. I know what I'm doing. This is not something for you to be concerned about, you can go now," Du Qingyang said as he waved a dismissive hand.

Chen Yang duly obliged and departed.

By the time he returned to the arena, all of the spectators were already beginning to leave, and everyone was still looking very excited as they discussed the riveting battle that they had just witnessed.

Upon re-entering the VIP booth, he was greeted by the sight of Hu Bi with an arm wrapped around the woman, and he already had one hand slipped down the front of her robes.

The woman was unable to break free from Hu Bi's iron grip, so she could only turn to Chen Yang with a pitiable look on her face.

Chen Yang's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, then turned his gaze to the arena.

Chapter 865: Blood Pond

"He won," Hu Bi grumbled as he stood up and pushed the woman in his arms toward Chen Yang. "I don't know how that bastard managed to kill a C tier scaled beast with so few profound acupoints opened, but he did it."

Chen Yang casually brushed the woman away, pushing her down onto the other chair as he asked with furrowed brows, "What happened?"

"That's what I want to know!" Hu Bi spat in a frustrated manner. "I'll get someone to deliver the beast core to your manor tomorrow."

After that, Hu Bi stormed out of the VIP booth, and Chen Yang took a glance at the woman before also departing.

……

At this moment, Han Li's entire body was riddled with wounds, and in particular, his legs were in excruciating pain as he trudged arduously back into the dim hall.

The horned man was already waiting for him in the hall, and he said, "You did very well for your first battle. Honestly, I thought you were screwed. Give me your badge."

Han Li removed the badge that was hanging from his waist before handing it over, and the horned man accepted the badge before waving a golden baton over it.

The number of profound points on the badge was instantly increased by twenty, much to Han Li's elation.

The horned man returned the badge to Han Li, then clapped his hands together, and two tall and imposing armorclad figures stepped into the hall, then grabbed onto Han Li's arms and hoisted him up into the air before dragging him toward a side door.

Han Li was naturally very alarmed by this, and he immediately tried to struggle free from the armorclad figures, only to discover that their hands were as hard and unyielding as iron shackles.

On top of that, their arms were as cold as ice, and it was as if they didn't possess bodies of flesh at all

Upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that the two armorclad figures had dark green skin that was bulging with veins, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

On top of that, their eyes were completely empty and lifeless, as if they were a pair of corpses, but they were still breathing, and their bodies were giving off a freezing aura.

"Don't be alarmed. Your injuries are quite severe, and they're taking you away to receive treatment. Otherwise, you'll be in no shape to take part in any further battles," the horned man said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then ceased his struggles, allowing the pair of armorclad figures to carry him into the side door.

Beyond the side door was a long passageway, and as Han Li continued to be dragged along, he deduced that the two armorclad figures were most likely some type of refined corpse, but he couldn't tell exactly what type of refinement process had been used.

The two armorclad figures led Han Li to the end of a passageway and into a large stone chamber, at the center of was a pond that was over a hundred feet in size and filled with some type of viscous, bright red liquid that very much resembled blood.

The center of the pond was bubbling incessantly, and wisps of red mist were rising up from its surface, filling the entire room with a strong bloody aroma.

However, the smell wasn't rank or pungent at all. Instead, Han Li was struck by a sense of reinvigoration as he inhaled the aroma.

The two armorclad figures strode over to the edge of the pond, then threw Han Li forward without any hesitation.

At this moment, Han Li's entire body was feeling sore and feeble, and he was powerless to resist as he plunged into the blood pond with a loud splash.

As soon as he entered the blood pond, Han Li's skin instantly turned bright red, and his facial features also became slightly contorted.

The liquid in the pond was incredibly hot, to the point that it was scorching every single inch of his skin, making him feel as if he had been set alight.

At the same time, bursts of heat were surging into his body before flowing toward his injuries, which immediately began to heal.

"You only have one hour," one of the armorclad figures declared in a raspy voice.

Han Li hurriedly began to focus on his recovery upon hearing this, inviting more and more of the heat in the pond into his own body.

Fifteen minutes passed by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's regenerative abilities were significantly enhanced by the blood pond, and at this point, he was already close to halfway to making a full recovery.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out, and two more armorclad figures emerged, carrying another gladiator.

It was a youngman with some corkscrew patterns on the left side of his face, extending from his forehead all the way down to his chin, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

The man's entire body was also riddled with wounds, the most severe of which were two giant gashes on his lower abdomen that almost split his body into three. Blood was gushing freely out of the two gashes, and even his internal organs were visible through them.

The two armorclad figures casually tossed the man into the blood pond, and the man had clearly been here before as he immediately began taking advantage of the pond's healing properties to enhance his own recovery.

The two gashes on his waist quickly began to mend, and once again, Han Li was astonished by just how potent the pond's healing properties were.

The man seemed to have detected Han Li's gaze, and as he turned to look back at Han Li, a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

"You're Li Feiyu, right? It's a pleasure to meet you."

"Have we met before?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"My name is Chen Lin, and I'm also from the ninth area. I was there during your run-in with Scarface, and I just witnessed your battle against the Tiger Scaled Beast. I must say, it's very impressive that you were able to kill that C tier Tiger Scaled Beast. Not many people in our ninth area would've been capable of such a feat," Chen Lin praised in an earnest manner.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Chen, I was merely very fortunate to have emerged victorious," Han Li replied in a modest manner.

Recently, Han Li had spent the vast majority of his time cultivating in his room, and during the few occasions where he had emerged from his room, all of the other gladiators of the ninth area seemed to have been actively avoiding him, so this was the first time that someone from the ninth area that someone had struck up a conversation with him.

Han Li had been meaning to ask someone about what had happened following his altercation with Scarface, and Chen Lin was happy to answer his questions, telling him about how Scarface had complained to Toxic Dragon, and it was only then that Han Li finally realized why everyone from the ninth area had been actively avoiding him.

"You're a very strong man, Fellow Daoist Li, but you should be on your guard when it comes to Scarface. He's an extremely petty man, and he's also on good terms with Toxic Dragon. In order to protect his authority in the ninth area, Toxic Dragon isn't just going to let this matter slide, so make sure to be careful," Chen Lin cautioned.

"Thank you for telling me all of this, Fellow Daoist Chen. How do you think I would fare against Toxic Dragon?" Han Li asked.

"To my knowledge, Toxic Dragon has already opened seventy profound acupoints, which would place him above average among the ten area leaders. To be frank, I don't think you stand any chance against Toxic Dragon as you are now, so my advice would be to submit to his authority and try to appease him," Chen Lin replied after a brief hesitation.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he nodded in response.

"Having said that, you don't have to worry about anything in the near future. Toxic Dragon suffered some pretty severe injuries in a battle against a top-level C tier scaled beast recently, and it'll take him two to three months to make a full recovery, so he won't come after you anytime soon," Chen Lin added.

"Looks like my luck isn't too terrible," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"According to the rules of the arena, each gladiator must participate in at least one battle per month. You've just come out of a battle, so you can rest for a month and take that time to grow stronger," Chen Lin advised.

"Oh? I wasn't aware of such a rule," Han Li said as he raised an eyebrow.

"Only in cases where the arena has conducted an evaluation and determined that a gladiator is too severely injured to take part in another battle within a month will they be given some leeway, and that's exactly what's happened in the case of Toxic Dragon," Chen Lin said.

Han Li nodded in response, then asked some more questions about the arena, and Chen Lin was happy to provide him with answers.

An hour later, the two armorclad figures that had brought Han Li to the blood pond declared, "Time's up."

Han Li made his way out of the blood pond upon hearing this, then cupped his fist in a grateful salute as he said, "Thank you, Fellow Daoist Chen."

"You're welcome, Fellow Daoist Li. Everything I've told you is information that's readily available, so there's really no need for you to thank me," Chen Lin replied as he returned the salute.

With that, Han Li departed from the stone chamber.

After spending a full hour in the blood pond, he had already mostly recovered from his injuries, and he quickly returned to the exchange hall.

From there, he strode over to the stone table, then exchanged all twenty-one of his profound points for seven Tarot Beast Cores before making his way back to the ninth area.

According to what he had just been told by Chen Lin, he was only going to have two to three months to prepare before Toxic Dragon came out of seclusion, so he had no time to waste.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I heard you managed to slay a C tier Tiger Scaled Beast! How impressive!"

"You've only just joined our ninth area, yet you're already putting all of us to shame, Fellow Daoist Li."

As soon as Han Li returned to the ninth area, several people immediately approached him with warm greetings as if they were old friends.

"You're all far too kind," Han Li replied in a placating fashion.

While he despised these fence-sitting gladiators, he didn't want to make enemies out of them.

Right at this moment, Han Li sensed a cold and resentful gaze, and he turned to discover none other than Scarface.

As soon as their eyes met, a hint of fear and hatred immediately flashed through Scarface's eyes, and he made his way into his own room, seemingly afraid of further confrontation.

Han Li thought back to what Chen Lin had told him, and his brows furrowed slightly as he also entered his own room.

Chapter 866: Sinister Plot

Only after returning to his room in the ninth area did Han Li heave a faint sigh of relief.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he closed his eyes and began channeling the Wingform Ascension Arts to refine the Tiger Scaled Beast Core in his body.

There were many ways through which one could store the starpower in a beast core in their body for relatively long periods of time, but some of the starpower would inevitably fade away over time, and it was not an easy task to obtain fresh beast cores.

Even though he had ultimately managed to win this battle, the process had been far too close for comfort.

If he wanted to survive, then he would have to elevate his own powers as quickly as possible, and only by constantly growing stronger would he have a chance of leaving this place alive.

The Tiger Scaled Beast Core gradually melted into a ball of starpower in his body.

As a C tier scaled beast, the Tiger Scaled Beast's core contained a sizable amount of starpower, several times that of the Tarot Beast Cores that he had purchased. However, just like the Tarot Beast Cores, the starpower in the Tiger Scaled Beast Cores was also very chaotic, and it immediately began rampaging within his body.

However, even as the starpower began to seep out of his body, he remained completely unconcerned, and sure enough, it didn't take long before a burst of suction force emerged from the opening of the Heaven Controlling Vial to suck in the dissipating starpower again.

Having already consumed several Tarot Beast Cores, Han Li had discovered that the Heaven Controlling Vial's absorption and purification of starpower was rather similar to its absorption of moonlight, but the difference was that this process was taking place within his body, while its absorption of starlight took place outside his body.

It appeared that starpower and the energy in moonlight had to be similar in certain areas.

If it weren't for the Heaven Controlling Vial, Han Li estimated that he wouldn't even have been able to absorb 0.1% of the starpower in the Tarot Beast Cores, and he would perhaps have fared a little better with the Tiger Scaled Beast Core, but even then, he would've only been able to absorb 1% to 2% of its starpower at the very most.

In contrast, with the Heaven Controlling Vial, he was able to absorb close to all of the starpower in the beast cores, and the difference was night and day.

Perhaps this was why consuming scaled beast cores had a far more pronounced effect on him than for Shi Chuankong.

Han Li continued to channel his Wingform Ascension Arts, directing the starpower toward the third profound acupoint.

Several days later, another speck of bright starlight appeared on his calf, and this third acupoint also began to open with the tremendous influx of starpower.

Han Li's eyes remained shut as he continued to cultivate, and the rays of white starlight emanating from the white tree root up above were also shining down upon him.

Right at this moment, three tiny white insects descended from the white tree root.

The insects were as thin as strands of hair, and they had translucent white bodies, making them almost indiscernible from the white starlight around them.

The three insects remained completely still as they drifted toward Han Li, who was focused entirely on his cultivation at this moment, so he remained completely oblivious to the insects.

The three insects quickly descended onto his shoulder, and as soon as they came into contact with his skin, they immediately fused into his body.

Upon entering Han Li's body, the insects suddenly seemed to have come to life, and they began rapidly burrowing their way toward his heart.

Han Li detected the insects as soon as they came into contact with his body, and his eyes instantly sprang open as an alarmed look appeared on his face.

Right at this moment, the Black Tribulation Centipede clinging to his heart suddenly stirred ever so slightly, and a faint black gleam appeared in its eyes, as if it had woken up.

At the moment, the Black Tribulation Centipede posed a direct threat to his life, so he had to keep it in check at all cost.

With that in mind, all of the muscles, tendons, and bones in his body began to vibrate at his behest, sending bursts of vibrational force coursing through his entire body.

As a result, the three white insects were slowed down significantly, but they were still squirming toward his heart.

A grim look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon sensing this, and he immediately tapped his right middle and index fingers against his own chest three times in rapid succession, sending three bursts of force penetrating into his own body to strike the three white insects.

The three insects instantly stiffened momentarily, but they were able to remain largely unharmed, and they continued in their advance after a brief moment of immobilization.

At this point, they were already quite close to Han Li's heart, and the Black Tribulation Centipede was becoming more and more active by the second.

An urgent look appeared on Han Li's face as a burst of bright translucent light flashed over his glabella, and three tiny translucent swords shot forth before piercing into his chest.

The translucent swords were substantial objects that pierced three holes into Han Li's skin, but he paid no heed to the injuries as he guided the three swords with his spiritual sense, sending them burrowing into his own body to strike the three white insects.

The three insects possessed remarkably resilient bodies, but they stood no chance against the tiny swords manifested by Han Li's Sword Observation Arts, and they were sliced into pieces before falling completely still.

As soon as the three white insects were killed, the Black Tribulation Centipede instantly settled down again, much to Han Li's relief.

Right at this moment, his brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he threw up a small mouthful of blood.

In the process of killing the three white insects, the Spiritual Sense Swords had inflicted quite a bit of damage onto his body.

However, instead of tending to his internal injuries, three translucent chains shot out of Han Li's glabella, then burrowed their way into his wounds to drag out the dismembered bodies of the three white insects.

In the process, the wounds on his chest were opened up even further, and they were bleeding profusely.

Han Li channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts momentarily, and specks of white starlight immediately converged toward the wounds on his chest, sealing them in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, Han Li was staring intently at the bodies of the white insects with a cold look in his eyes.

If he hadn't reacted in time and used his Sword Observation Arts to slay the three insects, they would've most likely already burrowed their way to his heart by now, and judging from how restless the Black Tribulation Centipede had become, the outcome certainly wouldn't have been pretty.

It was clear that these white insects weren't naturally found in the arena, so Han Li immediately began to suspect that someone was plotting against him, and the prime suspect was none other than Scarface.

After taking a deep breath to compose himself, Han Li cleaned the blood from his body, then emerged from his room.

At this moment, there were quite a few gladiators gathered in the cave, and Scarface was among them.

Everyone extended warm greetings to Han Li upon catching sight of him, while a slightly unnatural look flashed through Scarface's eyes as he turned his head to the side in silence.

Han Li returned everyone's greetings, then took a subtle glance at Scarface before making his way toward Chen Lin's room.

He knocked on the stone door of Chen Lin's room a few times, and shortly thereafter, the door swung open to reveal Chen Lin.

"Fellow Daoist Li? What brings you here today?" Chen Lin asked as a slightly surprised smile appeared on his face.

"Can I come in, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked with a solemn expression.

"Of course," Chen Lin replied as he stepped to the side and made an inviting hand gesture.

After Han Li entered the room, the stone door swung shut again.

Chen Lin invited Han Li to take a seat at the stone table, then asked, "Did something happen, Fellow Daoist Li? You don't appear to be in a very good mood."

Han Li immediately gave Chen Lin a recount of what had just happened to him in his room.

After hearing Han Li's recount, Chen Lin sprang to his feet as he exclaimed in a stunned voice, "You managed to survive that? That's incredible!"

"Why do you say that, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked.

"If I'm mistaken, the white insects that you just described are Heart Pitting Insects, creatures that can only be found in the Heart Devouring Valley. These things are sworn enemies of Black Tribulation Centipedes, and if they run into each other, a fight to the death is sure to ensue. If you had allowed them to reach your heart, then your fate would've been sealed," Chen Lin replied with tightly furrowed brows.

"It sounds like I was very fortunate to have survived then," Han Li mused with a wry smile.

"Was it Scarface?" Chen Lin asked.

"Who else could it have been?" Han Li sighed.

"Under normal circumstances, gladiators aren't permitted from leaving their respective areas, so he's the only one in our ninth area capable of getting his hands on Heart Pitting Insects," Chen Lin mused.

"Oh? Does he have some type of special privilege?" Han Li asked.

"I wouldn't quite go that far, it's just that he has a relative who's working as an administrator in the city lord's manor, and through that connection, he's able to bring in some things from outside the arena to trade with other gladiators. On top of that, as I mentioned last time, he's on very good terms with Toxic Dragon, so everyone generally stays out of his way, and that's why he's become more and more arrogant over time," Chen Lin explained.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

Prior to this, he hadn't seen Scarface as a threat, but it seemed that he would have to be on his guard.

Chapter 867: Second Arena Battle

"Thank you for telling me all of this, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said as he stood up to depart.

"Don't do anything rash, Fellow Daoist Li. Scarface on his own is nothing to be afraid of, but as the saying goes, before you beat a dog, you have to look at who its owner is. For Toxic Dragon, Scarface is a very obedient and useful dog, so if you kill him, you'll risk completely turning Toxic Dragon against yourself," Chen Lin hurriedly said.

"I've already turned Toxic Dragon against myself, haven't I? If he's going to come after me anyway, then what difference does it make if I take Scarface out of the picture or not?" Han Li countered.

"Even if you're not afraid of Toxic Dragon, you still have to follow the rules of the arena. Personal conflicts are permitted in our arena in private, and they're even encouraged to a certain extent, but battls of life and death can only take place in the arena. If you kill someone in private, you'll be in a lot of trouble, and that's why I'm telling you not to be rash," Chen Lin continued.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he sat back down again.

Chen Lin also sat down beside him as he said with a relieved smile, "I'm glad I managed to talk some sense into you."

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said with a smile.

"It's fine. Before you leave, I have something for you," Chen Lin said after a brief moment of hesitation.

Before Han Li had a chance to ask any questions, Chen Lin made his way into his inner chamber before bringing out a black stone box.

"Scarface isn't the type who knows when to give up, so take this for now. It may save you some trouble in the future," Chen Lin said as he offered the black stone box to Han Li in a slightly reluctant manner.

"What's this?" Han Li asked.

"It's a Heavenly Star Shell. You've seen this thing at the exchange center, right? There's no devilish qi in this godforsaken place, nor can devilish treasures be used, so it's very difficult to set up any restrictions. Hence, a Heavenly Star Shell is considered to be quite an advanced tool around these parts," Chen Lin explained with a smile.

Upon hearing mention of the term "Heavenly Star Shell", Han Li immediately recalled that he had indeed seen the name in the exchange hall. He didn't know what it was used for, but it was quite expensive, and that was why it had left an impression on him.

"I can't accept something so precious, Fellow Daoist Chen. I'm already extremely grateful for all of the information that you've imparted upon me," Han Li refused.

"You misunderstand my intentions, Fellow Daoist Li. I would like to give this to you for free, but I'm afraid my finances won't allow for that," Chen Lin said with a wry smile.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and Chen Lin explained, "This is an old Heavenly Star Shell of mine, and much of its starpower has already been exhausted. I got into some conflicts with some other gladiators some time ago, so I purchased a better one in order to ensure my own safety, and this one's just been sitting around ever since.

“I know you won't have many profound points at the moment, so I can sell this Heavenly Star Shell to you for half price."

Han Li was tempted by the offer, but he replied in a resigned manner, "Truth be told, I've already exchanged all of my profound points for beast cores, so I don't have anything that I can give you in exchange aside from Tarot Beast Cores."

"It's fine. It's not every day that I meet another gladiator who I can get along with, so you can take this Heavenly Star Shell for now. As for the compensation, I can wait until you've won a couple more arena battles," Chen Lin said with a smile.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then nodded in response.

"In that case, I'll have to thank you again, Fellow Daoist Chen."

He accepted the black stone box as he spoke, then opened it to reveal a palm-sized white shell with many complex patterns on its surface sitting inside.

"I've used this thing before, so it has my mark, but all you need to do is drip some of your blood essence onto it, and it'll recognize you as its new owner. All you need to do from there is place it in your room, and it'll release a layer of starpower that encompasses the entirety of your door. That way, no one will be able to enter your room unless they break in by force, and little things like Heart Pitting Insects will also be kept out," Chen Lin explained.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Chen, I'll remember what you've done for me," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute, then promptly departed.

After returning to his room, Han Li pulled out the Heavenly Star Shell, then dripped a drop of blood essence onto it.

The drop of blood essence created a red stain on the shell, which then vanished amid a flash of white light.

At the same time, all of the patterns on its surface lit up, releasing a layer of hazy white light.

Han Li set the shell down beside his door, and the white light immediately encompassed the entire door, including even all of the gaps around it.

After inspecting the Heavenly Star Shell momentarily with his spiritual sense, he discovered that the starpower within it was still quite abundant, so it was clear that Chen Lin had overstated how much he had used it in the past.

After some contemplation, Han Li sat back down onto his stone bed, then swallowed a Tarot Beast Core and began cultivating his Wingform Ascension Arts.

……

A month flew by in a flash.

Inside Han Li's room, the white tree root on the ceiling was still glowing faintly, and he was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed on his bed. At this point, he had already opened a total of forty-one profound acupoints.

In addition to the profound acupoint that he had opened after consuming the Tiger Scaled Beast Core, he had consumed seven Tarot Beast Cores in succession to open up two more profound acupoints, both of which were also on his legs.

Right at this moment, a faint buzzing sound suddenly rang out in his room, and a burst of black light began flashing incessantly by his bed.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes, and his brows furrowed slightly as he picked up the flashing badge by his bedside.

He slowly rose to his feet before making his way out of his room, and he discovered that there were more people than usual gathered in the ninth area, indicating that there were perhaps also some other arena battles taking place.

Han Li passed straight through the exchange hall to arrive in the waiting hall, and the horned man waiting there immediately called out to him.

As the only human gladiator, he had left quite a deep impression on the horned man.

"All of the platforms for the ninth area are currently occupied, so you'll have to wait until one of the ongoing battles ends before you can go in," the horned man said with a smile, speaking much more amicably than last time.

"It's fine, I'll just wait," Han Li replied with a nod, then sat down with his legs crossed near in the waiting hall.

Around fifteen minutes later, one of the battles finally concluded. Both of the gladiators participating in the battle had perished, and as a result, the city lord's manor had made a killing.

Han Li rose to his feet upon hearing the commotion from the spectators outside, and he was greeted by the sight of two sets of gladiator remains being carried in from outside. One of them had a huge hole in their head, while the other had had their chest completely torn open.

After waiting for a while longer for the platform to be repaired, the horned man entered the venue to announce the next battle.

"Everyone, I'm sure all of you still remember the human who miraculously defeated that Tiger Scaled Beast last month. Today, he returns to our arena, and he'll be going up against another C tier scaled beast, a Mountain Plowing Ape. He only possesses fewer than forty profound acupoints, will he be able to pull off another stunning upset?"

The horned man's announcement immediately sent the entire arena into a frenzy, and some of the spectators had already begun yelling Han Li's alias.

"Li Feiyu! Li Feiyu! Li Feiyu..."

Of course, there was also no shortage of spectators rooting against him, some of whom felt that he had only been lucky last time, while others simply despised him for the fact that he was a human.

Han Li could hear some of the cheers and jeers being directed at him from inside the waiting, but he remained completely unfazed and disinterested.

"The battle between Li Feiyu and the Mountain Plowing Ape is about to begin soon, so place your best now. Once the battle commences, no further bets will be taken. Once again, the odds for this battle are 5:1!" the horned man declared.

The atmosphere instantly became even more heated after the odds were declared, and most of the spectators still chose to bet on the Mountain Plowing Ape, but many were considering betting on Han Li this time.

Inside one of the VIP booths, Chen Yang was resting against a large black chair, but this time, he wasn't accompanied by the woman from last time, and Hu Bi wasn't with him, either.

"I don't know how you managed to win the last battle, but you really shouldn't have challenged another C tier scaled beast, particularly not a Mountain Plowing Ape. You may have pulled off a miracle last time, but lightning isn't going to strike twice," he murmured to himself with slightly narrowed eyes.

Moments later, the sound of a gong being struck rang out, indicating the imminent commencement of the battle.

The stone door was slowly opened, and Han Li emerged from the waiting hall, looking as calm as ever.

Chapter 868: Life or Death

In contrast with the near-unanimous chorus of boos Han Li had received during his first battle, the reception was clearly a little warmer this time.

Ofcourse, Han Li didn't really care about this, and he continued to stare at the stone door across from him on the other side of the arena.

As the stone door slowly swung open, he immediately heard a violent roar ringing out from within the dark tunnel.

Immediately thereafter, a huge ape that was over thirty feet tall emerged. Its body was completely covered in green scales, and its arms were almost thicker than its own torso.

Its entire body was riddled with scars left behind by fists, blades, and claws, clearly indicating that it had endured many past battles, so it was most likely going to be even more formidable than Han Li had anticipated.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a solemn look appeared on his face.

While he was observing the Mountain Plowing Ape, it was slowly moving along the edge of the platform, seemingly observing him as well.

With neither of the two combatants making a move, the spectators immediately began hurling torrents of abuse to express their dissatisfaction.

Right at this moment, the Mountain Plowing Ape suddenly stopped in its tracks, then raised its massive arms up high before slamming them down onto the ground.

The entire platform shuddered violently as a burst of tremendous force surged through the ground, shattering one black stone slab after another.

Even though Han Li was already doing his best to remain steady, he still couldn't help but sway with the trembling ground.

After the dust settled, the Mountain Plowing Ape was already nowhere to be seen, and Han Li immediately looked up just as a huge shadow loomed overhead.

As it turned out, the Mountain Plowing Ape had appeared directly above him and was plummeting down from overhead.

Han Li immediately felt the air constrict around him, and the pressure exerted by the Mountain Plowing Ape struck him with a sense of asphyxiation.

Right at this moment, the two Wingform Ascension Arts profound acupoints on his leg lit up, and he glided over the ground, reappearing over a hundred feet away in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, the Mountain Plowing Ape crashed down onto the ground where he had been standing just a moment ago, smashing a huge crater into the platform.

Before Han Li had a chance to gather himself, the Mountain Plowing Ape sprang out of the crater at an incredible speed, swinging one of its enormous fists at Han Li's head with tremendous power.

Han Li took a step back, and all of the profound acupoints on his body lit up in unison as he retaliated with a punch of his own.

A loud thump rang out as the two fists clashed, and Han Li felt his entire skeleton shudder within his own body from the force of the collision, and a string of cracks and pops rang out incessantly from all of his joints.

The Mountain Plowing Ape seemed to be rather taken aback by the fact that Han Li had chosen to take such a direct approach, and it let loose a thunderous roar as it forced its fist down with even greater force.

As a result, Han Li was completely overwhelmed, and he was sent tumbling back through the air, rolling end over end over ten times before crashing into the wall on the edge of the platform.

His entire body was in excruciating pain from the devastating blow, and he was sorely regretting his decision to test out his own physical prowess against the Mountain Plowing Ape.

After sending Han Li flying, the Mountain Plowing Ape immediately charged forward in pursuit before swinging another punch at him, and Han Li hurriedly crouched down to just barely evade the attack.

He then stomped down onto the ground with both feet to launch himself up into the air, and a layer of white light emerged over his fist as he threw a punch into the Mountain Plowing Ape's left kneecap with all his might.

A dull thump rang out as the Mountain Plowing Ape's knee was knocked to the side, causing it to teeter unsteadily.

Han Li immediately pounced on this opportunity, throwing another punch straight into the Mountain Plowing Ape's forehead.

The Mountain Plowing Ape was thrown off balance by the consecutive blows, and it fell onto its back with a loud thud.

Han Li charged forward upon seeing this, then sprang up into the air before channeling both his Wingform Ascension Arts and his Great Universe Origin Arts as he stomped down upon the Mountain Plowing Ape's head.

The Mountain Plowing Ape didn't have time to raise its arms to defend itself, so it could only open its cavernous mouth to let loose a high-pitched shriek.

A burst of hazy white light appeared within its oral cavity, and within the white light was a sharp beast tooth that was aimed at Han Li's chest.

An alarmed look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and the profound acupoints on his legs abruptly brightened as he stomped down onto the air below, changing directions while in mid-air.

Even though Han Li was able to evade the beast tooth, he was still grazed by the white light around the tooth, which instantly tore through his True Extreme Film before inflicting a long gash in front of chest that was deep enough to expose bone.

Han Li gave an involuntary groan of pain, but he gritted his teeth and fought through the pain as he swung a fist down onto the Mountain Plowing Ape's glabella, slamming its head deep into the ground.

Even though he appeared to be in a dominant position, Han Li didn't let down his guard, and he continued to rain down one punch after another onto the Mountain Plowing Ape's head.

At this point, all of the spectators had erupted into thunderous cheers, and almost everyone was cheering Han Li on with frenetic vigor.

Inside the VIP booth, Chen Yang was watching the unfolding battle with a contemplative look on his face, and a hint of wariness flashed through his eyes.

Some time later, Han Li had already lost count of how many punches he had thrown. At this point, the Mountain Plowing Ape's head was completely embedded into the ground, while the skin and flesh on the back of his fists had peeled away to reveal the bones underneath.

After ceasing his relentless barrage, he looked down at the motionless Mountain Plowing Ape, then reached down with the middle and index fingers of his right hand before plunging them into the Mountain Plowing Ape's temple in a sharp and swift motion.

A dull thump rang out, but his fingers were unable to pierce through the ape's skull.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression changed drastically as he sprang back in retreat.

Almost at the exact same moment, the Mountain Plowing Ape's giant arms swung at him from both sides without any warning. Thankfully, he had taken timely evasive measures. Otherwise, the consequences would've been dire.

The Mountain Plowing Ape pressed its elbows against the ground, then let loose a low roar as it forcibly pulled its own head out of the deep crater on the platform.

The spectators erupted into another chorus of raucous cheers upon seeing this, but as soon as they caught sight of the Mountain Plowing Ape's face, the cheers instantly turned into mocking laughter.

The Mountain Plowing Ape's nose had been completely bashed in by Han Li, creating a large hole. At the same time, one of its eye sockets had also been broken, and the fluids from its destroyed eyeball were mixing with its blood to create a gruesome sight.

In contrast with the spectators, Han Li didn't find the Mountain Plowing Ape's appearance comical at all.

Instead, he couldn't help but feel a little sorry for the Mountain Plowing Ape as he looked at the multitude of injuries on its body.

In this arena, he was no different from this Mountain Plowing Ape. Both of them were just instruments for the entertainment of others.

Even if he were to emerge victorious in this battle, who was to say that his luck wouldn't run out someday?

However, no matter how sorry he felt for the Mountain Plowing Ape, this was a matter of life and death, so he certainly wasn't going to hold back.

The Mountain Plowing Ape seemed to have been completely enraged by the injuries that it had sustained, and its only remaining eye had turned bright red.

It let loose a thunderous roar as it charged straight at Han Li, then sprang up into the air before swinging its fists down at him with all its might.

Through the gaps between the scales on the Mountain Plowing Ape's arms, Han Li could see specks of white light, indicating that it was injecting all of its power into its arms to try and kill Han Li in a single blow.

In response, Han Li channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts, and in the blink of an eye, he had moved to over a hundred feet away.

However, before he even had a chance to steady himself, the Mountain Plowing Ape's fists had already slammed into the ground, and the entire platform trembled violently as a string of loud explosions rang out in rapid succession.

Countless loose rocks were flung up into the air alongside an enormous cloud of dust, and Han Li had only just landed on the ground when he was sent flying back through the air along with a large stone slab.

By the time he landed on the ground again, the force from the Mountain Plowing Ape's fists were still surging through the platform, and as a result, he was thrown up into the air again, with the cycle repeating itself over and over again.

At this point, the entire platform had already been reduced to a jagged mess.

Chapter 869: Burgeoning Reputation

Han Li only just barely steadied himself when the Mountain Plowing Ape let loose another thunderous roar, and it rushed directly at Han Li, sending countless loose rocks flying in all directions.

Its punch was too fast for Han Li to evade, so he could only cross his arms in front of his own chest to form a protective barrier.

A loud thump rang out, and Han Li felt a numb sensation shoot through both of his arms, following which he was sent flying like a ragdoll before crashing into the wall.

The Mountain Plowing Ape's punch packed such immense power that he bounced straight off the wall, and his internal organs were churning within his body.

Blood began to gush to the base of his throat, yet before he even had a chance to throw it up, he was struck by another devastating blow that sent him crashing into the wall again.

He gritted his teeth against the excruciating pain in his body, and in the instant that he struck the wall, he twisted around before pushing off against the wall with his legs, trying to leap to safety.

However, he had only just risen up into the air when a giant hand from the Mountain Plowing Ape came swinging down upon him, and he could only raise his arms to the heavens to defend himself.

Another loud thump rang out, and this time, Han Li was smashed into the ground, completely inundated by loose rocks.

The Mountain Plowing Ape immediately pressed its advantage, descending upon Han Li before throwing several more punches into the ground.

All of a sudden, the roles from earlier had been reversed, and it was Han Li's turn to defend himself against the Mountain Plowing Ape's enraged assault.

At this point, a cloud of dust had risen up over the entire venue, making it impossible for the spectators to see what was happening.

"Looks like I overestimated him," Chen Yang murmured to himself as he rose to his feet in the VIP booth. "What is the city lord thinking? Does he really want him to die?"

Amid the dust and wreckage, Han Li's entire body was drenched in blood, yet his arms were still raised in front of himself, protecting his heart and other internal organs.

His vision was already blurry with blood, and his teeth were chattering in his jaw. He attempted to draw upon the bloodline power in his body over and over again, but for some reason, it refused to respond.

It was as if the bloodline power in his body had somehow been suppressed and fallen into a dormant state.

If things were to continue like this, then he wasn't going to be able to last much longer.

Right at this moment, his eyes abruptly widened, and a streak of translucent light abruptly shot out of his glabella before vanishing into thin air.

In the next instant, a tiny translucent sword appeared several dozen feet in front of him, and it passed straight through the Mountain Plowing Ape's fist before piercing into its broken eyeball.

All of a sudden, the Mountain Plowing Ape's fist drew to an abrupt halt no more than three feet away from Han Li's head.

The spectators in the stands could only hear the repeated booming impacts of the Mountain Plowing Ape's fists, but they were unable to see anything through the dense smoke. All of a sudden, they felt a burst of formidable spiritual sense flash through the air, following which a strong gust of wind swept forth in all directions, blowing all of the dust away.

With vision finally restored, everyone discovered that the Mountain Plowing Ape had already fallen to the ground, while Han Li's body was mangled beyond recognition, but he was still trudging arduously onto the Mountain Plowing Ape's head.

The Mountain Plowing Ape's chest was still rising and falling, indicating that it wasn't dead yet, and that was indeed the case.

Just now, Han Li had only used his Spiritual Sense Sword to destroy its soul, reducing it to an empty husk, but technically, its body was still alive.

After climbing onto the Mountain Plowing Ape's head, Han Li plunged his arm into its broken eye socket, then dug around momentarily before withdrawing his arm with tightly gritted teeth.

As he spread his hand open, a fist-sized beast core was revealed in his grasp, and the heaving of the Mountain Plowing Ape's finally subsided.

None of the spectators knew what to make of what they had just witnessed, and they had no idea how Han Li had managed to emerge victorious.

"What? He won?" Chen Yang exclaimed with a stunned expression, and he was also completely in the dark.

All of a sudden, a spectator who had made a risky bet on Han Li let loose an elated cheer, and this was followed by a raucous wave of cheers.

Han Li's hand was trembling uncontrollably as he stuffed the beast core into his own mouth.

At this moment, blood was flowing out of all of his orifices, and before he knew it, he had fallen unconscious.

……

By the time he woke up again, he was greeted by a strong bloody aroma, and he discovered that he was leaning against the edge of the blood pond with a layer of bright red mist permeating through the air around him.

He attempted to lift an arm, and sharp pangs of excruciating pain instantly speared through his entire body.

He gritted his teeth through the pain as he wiped a hand over his own face, then plunged his entire face into the blood pond for a more thorough clean.

Right at his moment, a familiar voice rang out from behind him.

"I've already allowed you to stay in there for an extra fifteen minutes. If you want to stay even longer, then you'll have to spend some of your profound points."

Han Li turned to discover the horned man standing behind him, and he remarked in a cold voice, "If it wasn't for your advice, I wouldn't even be in here right now."

"Don't try to blame me, take a look at that guy over there," the horned man chuckled coldly.

Han Li stood up from the pond with great difficulty upon hearing this, and he turned to the direction that the horned man was pointing in to discover a dark red object resting against the wall. Han Li was just barely able to identify the object as a set of mangled remains.

"Because you chose the Mountain Plowing Ape, he had to choose the even more formidable Black Scaled Elephant, and even though he had seven more profound acupoints than you, he still ended up like that," the horned man said in an expressionless manner.

"In that case, why didn't you set up a battle between the two of us?" Han Li asked.

"He's not your average gladiator. Instead, he's a free gladiator, and he voluntarily came here to participate in arena battles of his own accord. In order to earn more profound points, he chose to battle a scaled beast, so we naturally had to respect his wishes. Having said that, as soon as you enter the arena, your life is in your own hands, and he paid the ultimate price for his decision," the horned man said.

Han Li didn't entirely believe what he had been told, and he strode silently out of the blood pond before making his way directly to the exchange hall.

Due to the fact that he had just defeated a bona fide C tier scaled beast, he had received ten additional profound points compared with his previous battle. This time, he also purchased seven Tarot Beast Cores, leaving nine profound points in reserve.

After returning to his room, Han Li took some time to treat his own injuries, then sat down with his legs crossed on his stone bed as he began to meditate.

The beast core of the Mountain Plowing Ape contained even more starpower than the Tiger Scaled Beast Core, and it had an even greater enhancement effect on his physical cultivation.

……

Close to a month flew by in a flash.

After absorbing the tremendous starpower in the Mountain Plowing Ape's beast core, Han Li had devoured all of the Tarot Beast Cores as well, and not only had he opened a forty-second profound acupoint, a forty-third one was also beginning to budge.

This rate of progress was utterly astonishing, but thankfully, the number of profound acupoints that he had opened wasn't particularly exceptional among the gladiators, and he hadn't participated in many battles, either, so he hadn't attracted much attention.

Even though some people were already aware that he had opened over forty profound acupoints, the increase wasn't significant, so he could still make up some excuses. After all, there were certain methods that allowed one to drastically enhance their powers in a short time at some long-term costs.

However, he knew that this wasn't a permanent solution, so he would have to find a way to conceal his profound acupoints.

After he fully recovered from his injuries, he applied to take part in another arena battle after a month had elapsed since his previous one.

This time, he was up against another gladiator who had opened thirty-eight profound acupoints, as opposed to a scaled beast.

His opponent had fewer profound acupoints than him, but they were more concentrated, mostly distributed over his right arm and hand, so his offensive prowess wasn't inferior to that of the Mountain Plowing Ape.

However, at the same time, he also had very clear weaknesses in the form of his lackluster speed and the relatively frailty of the rest of his body. Hence, Han Li was able to quickly break all three of his other limbs with the exception of his right arm, forcing him to surrender.

From that point onward, Han Li began to build a reputation in the ninth area. As a result, his odds suffered a significant dip, but his battles were always sure to attract enormous crowds.

Han Li had won this battle relatively easily, remaining relatively unscathed in the process, so he took part in another battle in just half a month, much to the horned man's surprise.

Over the following three months, Han Li participated in a total of five arena battles, two of which were very close victories, and he quickly made a name for himself as an incredibly tenacious and resourceful human gladiator.

As a result, many of the other ninth area gladiators had begun trying to befriend him.

One night, Han Li was cultivating the Wingform Ascension Arts when he suddenly heard someone knocking on his door, and he opened the door to discover Chen Lin standing outside.

Chapter 870: Gu Qianxun's Invitation

"Come in, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said as he made an inviting hand gesture, and Chen Lin duly obliged.

After the two of them had taken a seat, a slightly awkward look appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "I'll compensate you for the Heavenly Star Shell as soon as possible. It's just that I've spent all of my profound points on my cultivation recently, so..."

Chen Lin raised a hand to interrupt him as he interjected with a faint smile, "It's fine, Fellow Daoist Li, I understand the situation that you're in, and I'm not here to demand payment from you. Instead, I wanted to discuss something else with you."

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li prompted.

"As I'm sure you're aware, Toxic Dragon will be coming out of seclusion soon, and he'll be sure to come after you once he does. Have you made any preparations?" Chen Lin asked with a serious expression.

"How else can I prepare? I'll just have to face him head-on," Han Li replied, and Chen Lin was rather taken aback by his calm demeanor.

"I understand that you're confident in your own abilities, but Toxic Dragon is not to be underestimated. I have a way to help you avert this crisis, would you be interested in hearing it?" Chen Lin asked in a mysterious manner.

"Of course," Han Li replied.

"Toxic Dragon is unmatched in our ninth area, but that doesn't make him invincible in the arena. There are several other area leaders who are more powerful than him, and I just so happen to be familiar with Mistress Gu Qianxun. If you want, I can ask her to mediate the conflict between you and Toxic Dragon," Chen Lin said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this.

He had heard of Gu Qianxun during his time in the arena, and he knew that she was the leader of the first area and the undisputed most powerful area leader. On top of that, the fact that she was a woman only further contributed to her legend.

"I've never even met Fellow Daoist Gu before, how can I expect her to help me?" Han Li asked.

"Mistress Gu Qianxun has seen a couple of your battles, and she's very interested in you. Truth be told, she was actually the one who asked me to come and see you after hearing about your conflict with Toxic Dragon," Chen Lin said.

"Even with Fellow Daoist Gu's powers, surely this is not something that she'd get involved in lightly. What would I need to do in exchange for her help?" Han Li asked.

"To tell you the truth, Mistress Gu Qianxun is very interested in you, and she would like to invite you to join her Myriad Bone Alliance," Chen Lin revealed.

Even though the arena was split up into ten areas, there were also some individual powers formed by gladiators from different areas, the most prominent of which was Gu Qianxuan's Myriad Bone Alliance, which had members from all areas.

This was not something that Green Goat City was opposed to. In fact, it was subtly encouraged.

The more circles and factions there were among gladiators, the more conflicts would arise, and that gave rise to rivalries that were lapped up by the spectators.

Han Li considered the offer momentarily, then shook his head as he replied, "I appreciate the kind offer, but I've grown quite accustomed to a free and autonomous lifestyle, so I'm afraid that I'll have to refuse."

He didn't know much about Gu Qianxun and the Myriad Bone Alliance, but he did know that Gu Qianxun was an extremely tough and unyielding woman, so in exchange for her protection, his freedom was most likely going to be severely restricted.

He was already very displeased at being forced to become an arena gladiator, so he certainly didn't want to have to deal with further restrictions. On top of that, he still wasn't very familiar with the arena yet, so it would be unwise to join the Myriad Bone Alliance blindly.

As for his conflict with Toxic Dragon, if worse came to worst, he would just have to resort to his Spirit Refinement Technique.

"Please consider this matter carefully, Fellow Daoist Li, Toxic Dragon is not to be underestimated," Chen Lin urged in a solemn manner.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Chen, but I've already made up my mind. Please pass on my gratitude and apologies to Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li replied.

"In that case, I won't try to dissuade you any further," Chen Lin sighed, then stood up to depart.

Following Chen Lin's departure, Han Li sat back down onto his bed, then closed his eyes to continue his cultivation, and soon, all forty-three of his profound acupoints lit up in unison.

As he opened more and more profound acupoints, the amount of starpower required to open more acupoints also increased.

Hence, he was only able to open a single profound acupoint of late, which was much slower progress than before.

With that in mind, he devoured another Tarot Beast Core before closing his eyes once again.

……

After leaving Han Li's room, Chen Lin made his way out of the ninth area and soon arrived in the exchange hall.

There were two gorgeous women standing outside the exchange hall, observing the plaza down below.

Both of them had very tall and proportionate figures, and one of them was wearing a purple dress, while the other was dressed in yellow.

The woman in purple turned around as if she had detected Chen Lin's approach, and it was revealed that she was a woman who appeared to be in her early twenties with a cold and proud look on her face.

Chen Lin gave the woman in purple a nod, then strode over to the woman in yellow as he said, "I'm sorry, Alliance Leader, I wasn't able to complete the mission you assigned to me."

"What? He turned you down? Is he not aware of how powerful Toxic Dragon is? What an arrogant and ungrateful bastard!" the woman in purple snapped in a cold voice before the woman in yellow even had a chance to reply.

Gu Qianxun slowly turned around, and it was revealed that she was rather ordinary in appearance, slightly lacking in beauty even compared with the woman in purple beside her.

However, there was a sense of unflappable composure about her, and she had a pair of bright and vibrant eyes, as well as exceptional glowing skin that made up for the inadequacies in her appearance.

If anyone were to gaze upon the two women, their eyes would inevitably be drawn to Gu Qianxun first.

"It's fine, I already anticipated that this would be his answer. I suppose we're going to have a good show to watch soon," Gu Qianxun said with her faint smile, and her voice was very alluring, warm and gentle, but tinged with a hint of authority.

Chen Lin was very relieved by Gu Qianxun's amicable reaction to the bad news.

"A good show? You think far too too highly of him! There are countless gladiators in our Myriad Bone Alliance who have just as many profound acupoints as him, what makes him so special?" the woman in purple scoffed in a disdainful manner.

"While it's true that he hasn't opened that many profound acupoints, he's an extremely seasoned fighter, and even against enemies more powerful than himself, he's always able to remain calm and find ways to make comebacks, and that's a very rare trait," Gu Qianxun replied.

"So what? There's such a massive gap between him and Toxic Dragon that none of his composure and resourcefulness will even matter in the end," the woman in purple countered.

"I suppose you're right," Gu Qianxun said with a faint smile, and a vindicated smile appeared on the face of the woman in purple upon hearing this.

"It sounds like Li Feiyu's truly in a pickle then," Chen Lin remarked in a grim voice.

"That'll depend on how sharp his eyes are," Gu Qianxun replied before departing, followed by the woman in purple.

"What's that supposed to mean?" Chen Lin murmured to himself with a perplexed expression.

......

A day and a night passed by in a flash.

On this day, the door of Toxic Dragon's room swung open, and an enormous figure emerged from within.

Scarface was already waiting outside, and he immediately approached Toxic Dragon.

Almost all of the gladiators in the ninth area were gathered here to welcome Toxic Dragon out of seclusion, and Chen Lin was also among them.

Even though he was only standing still on the spot, there was a mountainous aura emanating from Toxic Dragon's enormous body, an aura that was even more formidable than before.

Scarface's eyes immediately lit up upon sensing this, and Toxic Dragon declared with a pleased smile, "Even though the injuries I suffered were quite severe, it proved to be a good thing in the end as I managed to open a profound acupoint."

"Didn't you open your last profound acupoint only less than a century ago? This is incredible progress!" Scarface praised in a sycophantic fashion, then took a glance at Han Li's room as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

Chen Lin's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a hint of concern flashed through his eyes.

"Is he in there?" Toxic Dragon asked as a cold look flashed through his eyes.

"He is, and it's already been quite a few days since he's come out. I bet he must be shitting himself in there!" Scarface goaded, and many people burst into laughter upon hearing this, including even some of the people who had been friendly to Han Li of late.

A faint smile appeared on Toxic Dragon's face as well, and he strode over to the door of Han Li's room, yet right as he was about to push it open, the door opened from the other side to reveal Han Li.

Even after catching sight of Toxic Dragon and all of the other gladiators outside, Han Li remained completely composed and unfazed.

Chapter 871: Battle

"You've finally come out, Li Feiyu. Are you ready to face your death?" Scarface chortled as he pointed a finger directly at Han Li's nose.

Han Li paid no heed to Scarface, slowly making his way out of his room to arrive before Toxic Dragon.

Scarface was furious at being ignored, and he continued, "You're lucky to have survived to this point because Boss Toxic Dragon suffered some injuries in a prior battle. Now that he's fully healed, you better kneel down and kowtow to him right now! Perhaps if he's in a good mood, he'll let you off the hook after you hand over all of your profound points!"

A cold gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes as he took a glance at Scarface, then turned his gaze back to Toxic Dragon, and all of the laughter from the surrounding bystanders abruptly subsided at the sight of his calm display.

Scarface was even more infuriated upon seeing this, and he was just about to say something further when Toxic Dragon gave him a stern glare, and he immediately stepped down in a sheepish manner.

"It's been a very long time since someone's dared to stand up to me. You know what I like to do with tough guys like you? I like to snap all of the bones in your body one after another!" Toxic Dragon harrumphed coldly as he cracked his knuckles in a menacing fashion.

"If you're trying to intimidate me, then don't bother. Do you want to do this here, or go somewhere else?" Han Li asked in a calm manner.

"You're a brave little bastard, huh? Let's go to the arena," Toxic Dragon declared before turning to depart, and Han Li also set off to walk silently beside him.

All of the bystanders were quite surprised to see this, clearly not anticipating Han Li's reaction, and everyone eagerly followed along.

It didn't take long before Han Li and Toxic Dragon arrived in the exchange hall. Many gladiators from other areas seemed to have been somehow tipped off to their imminent battle, and at this moment, the exchange hall was almost completely filled with eager spectators.

The crowd was led by three figures who were giving off auras that weren't inferior to Toxic Dragon's, and they were observing Toxic Dragon and Han Li with intrigued expressions.

"What brings you three here today?" Toxic Dragon asked as he stopped in his tracks, and Han Li took this opportunity to take a glance at the trio.

At the center of the trio was a woman in yellow with skin that was as fair as jade, and she was giving off an innate aura of unflappable composure that immediately made her stand out from the crowd.

The woman was none other than Gu Qianxun, and just like last time, she was accompanied by the woman in purple.

To Gu Qianxun's left was a black-robed man with dark, glowing skin, and he was a lot shorter than Toxic Dragon, even a little shorter than Han Li, but his limbs were incredibly thick, and his arms were as thick as Han Li's legs, while his legs were as thick as his waist.

His short stature and enormous limbs gave him a very disproportionate appearance, but it was clear that he possessed immense explosive power.

To Gu Qianxun's right was a blue-skinned young man who was quite handsome, but his entire body was riddled with squiggly worm-like patterns that were giving off a glacial aura.

"That's Gu Qianxun from the first area!"

"And those two are the leaders of the fourth and sixth areas, Baleful God Tu Gang and Ice Emperor Fist Sun Binghe!"

The gladiators of the ninth area immediately erupted into spirited discussion at the sight of the trio.

Han Li took a glance at the two men, then turned his gaze back to Gu Qianxun.

Gu Qianxun looked back at him as well, and as soon as their eyes met, Han Li sensed a burst of peculiar power being transmitted through her gaze.

His Spirit Refinement Technique immediately began working on its own, and the peculiar sensation was instantly erased by his tremendous spiritual sense.

Gu Qianxun turned her gaze to Toxic Dragon as she complained, "You're an area leader, Toxic Dragon, is there really a need for you to go after a newbie?"

"Would you be saying the same thing if the newbie displayed extreme insolence and challenged your authority?" Toxic Dragon countered in a cold voice.

Gu Qianxun merely smiled and offered no response.

"Please pardon me, fellow daoists. I'll come back for a chat after I've snapped this bastard's head off his shoulders," Toxic Dragon said, clearly not regarding Han Li as a serious threat at all.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he began making his way toward the arena below.

Han Li remained as composed as ever, seemingly completely unfazed by Toxic Dragon's threat, and as he passed by Gu Qianxun, he gave her a slight nod of gratitude for her offer to help mediate his conflict with Toxic Dragon.

"Hold on a second," Gu Qianxun suddenly called out, and Han Li stopped in his tracks before turning to her with an inquisitive gaze.

Gu Qianxun took a glance at the woman in purple beside her, and a reluctant look appeared on the latter's face, but she still strode over to Han Li, before flipping a hand over to produce a white jade vial.

"Inside that vial is a Hyper Dragon Pill. It can drastically enhance your physical prowess to somewhat close the gap between you and Toxic Dragon. Of course, it also had some side effects, but you'll be fine after a month or two of rest," Gu Qianxun explained.

"How generous of you, Fellow Daoist Gu," Tu Gang remarked, while Sun Binghe remained silent, but a surprised look flashed through his eyes.

It was clear from their reactions that this Hyper Dragon Pill was quite a precious pill, and he couldn't help but wonder how this pill matched up against the Blood Tide Pill given to him by Shi Pokong.

"I don't know what you see in him, Big Sister!" the woman in purple harrumphed coldly, then turned back to Han Li as she snapped, "Hurry up and take the pill!"

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he turned to Gu Qianxun as he said, "Thank you for looking out for me, but I plan to face Toxic Dragon in a fair and square battle, and it would be unfair if I were to accept assistance from others."

After that, he turned to depart, paying no heed to the rude woman in purple.

An infuriated look appeared on the face of the woman in purple as she yelled after him, "You ungrateful cur! Without this Hyper Dragon Pill, you won't even be able to withstand a single attack from Toxic Dragon!"

Han Li continued to ignore the woman in purple, and before long, he had vanished into the passageway leading into the arena.

The woman in purple was even more infuriated upon seeing this, and she stomped her foot in frustration before turning back to Gu Qianxun.

"He seems like an interesting man, I wonder if he'll be able to live past today," Tu Gang mused with a smile as he took a glance at Gu Qianxun.

……

Han Li made his way down the passageway into the resting hall, and Toxic Dragon was already there, discussing something with the horned man.

The horned man raised his head at the sight of Han Li's arrival, then said, "Toxic Dragon has just told me about what's happening between the two of you. At the moment, all three platforms are in use, so you'll have to wait a little."

Han Li nodded in response, then strode over to a corner of the hall before sitting down with her eyes closed, stoically ignoring Toxic Dragon this entire time.

Toxic Dragon's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Han Li's calm demeanor, but he merely brushed it off as false composure and bravado.

Close to an hour passed by before one of the three battles finally concluded, and before long, it was Han Li and Toxic Dragon's turn to take the stage.

While announcing the battle, the horned man made no secret of the personal vendetta between Han Li and Toxic Dragon.

Both Toxic Dragon and Han Li were very renowned figures of the arena. Toxic Dragon was the leader of the ninth area, while Han Li was one of the brightest new talents, and he was at the height of his popularity.

A personal grudge match between the two naturally drew a great deal of excitement from the crowd, and many of the spectators were chanting the names of the two combatants as the atmosphere erupted into a frenzy.

The odds were announced at 2:1, and Toxic Dragon turned to Han Li as he sneered, "It looks like you're quite popular. Bask in the cheers while you still can, you won't be able to see them soon."

Han Li remained silent as he stood with his head lowered, seemingly lost in his own thoughts.

He wasn't doing this to put on a facade of composure. Instead, it was because Toxic Dragon had been releasing tremendous waves of killing intent this entire time, and it felt as if there were mountains of bones and rivers of blood behind him.

Han Li had killed countless people in the past, but his killing intent couldn't even begin to compare with Toxic Dragon's, and it was clear that Toxic Dragon's rise to the top of the ninth area was one that was built upon countless bodies.

Han Li was having to focus with all his might in order to avoid being affected by Toxic Dragon's killing intent, and Toxic Dragon was rather taken aback by Han Li's composure.

At the entrance of the exchange hall, Gu Qianxun, Tu Gang, and Sun Binghe were watching the battle from above, while most of the other gladiators had gone away to place their bets.

"The fact that this Li Feiyu doesn't appear to be affected by Toxic Dragon's Asura Killing Domain indicates that he possesses tremendous mental fortitude," Tu Gang remarked.

Gu Qianxun and Sun Binghe offered no response to this, while the woman in purple gave a disdainful harrumph.

Chapter 872: Bet

"What do you think of this matchup, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Tu Gang asked with a smile as he turned to Gu Qianxun.

"On paper, Toxic Dragon naturally holds a significant advantage, but there are many potentially disruptive factors at play, so Li Feiyu is not without chances," Gu Qinaxun replied.

"It sounds like you think Li Feiyu will cause an upset," Tu Gang said as the smile on his face grew even more pronounced.

Gu Qianxun offered no response.

"You've always had a sharp eye, particularly when it comes to predicting the outcomes of battles, but on this occasion, I must disagree with your judgment. How about we make a bet?" Tu Gang proposed.

"What would you like to bet, Fellow Daoist Tu?" Gu Qianxun asked.

An incredulous look appeared on the face of the woman in purple upon hearing this, and everyone else was also quite intrigued.

"Some years ago, I obtained the shell of a B tier Black Scaled Turtle by chance. Is that something that's of interest to you, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Tu Gang asked.

"It looks like you've come prepared, Fellow Daoist Lu. A B tier Black Scaled Turtle shell is quite a rare treasure, and it also happens to be something that I'm currently looking for. What do you want me to wager in exchange?" Gu Qianxun asked.

"I heard that you have a piece of Phoenix Blood Jade. Have you used it yet?" Tu Gang asked.

"I was wondering why you suddenly decided to come and watch this battle, you're only here because you're interested in my Phoenix Blood Jade," Gu Qianxun chuckled. "You're in luck, I do still have it."

Tu Gang's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he asked, "Do we have ourselves a bet then?"

"Sure, why not?" Gu Qianxun replied with a calm nod.

"It's decided then!" Tu Gang declared with an elated expression.

"Is that really a good idea, Big Sister?" the woman in purple asked.

Gu Qianxun merely smiled in response.

For some reason, Tu Gang was struck by a sense of uneasiness at the sight of Gu Qianxun's smile, but the bet was already made, so it was too late for second thoughts. In any case, Toxic Dragon was a far more powerful and established gladiator than Li Feiyu, so the odds were heavily in his favor.

"Would you be interested in taking part in this bet as well, Fellow Daoist Sun?" Tu Gang asked.

"Not at all," Sun Binghe replied in a voice that was just as cold as the aura that he exuded.

Tu Gang was unbothered by Sun Binghe's cold response and turned his attention back to the arena, where Han Li was intently observing Toxic Dragon, completely oblivious to the bet that had just been made.

Toxic Dragon's arms were crossed in front of his chest, and he was looking at Han Li as if he were looking at a dead man.

As soon as the horned man announced the commencement of the battle, Han Li immediately sprang forward like lightning, darting over to Toxic Dragon's side in the blink of an eye before throwing a punch at his ribs.

Given that he was far weaker than Toxic Dragon, he had to seize the initiative if he wanted to have any chance at victory.

In response to Han Li's attack, Toxic Dragon merely spread his arms open, and all of the air around him instantly twisted and warped as a tremendous aura erupted out of his body.

The aura was interspersed with his immense killing intent to form a wave of pressure that converged toward Han Li from all directions.

Han Li's fist wasn't even able to make contact with Toxic Dragon before he was stopped cold in his tracks, and he felt as if he had been dealt a heavy blow to the head, causing him to involuntarily stumble back a few steps.

A cold sneer appeared on Toxic Dragon's face, and all of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as a giant crater appeared on the platform, while countless loose rocks were sent flying in all directions.

Toxic Dragon had vanished from the spot in the blink of an eye, and in the next instant, a long, black leg appeared in front of Han Li before sweeping horizontally toward him.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the space in the wake of the leg rippled and warped, and the kick was aimed directly at Han Li's head.

Even before the kick had arrived, Han Li's skin was already torn open by the ferocious wind that it was generating.

In this battle of life and death, Han Li didn't dare to hold back, revealing all forty-three of his profound acupoints from the get-go, and the seven profound acupoints on his legs were glowing particularly brightly as he stomped his feet down onto the ground.

A resounding boom rang out as a huge crater appeared beneath his feet as well, and he shot back rapidly in retreat to evade Toxic Dragon's sweeping kick.

A hint of surprise flashed through Toxic Dragon's eyes upon seeing this, but in the next instant, the ground rumbled violently once again as he shot forth after Han Li as a black shadow.

The two of them were roughly comparable in speed, and in a more open environment, Han Li would've been able to escape, but there was nowhere for him to run, given the confines of the battle platform.

Toxic Dragon let loose a low roar as he swelled drastically in height, and seventy-one profound acupoints appeared over his body, with most of them gathered in his torso and his right leg.

There were around thirty to forty profound acupoints on his right leg alone, and it unleashed seven or eight leg projections that stomped down upon Han Li at once.

An explosive boom rang out in the air, and the entire platform was trembling slightly in the face of Toxic Dragon's almighty stomp.

Han Li remained unfazed as he began weaving back and forth through the air like a willow leaf in a whirlwind, and somehow, he was able to evade all of the oncoming leg projections, much to Toxic Dragon's astonishment.

A surprised look also appeared on Gu Qianxun's face as she murmured to herself, "What kind of movement technique is this?"

"He's already opened forty-three profound acupoints? That's more than I heard. Could it be that he took something to overstimulate his own latent potential in exchange for short-term gains?" Tu Gang mused.

Even though Han Li was able to evade Toxic Dragon's attack using his Wingform Ascension Arts, he was still struck by the shockwaves from Toxic Dragon's fearsome attack, causing his complexion to pale slightly.

His eyes narrowed slightly, and instead of taking evasive measures, he thrust his right middle and index fingers directly toward Toxic Dragon's heart.

His fingers were glowing white like fair jade, and they were piercing through the air with tremendous penetrative force.

In response, Toxic Dragon raised a hand before swatting it down upon Han Li's arm.

Even though he hadn't opened any profound acupoints in his hand, this was still an extremely formidable attack, and if it were to land, Han Li's arm would most likely be completely pulverized.

However, right at this moment, Han Li suddenly changed the direction of his attack, piercing his fingers down toward Toxic Dragon's dantian.

Toxic Dragon had no time to react to this abrupt change, and all he could do was conjure up his True Extreme Film.

A loud tearing sound rang out, and Han Li's fingers were able to pierce straight through the True Extreme Film en route toward Toxic Dragon's dantian.

Toxic Dragon's expression finally changed slightly upon seeing this, and he stomped his right foot into the ground, causing the entire platform to shudder violently.

The force transmitted into the platform by his stomp launched Han Li upward involuntarily, and as a result, his fingers were unable to strike their target.

A hint of frustration flashed through Han Li's eyes. He had gone all-out in this opening series of exchanges, but all of his attacks had been counteracted by Toxic Dragon with ease.

He was already aware that there was a significant power disparity between them, but the situation was even worse than he anticipated.

After sending Han Li flying up into the air, Toxic Dragon lashed out at him with a sweeping kick that packed tremendous power, causing the air to rumble and explode.

Han Li was still in mid-air, rendering him unable to change directions or take evasive measures, so he could inject all of his power into his fists as he lashed out in retaliation.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of sharp pain speared through Han Li's arms, and he was sent flying like a ragdoll before slamming heavily down onto the ground, creating yet another huge crater.

Tu Gang was ecstatic to see this, and he chortled with glee, "Looks like I've got this one in the bag."

"It's still too early to say that," Gu Qianxun said in an indifferent manner.

"Fine, let's keep watching then. I want to see how he could possibly turn this around," Tu Gang said.

Inside the crater in the ground, Han Li was feeling very lightheaded. His mouth and nose were filled with blood, while his arms felt as if they had been torn to shreds.

He shook his head vigorously to shake off the lightheadedness, then sprang out of the crater, but as soon as he raised his head, he was greeted by the sight of another sweeping kick from Toxic Dragon, this one aimed at his chest.

However, with his feet planted firmly against the ground this time, he was able to dart back in retreat using his Wingform Ascension Arts, allowing him to just barely evade the kick.

A cold sneer appeared on Toxic Dragon's face as he swiveled around once again, and he thrust his right leg toward Han Li's chest like a spear.

All of the profound acupoints on his right leg were glowing brightly, and every single one of them was releasing immense power.

At this point, Han Li was backed into a corner, and a cold look flashed through his eyes as he prepared to resort to his Spiritual Sense Sword as a last roll of the dice.

However, right at this moment, a peculiar look suddenly flashed through his eyes, and he began darting away to the side while sweeping an arm through the air.

Chapter 873: Lurking Concern

A semi-transparent spiritual sense chain shot out of the palm of his arm, then wrapped itself around Toxic Dragon's leg before tugging it to the side.

The tip of the chain then pierced straight through his True Extreme Film before plunging into a certain spot on his leg.

Toxic Dragon's right leg instantly stiffened before it was diverted to the side by the spiritual sense chain, causing it to glance past Han Li's body.

A resounding boom rang out as he crashed into the ground with a loud boom, while Han Li darted back to over a hundred feet away with a bright gleam in his eyes.

Everyone was taken aback by this sudden and unexpected turn, and the entire venue instantly fell silent.

"What just happened?" Tu Gang exclaimed in an incredulous voice, while a stunned look had also appeared on Sun Binghe's face.

At this moment, Chen Lin was watching the battle while standing behind Gu Qianxun, and a hint of realization flashed through his eyes as he recalled what Gu Qianxun had said to him earlier.

As for Gu Qianxun herself, there was a faint smile on her face, and she seemed to have already anticipated this outcome.

On the platform, Toxic Dragon had taken quite a hard fall, but he remained unscathed as he slammed a palm against the ground to bounce back to his feet.

He then turned to Han Li with a furious expression, but there was also a rather peculiar look in his eyes.

In the next instant, a huge crater appeared beneath his feet amid a loud boom, and he vanished once again before reappearing beside Han Li and sweeping his right leg toward Han Li's waist like a giant cleaver.

Han Li dodged to the side while releasing another spiritual sense chain from the palm of his hand, and it wrapped itself around Toxic Dragon's leg like lightning, then pierced into the same spot on his leg, namely a certain profound acupoint.

As soon as the spiritual sense chain pierced into that profound acupoint, the starlight emanating from it instantly began to flash erratically, and the True Extreme Film near it also became a lot thinner than before.

Toxic Dragon's right leg stiffened once again, and for a second time, he tumbled to the ground.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as the spiritual sense chain vanished from the palm of his hand.

All the while, all of the spectators were looking on in astonishment.

Just a moment ago, Toxic Dragon had been dominating the battle, but things had taken a very sharp turn for the worse from his perspective.

Han Li's spiritual sense chain was almost completely transparent, and it was extremely fast, so no one was able to see anything aside from a blurry white shadow erupt out of Han Li's hand, and before they knew it, Toxic Dragon had taken another fall.

Outside the exchange hall.

"You knew all along, didn't you?" Tu Gang asked as he turned to Gu Qianxun with a grim expression.

"What do you think?" Gu Qianxun asked with a faint smile.

"You possess far sharper eyes than I do, Fellow Daoist Gu. I'll send someone to deliver the Black Scaled Turtle shell to you," Tu Gang harrumphed coldly, then turned to depart, followed shortly thereafter by Sun Binghe.

"Why did they leave? It looks like Li Feiyu has gained the upper hand, but Toxic Dragon hasn't suffered any significant injuries, so the outcome is still undecided," the woman in purple exclaimed.

"It's already over," Gu Qianxun declared in an indifferent voice.

A perplexed look appeared on the face of the woman in purple.

"This is why I always tell you to be more humble, Yao Li. You've grown a lot stronger of late, but you're still a little rough around the edges. You should learn from Li Feiyu and not be so immature from now on," Gu Qianxun said as she also departed.

A hint of fury and indignation flashed through Yao Li's eyes upon hearing this, but she still lowered her head submissively as she gave an affirmative response.

Chen Lin departed from the exchange hall with Gu Qianxun, leaving Yao Li to continue watching the battle with a cold look in her eyes.

Scarface was also watching the battle from within the crowd, and at this point, his face had turned deathly pale as he stared after Gu Qianxun's departing figure with a horrified look in his eyes.

On the battle platform, Toxic Dragon stood up once again with a furious look in his eyes, but this time, he didn't immediately attack.

"Should we end things here, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

The enraged look on Toxic Dragon's face eased slightly in response to Han Li's decision not to speak out loud, and he asked through voice transmission, "How did you find out?"

"I have my ways. That profound acupoint on your leg is very vulnerable. All I need to do is disrupt it slightly, and that's enough to completely immobilize you on a temporary basis. That alone won't be enough to win me the battle, but if we go at it for a bit longer, I'm sure many of the gladiators watching this battle will also be able to identify this weakness of yours," Han Li said with a faint smile, and a steely look appeared on Toxic Dragon's face upon hearing this.

The bodily refinement cultivation art that he was using was primarily focused on refining the right leg. It was an extremely formidable cultivation art, but he didn't have the complete version, and he had been in too much of a hurry to make progress in it, so he had accumulated some internal injuries in one of the profound acupoints on his legs.

He had tried many methods to rectify the issue, and he had made some progress, ensuring that the profound acupoint didn't appear abnormal in any way, but ultimately, he was unable to remedy the problem at its roots.

This was a weakness that he had always carefully protected, and thanks to his tremendous power, very few people were able to even make contact with his body during past arena battles, so he had managed to keep this a secret thus far, but Han Li was somehow able to see right through him.

On top of that, perhaps the average person wouldn't have been able to see anything, but Toxic Dragon was certain that Gu Qianxun, Tu Gang, and Sun Binghe had already identified this weakness of his from his prior exchanges with Han Li.

Just as Han Li said, if the battle were to continue, more and more people would be clued in to this weakness of his, and that could prove to be extremely problematic. Hence, he was left unsure of what to do.

Han Li had actually only been able to identify this weakness in Toxic Dragon's profound acupoint through an immense stroke of fortune. It just so happened to be the case that this vulnerable profound acupoint was one that could also be opened using the Wingform Ascension Arts.

Han Li had only recently opened this particular profound acupoint, so he was very sensitive to it, and it was this factor, coupled with his tremendous spiritual sense, that allowed him to pinpoint this weakness in Toxic Dragon.

However, this was not a sufficiently damning weakness to allow him to win the battle. If Toxic Dragon were to cast aside all inhibitions and continue to go after Han Li at all costs, he would still most likely emerge victorious.

With that in mind, Han Li said, "I know of a way to help you heal this profound acupoint."

Toxic Dragon's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked, "Is that true?"

He was so excited that he had forgotten to raise his question through voice transmission, and even his voice was trembling slightly as he spoke.

"I'm currently using a bodily refinement cultivation art that also focuses on the legs. Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to identify this weakness of yours," Han Li said.

The Wingform Ascension Arts laid out the correct way to open this particular profound acupoint, and with the assistance of his immense spiritual sense, he was at least 70% confident in his ability to remedy Toxic Dragon's injured profound acupoint.

"If you can resolve this problem for me, then I'm willing to set all of our prior differences aside, and I can also provide you with assistance in anything that you want," Toxic Dragon said as he hurriedly extended a salute toward Han Li.

Everyone was astonished to see this, and no one had any idea of what was happening.

"There's no need for such formalities, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon. Let's go somewhere more private to discuss this matter," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Toxic Dragon nodded in response, then turned to the horned man to declare that he was forfeiting the match.

The horned man was very taken aback to hear this, but he had no choice but to announce the outcome of the battle.

Toxic Dragon paid no heed to the disgruntled spectators as he and Han Li departed from the battle platform, and they quickly returned to the ninth area together.

They made their way to Toxic Dragon's room, and Toxic Dragon pressed a hand against the stone door, upon which a burst of white light flashed from the gaps around the door before it slowly swung open.

Upon entering the room, Han Li discovered that Toxic Dragon's room was far larger than his and Chen Lin's, and it was also much more furnished.

"Please take a seat, Fellow Daoist Li," Toxic Dragon said as he made an inviting hand gesture.

After both of them had sat down at a stone table, Toxic Dragon immediately cut straight to the chase.

"This is a problem that has plagued me for many years. Do you really have a way to resolve it, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"The internal injuries that you suffered in this profound acupoint aren't just a result of your overzealousness to make progress. If I'm not mistaken, it also has something to do with the cultivation art that you're using," Han Li said.

"I don't want to rebuke you, but I don't believe that to be the case," Toxic Dragon replied in a hesitant manner. "The cultivation art that I'm using isn't particularly advanced or profound, but it's a legitimate cultivation art, so there's definitely nothing wrong with it."

"It's fine. I don't need you to give me the cultivation art, I just need you to tell me about the method laid out in the cultivation art for opening this particular profound acupoint," Han Li said.

Toxic Dragon duly obliged, even telling Han Li about some of the cultivation art's hidden intricacies.

"It's just as I expected. Your Profound Origin Divine Movement Arts can allow one to make rapid progress and open profound acupoints very quickly, but it's rather lackluster when it comes to building a stable foundation. I'm sure you've already noticed this problem and intentionally slowed down your own rate of progress to limit the detrimental effects to a single profound acupoint. Otherwise, you would be in even more trouble right now," Han Li said.

Toxic Dragon's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he extended another respectful salute toward Han Li as he said, "You've struck the nail right on the head, Fellow Daoist Li. If you can help me remedy this problem, I'll be sure to repay you."

"Helping you is going to be quite costly for me as well..." Han Li said as he put on a hesitant display.

"Go ahead and state any condition that you have, Fellow Daoist Li. As long as it's within my means, I'll be sure to help you," Toxic Dragon promised.

Chapter 874: Scarface's Demise

"Truth be told, there aren't many people in the entirety of Green Goat City that can treat your injuries, and I'm the only one capable of doing so in our ninth area," Han Li said.

"I believe you. The fact that you were able to see through my condition and identify its cause is sufficient reason for me to believe that you're the only one who can save me. May I ask how you plan to treat my condition?" Toxic Dragon asked.

"Your problem is that you've used an incorrect acupoint opening method, so that's where I'll begin addressing the matter. I'm using a cultivation art by the name of the Wingform Ascension Arts, and it also opens profound acupoints on the legs, so I can teach you the correct acupoint opening method," Han Li replied.

"How is that going to help me? I've already opened the profound acupoint, so it's already too late, is it not?" Toxic Dragon asked with a perplexed expression.

"The acupoint opening method on its own naturally won't be enough, assistance is also required from someone with powerful spiritual sense, and I just so happen to fit the bill," Han Li explained with a smile.

A complex look appeared on Toxic Dragon's face upon hearing this, and he sighed, "It sounds like you really are the only one who can help me. I'm sure your conditions must be very difficult to fulfill, right?"

"Not at all," Han Li chuckled. "Aside from some beast cores for my cultivation, I'll only need your help in some minor favors."

"What would you like me to do for you, Fellow Daoist Li?" Toxic Dragon asked.

"I know that you have many connections in the arena, so I would like you to help me track down a few people," Han Li replied with a serious expression.

"Who would you like me to find?" Toxic Dragon asked.

"I actually came to Green Goat City with two other people, one of whom is called Shi Kong, while the other is called Daoist Xie. Seeing as I've been forced to become a gladiator, I presume they've suffered a similar fate. Have you heard of them?" Han Li asked.

Toxic Dragon was quite relieved to hear that Han Li's demands were very reasonable, and he replied, "I'm afraid I haven't heard of these two names before, but I can help you look for them. The gladiator turnover rate is quite high, so there are always many newbies, but if we narrow it down to gladiators who entered the arena at the same time as you, then that'll narrow things down a lot."

"Also, have you ever heard of an extremely beautiful woman who appeared in the city over the past century or so? She..."

Han Li wanted to give Toxic Dragon a physical description of Violet Spirit, but didn't know where to begin.

A peculiar look appeared on Toxic Dragon's face as he shook his head and replied, "In Green Goat City, women are the rarest and most prized commodity. Even women with slightly above average looks are extremely rare, let alone extremely beautiful women. If such a woman really has appeared in Green Goat City, then the entire city would be aware of her."

Han Li nodded in response. Chen Yang was a trusted subordinate of the city lord, yet even he only had a female servant who was quite ordinary in appearance, so it seemed that Toxic Dragon was telling the truth.

"Is that all you need me to do for you, Fellow Daoist Li?" Toxic Dragon asked with a hint of disbelief in his eyes.

"Your condition isn't something that can be remedied in a short time, so I'm going to be taking a lot of beast cores from you over time," Han Li replied.

"That's fine. If you can cure my condition, then I'll perhaps be able to participate in some higher level battles, and if I can do that, then the rewards that I'll be able to earn will go far beyond what I can now," Toxic Dragon said with a nonchalant wave of his hand.

"What are these higher level battles that you speak of, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon?" Han Li asked.

"I don't mean to belittle you, Fellow Daoist Li, but with the number of profound acupoints that you've opened thus far, you won't come into contact with such battles for a very long time, so there's no need for you to get ahead of yourself. You'll find out about them when the time comes," Toxic Dragon said.

Han Li didn't pry into the matter any further, and he changed the subject as he declared, "On top of that, I want you to hand Scarface over to me."

"What are you going to do with him, Fellow Daoist Li?" Toxic Dragon asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

Han Li remained silent as he dragged a hand across his own throat, simulating a killing gesture.

"Scarface can be very petty and snide, and I understand that there's some bad blood between the two of you, but surely that's not enough to warrant his death," Toxic Dragon said in a hesitant manner.

"I had no intention of going after him, but he went too far by trying to kill me with Heart Pitting Insects," Han Li said in a cold voice.

"Heart Pitting Insects?" Toxic Dragon asked with a surprised expression.

Han Li gave Toxic Dragon a recount of his close encounter with the Heart Pitting Insects, and after hearing his story, Toxic Dragon's brows furrowed tightly as he said, "Fellow Daoist Li, I'm not trying to protect Scarface, but this sounds very suspicious, and I think there may be some type of misunderstanding involved."

"Why do you say that?" Han Li asked.

"Scarface is indeed able to acquire certain things that others in the arena aren't able to, but that definitely doesn't include Heart Pitting Insects. Those insects are no less valuable than Black Tribulation Centipedes, and I'm certain there's no way that Scarface could've acquired them. On top of that, I told him not to do anything rash before I went into seclusion, and he's always been very obedient to me, so this would be a very uncharacteristic move from him," Toxic Dragon explained.

"In that case, this does seem to be rather suspicious," Han Li mused with slightly furrowed brows.

"This isn't a difficult matter to make sense of, we'll just have to go and confront Scarface together. If he really did do it, then I'll put an end to his life for you. However, if he's not the culprit, then I implore you to spare him. After all, he's been with me for many years, and it would be sad to see him go," Toxic Dragon said.

Han Li nodded in response.

"If he's not the culprit, or he was acting under someone else's instructions, then I can spare him."

"Alright, in that case, let's go right now," Toxic Dragon said as he rose to his feet.

As soon as the two of them made their way out of Toxic Dragon's room, they were immediately greeted by the sound of a loud commotion.

At this moment, there were many people gathered in front of a certain room, and Toxic Dragon raised an eyebrow as he said, "That's Scarface's room... Did something happen?"

The two of them exchanged a glance before hurriedly making their way over to the crowd, and everyone that was gathered in front of Scarface's room immediately parted at the sight of Toxic Dragon to allow him through.

Toxic Dragon rushed into the room with Han Li in tow, and as soon as they entered the room, they spotted Scarface laying on the stone bed in the corner of his room.

There was a large hole on his chest, and his eyeballs were bulging outward, while his expression was twisted in horror and agony. It was clear that he had already been dead for quite some time.

"What the hell happened here?" Toxic Dragon yelled in a furious voice.

A short green-skinned man stepped forward with a slightly fearful expression as he said, "A few days ago, Scarface agreed to procure some things for me, and he told me to come and look for him today, but when I arrived not long ago, his door was shut, and he didn't answer when I knocked. Hence, I decided to go in, and this is what I saw."

Han Li strode over to inspect the hole on Scarface's chest, and after carefully probing his fingers into the hole, he pulled out a piece of a black centipede's tail and a thin, white line.

"That's a Black Tribulation Centipede and a Heart Pitting Insect!" someone exclaimed, and everyone hurriedly backed away with horrified looks on their faces.

Han Li then turned to discover an opened bone box sitting beside Scarface's hand. He picked up the box before conducting a close inspection, and Toxic Dragon also took a closer look, then declared, "It looks like this box was crafted using the nasal bone of an Insect Devouring Beast.

“This beast is capable of sucking Heart Pitting Insects into its trunk, then melting the insect using its nasal mucus, so its nasal bone can restrict Heart Pitting Insects and is often used to craft containers for such insects."

"Is he insane? He must have a death wish to be keeping Heart Pitting Insects in his room!" someone exclaimed.

"What an idiot," another gladiator scoffed.

"Who's going to give me my Sword Thorn Beast bones now that he's dead? I gave him three Polo Beast Cores in exchange for that!" a muscular gray-skinned man suddenly whined.

Right at this moment, a group of armorclad guards from the arena arrived on the scene, and they forcibly evicted all of the gladiators from Scarface's room.

The leader of the guards inspected Scarface's body momentarily, then announced that this stone room was going to be shut down for now before ordering his subordinates to carry Scarface's body away.

Everyone turned to Toxic Dragon with peculiar looks on their faces upon seeing this, and Toxic Dragon exchanged a glance with Han Li before both returned to the former's room.

Only then did the gladiators of the ninth area realize that the two of them had become inexplicably close, considering they had been at each other's throats not long ago.

After re-entering his room, Toxic Dragon asked, "What do you think of all of this, Fellow Daoist Li?"

Chapter 875: Acupoint Closing Technique

"The timing of Scarface's death is far too suspicious, but this does confirm to me that he was the one who put those Heart Pitting Insects into my room. Having said that, it appears that he was only doing someone else's bidding," Han Li mused.

"Regardless of whose instructions he was carrying out, someone capable of acquiring Heart Pitting Insects is definitely not to be looked down on. It looks like you may have some major trouble on your hands, Fellow Daoist Li," Toxic Dragon mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"Are you afraid of getting swept up in my mess, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon? In that case, we can revoke our earlier agreement," Han Li said with a smile.

At the moment, Han Li could only think of two people who he had bad blood with in Green Goat City, namely Chen Yang and Scarface. However, if the former wanted him dead, then he would've already been dead and buried long ago, while the latter was now dead himself, so the case had run cold.

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Li," Toxic Dragon chuckled. "Of course I'm afraid of trouble, but this agreement is too important to me to invoke. In fact, as a show of my sincerity, I'll issue you some of the beast cores that I promised you now."

"In that case, I'll teach you the acupoint opening method that I mentioned before, and after that, I'll use my spiritual sense to remedy your faulty profound acupoint. I don't know how many treatments it's going to take, but as long as you follow through on your promises, I'll be sure to see things through to the end," Han Li said.

"Deal!" Toxic Dragon replied with a pleased nod.

Around an hour later, Han Li returned to his room, then pulled out the ten Tarot Beast Cores that he had received from Toxic Dragon out of his sleeve. After that, he devoured one of the beast cores before commencing his cultivation of the Wingform Ascension Arts.

……

Over six years flew by in a flash.

During this time, Han Li had taken part in many arena battles, and his powers had been steadily growing in the process.

Most of the profound points that he had earned had been redeemed for beast cores, and that was also supplemented by the beast cores given to him by Toxic Dragon, amounting to quite a significant number, all of which had been used up in his cultivation.

However, the more progress he made, the slower progress became.

The more profound acupoints that he opened, the more starpower required to open each additional profound acupoint, and there was a limit to the amount of starpower in a single Tarot Beast Core, so he had to consume many such beast cores to open just a single profound acupoint.

Even so, he had already opened forty-nine profound acupoints up to this point, and this was an absolutely unheard of rate of progress.

While his rapid progress was a good thing, it was also a cause for concern.

After all, if someone were to discover just how rapidly he had been progressing in his bodily refinement, then that would undoubtedly lead to a disaster for him.

In a very timely stroke of fortune, one day roughly two years ago, Han Li had just finished a battle and trudged back to his room in an exhausted manner to find that his Heavenly Star Shell had been destroyed.

However, nothing had been moved in his room, and nothing had gone missing. The only thing that had changed was that the leg bone of an unknown scaled beast had appeared in a corner of the room.

A passage of text had been engraved onto the beast bone, and it was truly like a blessing from the heavens.

The passage of text contained a secret technique that taught one how to use starpower to close profound acupoints.

The inscriptions appeared to be quite fresh, and the handwriting was also a little rough, indicating that whoever had made the inscriptions had done so in a hurry.

At the end of the passage of text were two words: "destroy immediately".

Han Li followed the instruction without any hesitation, crushing the bone into powder after memorizing the secret technique.

It was unclear who had left this beast bone in his room, but in Han Li's mind, he was certain that it had to have been Daoist Xie.

As for how Daoist Xie had found out that this was something that he needed and how Daoist Xie had managed to sneak the bone into his room, those were just questions that he would have to ask Daoist Xie the next time they met.

The secret technique was quite simple, and it didn't take long for Han Li to master it, following which he closed his six latest profound acupoints, and to this day, everyone was still under the false impression that he had only opened forty-three profound acupoints.

……

At this moment, a battle between a gladiator and a C tier scaled beast was taking place in the ninth area, and thunderous cheers were ringing out across the spectator stands.

"Shadow, Shadow, Shadow..."

All of the spectators were chanting a certain name, and on the battle platform was a massive Black Scaled Elephant that was riddled with wounds, currently in the process of charging at a spear-wielding young man.

The man was none other than Han Li, and the bone spear that he was wielding was rather peculiar in that the tip of the spear was almost equal in length with its shaft, and it was shimmering with faint starlight.

It appeared to be a spike from some type of scaled beast.

The Black Scaled Elephant appeared to be charging forward with tremendous power, but in reality, its footsteps were a little clumsy, and its long tusks were aimed directly at Han Li like a pair of spears.

Han Li also had some blood on his body, but he was looking quite casual and relaxed.

In the face of the oncoming Black Scaled Elephant, Han Li crouched down slightly, and the profound acupoints on his legs lit up as he sprang up into the air.

In the blink of an eye, he appeared directly in front of the Black Scaled Elephant, which seemed to have been caught completely off guard, and it whipped its trunk viciously at Han Li at such an incredible speed that the majority of the spectators in the stands were only able to see a blur flash through the air.

Not only was the Black Scaled Elephant's trunk incredibly fast, it also possessed tremendous strength, and its scales were even more resilient than its body. If Han Li were to receive a direct blow from the attack, then the consequences would be catastrophic.

However, right as the trunk was about to make contact with Han Li, the profound acupoints on his legs lit up once again, and he curled up into a ball, then stomped down onto the sweeping trunk to send himself flying horizontally through the air.

At the same time, he plunged his bone spear into the side of the Black Scaled Elephant's face, and the spear resembled a sharp scythe, slicing all the way along the elephant's face before tearing a huge gash into its abdomen.

A massive torrent of blood came gushing out of the wound, staining half of the entire platform red.

The Black Scaled Elephant stumbled forward a few more steps, then collapsed to the ground with a massive thump.

Han Li immediately pounced on this opportunity, leaping high up into the air while raising his spear above his head. The muscles on his arms bulged as all of his forty-three profound acupoints lit up in unison, and he hurled the spear through the air like a javelin.

A loud shrieking sound rang out, followed by a loud crunch, and the spear pierced straight through the Black Scaled Elephant's head before plunging deep into the battle platform, following which Han Li also landed on the elephant's back.

"Shadow, Shadow, Shadow..."

……

The outcome of the battle was already decided, and the atmosphere in the entire arena was completely ignited as everyone erupted into thunderous cheers.

There was a covert VIP booth on the mountain face above the spectator stands, and an imposing black-robed man was standing with his hands clasped behind his back, silently observing the unfolding scene.

The man was none other than Du Qingyang, and he was looking at Han Li from afar as he murmured to himself, "Looks like the cultivation art that you're using greatly enhances your speed. How interesting.

After that, he made his way out of the VIP booth and returned straight to his cave abode.

Around an hour later, Hu Bi hurriedly arrived outside a conference hall of the city lord's cave abode, and before he even had a chance to declare his own arrival, the heavy doors of the conference hall swung open inward on their own, following which an authoritative voice ordered from inside, "Come in."

Hu Bi didn't dare to hesitate, and he hurriedly entered the hall to discover that there were already four people seated at the long table inside.

On the left were a bald man and a thin elderly man, both of whom were also hunting party captains, just like himself, while on right were a square-faced young man and a man with his hair tied up with a hair tie, both of whom were captains of city guard squads.

As for the main seat directly facing the entrance of the hall, that was occupied by Du Qingyang.

"Hu Bi pays his respects to City Lord Du," Hu Bi said with a respectful bow.

At this moment, Du Qingyang was playing with a strange black stone statue with three heads and six arms, and he gave a nonchalant nod, indicating for Hu Bi to sit down.

"I've summoned all of you here today to tell you that you can begin setting up the Sinha Blood Array," Du Qingyang declared as he sat up a little straighter.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, and they all appeared elated as they hurriedly replied in a respectful manner, "Yes, City Lord Du."

"Now that we're getting close, I have some finer details to lay out, so make sure you listen up and don't make any mistakes," Du Qingyang said, and everyone nodded in response.

Chapter 876: Cultivation Art Exchange

The meeting went on for about fifteen minutes before the stone door was slowly opened, and as everyone departed, no communication took place between them, but all of them had excited smiles on their faces.

Following their departure, Chen Yang slowly emerged from the shadows near the entrance of the conference hall with a cold look in his eyes, and he turned and spat onto the ground.

Meanwhile, Han Li had just returned to the ninth area following his battle when he was greeted by the sight of Toxic Dragon standing by his door.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "I can't treat you in my current condition. You'll have to wait for me to rest and recuperate a little first."

"Don't try to fool me," Toxic Dragon scoffed. "With your current powers, killing a Black Scaled Elephant isn't a difficult task at all. I'm not sure even I'd be able to defeat you in a battle now. How many profound acupoints have you actually opened? Forty-five? Forty-seven?"

"Even if that's the case, you can't just stand in front of my door and force me to treat you. Besides, that profound acupoint of yours has already been remedied to the point that it doesn't really require any further treatment. I'm sure you can sense that yourself," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"That's not the reason why I'm waiting here for you," Toxic Dragon said.

"Oh? Then why are you here?" Han Li asked.

"Some of the elite gladiators from all of the arena's different areas will be gathering today to hold a small exchange event. Everything can be put up for exchange, including profound points, bodily refinement cultivation arts, or other items, and you can exchange cultivation insights with others as well if you'd like. Are you interested?" Toxic Dragon asked.

"Is an event like this not prohibited by the city lord's manor?" Han Li asked.

"Not at all. If anything, it's encouraged by the city lord's manor. After all, these types of events can help gladiators further enhance their own powers, thereby making arena battles more riveting for spectators to watch, so this actually benefits the city lord's manor," Toxic Dragon explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"On top of that, not all gladiators are here against their will like us. A considerable portion of them have come here voluntarily to hone their own powers, and they have more freedom than we do, so they're able to procure items from the outside that are completely out of our reach," Toxic Dragon continued.

"In that case, this does sound like a splendid opportunity. I'll go and take a look with you," Han Li said with a smile.

With that, Toxic Dragon led the way out of the ninth area before making his way to the first area with Han Li in tow.

As they passed through each area, they were stopped by armored guards from the city lord's manor, but they would quickly be granted free passage once they were identified.

"Looks like being the leader of an area comes with many privileges," Han Li remarked with a smile.

"You don't necessarily have to be an area leader, anyone will be able to enjoy the same privileges as long as they've displayed enough power. Honestly, if you show your true power and fight a few more spectacular battles, then you'll be able to participate in events like this even without my accompaniment," Toxic Dragon said.

Han Li nodded in response, then asked, "Has there been any news on Shi Kong and the others?"

"I don't think the beautiful woman that you mentioned has ever appeared in Green Goat City, and I haven't been able to dig up any information on Shi Kong, either. However, I have heard that Daoist Xie is currently with Chen Yang," Toxic Dragon replied.

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this. He had ventured into this Scalptia Spatial Domain in search of Violet Spirit, but so many years had passed by, and he was still trapped here with no progress made.

The two of them continued onward in silence, and before long, they reached a spacious hall in the first area.

As soon as he entered the hall, Han Li immediately heard a loud commotion, and he was greeted by a lively and bustling sight resembling a busy market.

The hall was packed with people, and the ground had been divided up into a series of stalls where all types of items were being displayed, including weapons, armor, and boxes crafted out of bone or stone, containing different types of precious pills.

"Sun Binghe has a scaled beast bone saber that I'd like to get my hands on, but I'm not sure if he'll be willing to sell it, so I'm going to ask him. Do you want to come with me?" Toxic Dragon asked.

"You can go on your own," Han Li replied with a shake of his head. "I don't know what I want to buy for now, so I'll do some exploring by myself."

Toxic Dragon nodded in response before departing, while Han Li made his way down the narrow aisles between the stalls, seeing if there was anything that caught his interest.

Over the years, he had earned quite a large sum of profound points, most of which had been spent on beast cores. Up to this point, he had only purchased a single weapon, which was that bone spear that he had used against the Black Scaled Elephant.

Right at this moment, Han Li caught sight of a pair of familiar figures not far up ahead, namely Gu Qianxun and Tu Gang.

Gu Qianxun spotted Han Li out of the corner of her eye, and she excused herself before making her way toward him.

"By the looks of it, you must've come here straight after a battle, right, Fellow Daoist Li?" Gu Qianxun asked with a faint smile.

"That's right. If it wasn't for Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon, I wouldn't even have been aware of this exchange event," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I've watched a few of your battles, and I've won quite a bit of stuff from Fellow Daoist Tu Gang and the others from betting on you," Gu Qianxun chuckled.

"In that case, shouldn't you share some of your spoils with me?" Han Li jibed.

"Winning bets is a matter of luck and sound judgment. If you'd like, you can come and watch a few of my battles and make some winnings for yourself by betting on me," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li was just about to say something when Gu Qianxun's voice rang out in his mind: "Before we stray too far off topic, there's something that I would like to exchange from you."

"Oh? What could I possibly have that would be of interest to you, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"In the past, I had always been under the impression that the cultivation arts that you've been using are quite crude, and that's why your profound acupoints are distributed all over your body with no particular areas of focus.

“However, I've recently come to notice that you've been specifically refining your legs, and you've also earned the moniker of 'Shadow' for your exceptional movement techniques. At this point, your reputation is almost on par with that of Toxic Dragon's in the ninth area, so this leg refinement cultivation art of yours must be quite exceptional," Gu Qianxun said.

"Is that what you want from me?" Han Li asked.

"That's right," Gu Qianxun replied with a nod.

"In that case, I'm afraid that I'll have to turn you down. The cultivation art you're referring to is called the Wingform Ascension Arts, and I obtained it through some special means, so it's not up for exchange," Han Li said.

Gu Qianxun remained completely unfazed as she said, "Don't be in a hurry to turn me down, Fellow Daoist Li. Why don't you have a listen to what I have to offer in exchange first?"

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"Are you interested in a cultivation art that focuses on refining the arms?" Gu Qianxun asked.

"I'm still yet to fully master the Wingform Ascension Arts, what good would another cultivation art do me? If I take on too many cultivation arts at once, I'll risk biting off more than I can chew," Han Li said.

"It's clear that your Wingform Ascension Arts focuses on opening profound acupoints on the legs, thereby greatly enhancing your speed, but it doesn't benefit you much in other areas. On top of that, I'm not just offering any ordinary cultivation art in exchange. Instead, the Titan Vajra Arts that I'm offering specializes in enhancing one's strength," Gu Qianxun said.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. He had heard of the Titan Vajra Arts from Toxic Dragon, and he knew that this was a cultivation art used by Tu Gang, so Gu Qianxun had most likely obtained it from him.

"Pardon me for being frank, Fellow Daoist Li, but your Wingform Ascension Arts may allow you to deal with C tier scaled beasts with ease, but it won't be enough for you to take on a B tier scaled beast or above. After all, the higher the tier of a scaled beast, the more physical prowess they possess, so speed alone won't be enough to break through their defenses," Gu Qianxun continued.

Han Li was well aware of this himself. He hadn't challenged a single B tier scaled beast up to this point, and one reason for this was that he didn't want to expose his true number of profound acupoints, but the main concern was that he simply lacked the power to go toe to toe against such fearsome scaled basts.

"I do indeed require a cultivation art like the Titan Vajra Arts, but given the fact that I obtained my Wingform Ascension Arts through rather special means, a one-for-one exchange is not very appealing to me," Han Li said.

"Truth be told, I obtained the Titan Vajra Arts from someone else as well, and it cost me dearly. I'd say it's no less precious than your Wingform Ascension Arts, but as a gesture of sincerity, I'm willing to throw in three additional C tier scaled beast cores. How does that sound?" Gu Qianxun asked after a brief pause.

"Three C tier scaled beast cores? What a stingy offer! This cultivation art of mine is the basis for my success as a gladiator, how could it possibly only be comparable in value to the Titan Vajra Arts?" Han Li countered as he raised an eyebrow.

Gu Qianxun fell silent again for a moment, then said, "In that case, I'll throw in a B tier scaled beast core as well. How about that?"

Chapter 877: Breakthrough

"Deal!" Han Li replied without any hesitation.

"Hold on just a second, Fellow Daoist Li, I also have a minor additional request. In addition to the cultivation art, would you also be able to include your cultivation insights as well?" Gu Qianxun asked.

"Sure. However, you can only keep the Wingform Ascension Arts and my cultivation insights to yourself and not pass it onto anyone else. If you agree to this condition, then swear a vow on it. If not, then I'm afraid that the deal will have to fall through," Han Li said.

"As far as I'm aware, you are the only one in Green Goat City who possesses this cultivation art. Even if this wasn't a condition of yours, there's no way I would've passed on such a rare cultivation art to anyone else," Gu Qianxun replied, following which she immediatley swore a vow to keep the cultivation art to herself.

With all of his conditions met, Han Li exchanged cultivation arts with her through spiritual sense communication, and he also received a B tier beast core for his efforts.

Both parties were very pleased with this outcome, and after parting ways with Gu Qianxun, Han Li explored the event for half a day, but didn't find anything else that caught his eye.

After bidding farewell to Toxic Dragon, he departed from the exchange event, but instead of returning to the ninth area, he went to the exchange hall instead.

"How can I help you today, Fellow Daoist Li?" a crimson-robed arena employee asked.

At this point, Han Li had forged quite a reputation for himself, and he took part in arena battles far more frequently than the average gladiator. On top of that, he also made more exchanges than the average gladiator, so he had become quite familiar with the arena employees.

"I want to enter the star pond," Han Li replied as he handed over his badge, which contained 118 profound points.

He had been working tirelessly these past few years and earned quite a large sum of profound points, but he had used all of it on cultivation, so he didn't have much to spare at all.

The crimson-robed employee nodded in response, and he took Han Li's badge before waving a silver baton over it, deducting a hundred profound points.

Han Li then followed the crimson-robed employee to the entrance of the passageway that led to the star pond, and like usual, the stone gate was tightly shut.

The crimson-robed young man pulled out a blue badge before pressing it against the stone gate, upon which was an indentation that the blue badge fit perfectly into.

Specks of starlight were released by the badge before rapidly spreading over the stone gate, which slowly swung open with a faint click.

"Come with me," the young man said as he removed the badge before leading Han Li into the passageway, and the stone gate swung shut behind them.

After walking through the dimly lit passageway for a short while, the two of them arrived at a staircase that led upward.

The staircase was quite long, and it took them a while to reach the top, where they arrived in a stone chamber that was around two hundred to three hundred feet in size.

To call it a stone chamber wasn't entirely accurate as there was no ceiling, so it was more like a man-made basin on a mountain summit.

At the center of the open-air area was a circular pond that was over a hundred feet in size, and it was surrounded by roughly a dozen trees that were a pristine white color throughout, including in their trunks, their branches, and their leaves, making it appear as if they had been carved out of white jade.

Furthermore, these trees were extremely lush and vibrant, and their dense canopies covered virtually the entire open-air area above the pond, while their trunks were riddled with countless white patterns that extended all the way into the pond.

It was nighttime at the moment, and rays of starlight were cascading down from above.

The leaves of the white trees were radiating rays of white light, and they collected all of the nearby starlight before funneling it into the trees, following which the starlight was then released into the pond.

As a result, the water in the pond was filled with radiant starlight, giving it the appearance of a starry pond.

A white-robed young man was seated with his legs crossed beside the pond, meditating with his eyes closed.

The man appeared to be in his early thirties, and his skin was extremely pale, completely devoid of color. On top of that, his hair and eyebrows were also white.

"Gladiator Li Feiyu has submitted a hundred profound points to enter the star pond," the crimson-robed young man declared in a respectful manner.

The white-robed man opened his eyes and took a glance at Han Li, then gave a slight nod.

The crimson-robed young man extended a respectful bow before departing.

The white-robed man remained silent as he pulled out a palm-sized hourglass, then set it down beside him to commence the countdown.

Han Li immediately leaped into the pond upon seeing this, sending glowing white water splashing in all directions.

He had been here on more than one past occasion, so he already knew the rules.

For a hundred profound points, he would only have an hour to spend in the star pond.

After sitting down in the pond with his legs crossed, he channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts, and pure starpower instantly began to surge into his body from all directions.

Han Li channeled all of the starpower toward a profound acupoint on his lower abdomen.

This was the only profound acupoint in the Wingform Ascension Arts that wasn't on the legs, but it was also the most important profound acupoint and the most difficult hurdle to overcome in the Wingform Ascension Arts.

As long as he could open this profound acupoint, he would essentially have achieved full mastery of the Wingform Ascension Arts, and it would only be a matter of time before the rest of the profound acupoints opened up.

During the past few years, Han Li had been focusing solely on his Wingform Ascension Arts, and he had made rapid progress, reaching this bottleneck three months ago.

Over the course of these three months, he had tried a whole host of ways to break through the bottleneck, but progress had proven elusive.

This was why he had saved up some profound points to enter the star pond in the hope that this would be the catalyst he needed.

The vast torrent of starpower entering his body surged toward the profound acupoint at his behest, but it refused to budge.

Han Li wasn't surprised to see this, and he channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts as he made a second attempt.

One burst of starpower crashed into the profound acupoint after another, and close to two hours flew by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, Han Li's complexion had become quite flushed, and sweat was beginning to bead up on his forehead, indicating that this was a very strenuous process.

However, his efforts were paying off, and the profound acupoint was not far away from completely opening.

Han Li took a deep breath to brace himself, then directed another burst of starpower at the profound acupoint, only to discover that it had become very resilient again, refusing to open any further.

"I had a feeling it wouldn't be so easy," Han Li murmured to himself as he flipped a hand over to produce a fist-sized beast core.

It was the B tier beast core that he had just obtained from Gu Qianxun, and inside it was a swirling vortex of white starlight.

At the same time, the beast core was giving off a burst of starpower fluctuations that was even more formidable than that of the star pond.

Compared with the Titan Vajra Arts, this B tier beast core was actually the more appealing of the two to Han Li.

The beast core contained tremendous starpower, thereby making it very effective when it came to opening profound acupoints, and that was why he had agreed to Gu Qianxun's proposal. Otherwise, he wouldn't have been willing to impart his cultivation art onto anyone else.

The higher the caliber of a beast core, the more difficult it was to refine, but thanks to the Heaven Controlling Vial, this was not a concern for Han Li.

The beast core quickly melted in his stomach to form a burst of extremely formidable and violent starpower that began to rampage through his body.

However, the starpower was then immediately tamed by the suction force released by the Heaven Controlling Vial, allowing Han Li to control it and direct it at his desired profound acupoint.

A resounding boom rang out in his mind as his spiritual sense churned violently. Even his dantian was trembling as the profound acupoint began to open further once again, much to Han Li's elation.

He took a deep breath as he redoubled his efforts, drawing upon the starpower from the beast core and the star pond with all his might, and a vortex took shape within the starpower around him.

The white-robed man's eyes sprang open in surprise upon seeing this, and he murmured to himself, "What cultivation art is he using? It's been a long time since I've seen anyone stir up the star pond to this extent."

Observing others through one's spiritual sense was strictly prohibited in the star pond, so he refrained from doing so, but he was looking at Han Li with a very intrigued expression.

Time slowly passed by, and it didn't take long before the sand in the hourglass ran out.

Han Li was still seated in the star pond with a radiant ball of starlight glowing on his lower abdomen, and it was giving off more and more violent starpower fluctuations.

It was clear that he was at a very crucial juncture in his cultivation, and the white-robed man took a hesitant glance at the spent hourglass, then decided not to rouse Han Li from his cultivation.

Several more minutes passed by, and right at this moment, a faint crack rang out from Han Li's lower abdomen as the all-important profound acupoint was finally opened.

All of the profound acupoints on his legs instantly began to release bursts of starlight, and his entire body was feeling as light as a feather.

An ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face as his eyes sprang open, and he flew straight out of the star pond.

The starlight radiating from the profound acupoints on his legs formed a nebulous cloud that carried his body, allowing him to remain suspended in mid-air.

Chapter 878: Letter and Vial

A peculiar look flashed through the white-robed man's eyes as he watched Han Li hover in mid-air, and only then did it occur to Han Li that he wasn't alone.

He immediately took a moment to regain his composure, then appeared in front of the white-robed man just a moment later, covering a distance over over a hundred feet in the blink of an eye.

The white-robed man observed Han Li in silence, while Han Li took a glance at the hourglass beside him, then cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Thank you for allowing me to cultivate in the star pond longer than the allotted time. How many more profound points should I issue?"

Even though he had been cultivating in the star pond, he had also been keeping constant tabs on what was happening around him, and he was quite grateful for the white-robed man's gesture of goodwill.

"There's no need for that, you only went a few minutes overtime anyway. However, I do have a question for you," the white-robed man replied.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist," Han Li prompted with a smile."

A slightly fervent look appeared in the white-robed man's eyes as he asked, "What is the cultivation art that you're using? It seems to be most extraordinary."

"The cultivation is called the Wingform Ascension Arts," Han Li replied.

He had already mentioned the name of this cultivation art to both Gu Qianxun and Toxic Dragon in the past, so there was no need to hide it.

"That's a great name for a brilliant cultivation art. With the breakthrough that you've just made, I'm sure you'll perform even better in future arena battles and truly establish a resounding reputation for yourself," the white-robed man said with a faint smile.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. Gladiators like myself are constantly putting their lives on the line, and I'm only working so hard in my cultivation so that I'll have some better chances at survival," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"The arena is a dangerous place, but at the very least, the battles are conducted in a fair and open fashion. While those in the outside world appear to enjoy more freedom and safety than us, that may not necessarily be the case," the white-robed man said with a shake of his head.

"That's true. Cultivation is an endeavor that goes against the natural order to begin with, so it really makes no difference whether one is in the arena or the outside world," Han Li replied with a nod.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before Han Li departed.

……

After leaving the star pond, Han Li traveled down the same passageway that he had arrived from, and he felt as light as a feather, as if he could take flight at any moment that he pleased.

Indeed, as soon as he decided to rise up into the air, his body immediately obliged, and it was as if he was no longer bound by the forces of gravity.

Han Li stepped down onto the air beneath his feet, and a faint pop immediately rang out as he launched himself forward through the air.

However, within the confines of the passageway, he wasn't able to fly very far before reaching the stone wall up ahead, and he stepped onto the air once again to send himself flying back again.

All of a sudden, he was like a child who had found a new toy, and he began darting back and forth within the passageway like an agile little bird.

Only after playing around for quite some time was he finally satisfied, but the grin on his face remained as wide as ever.

In the outside world, the flight ability granted by the Wingform Ascension Arts was naturally nothing of note, but it was extraordinarily useful in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

With this ability up his sleeve, things were going to become a lot more convenient for him both in battle and in daily life.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he returned to his room to rest.

Opening that all-important profound acupoint had been a highly intense process that had severely taxed his spiritual sense, so he was feeling quite exhausted, and he was just about to fall asleep on his bed when he suddenly spotted something on the stone table in the room.

The table had been completely empty when he left, but at this moment, there was an envelope sitting on it, next to which was a small red vial that was several inches in size. Through its semi-transparent wall, he could see some dark red liquid inside.

Han Li immediately turned his gaze to the door of his room, only to find that there was nothing amiss.

The newly purchased Heavenly Star Shell was completely unharmed, and the door didn't appear to have been tampered with, either.

His expression immediately darkened significantly upon seeing this.

Someone had been able to bypass his Heavenly Star Shell and sneak into his room without leaving any trace behind.

In the wake of this discovery, Han Li was wide awake, and he strode over to the table and thoroughly examined the envelope and the vial. Only after verifying that there didn't seem to be any problems with them did he open the envelope to reveal a sheet of purple paper, written onto which was a small passage of text.

Han Li read the message on the letter, and his expression instantly changed drastically as he rushed over to the stone door, pressing an ear against it to hear what was happening outside.

Moments later, his expression eased slightly as he returned to the stone table, then looked down at the letter once again.

The message on the letter read: "The Green Goat City Lord yearns for your true spirit bloodline and wishes to make it his own, and he'll be making a move against you soon. If you want to live, then drink what's in the vial, and it may save your life."

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of this message.

Who was it that had delivered these two things to him? Could it have been Daoist Xie?

However, he then quickly shook his head to dismiss that possibility. The method used to infiltrate his room was far more advanced than the method employed last time, so it was most likely someone else on this occasion.

Furthermore, if it were Daoist Xie, then he would've left some type of sign behind to prove the validity of the message.

If it wasn't Daoist Xie, then who could it be? Was the message to be trusted, or was someone doing this as part of a plot against him?

Countless questions arose in Han Li's mind at once, rendering him unable to focus.

This was a very concerning sign, and he hurriedly took a deep breath to compose himself.

In contrast with finding out who it was that had delivered these two things to him, it was much more urgent for him to verify the validity of the message.

With that in mind, the thought of Chen Yang flashed through his mind.

He recalled that Chen Yang had indeed displayed a slightly strange reaction back when he had revealed his true spirit bloodline to him in battle.

However, what did the Green Goat City Lord need a true spirit bloodline for? Was it to enhance his own combat prowess?

After some contemplation, Han Li picked up the red vial to conduct a close examination.

The dark red liquid in the vial resembled some type of blood, but it had no bloody odor.

Even after racking his own brains extensively, Han Li was unable to identify this liquid, so he could only stow the envelope and the vial away before leaving his room to pay Chen Lin a visit.

However, Chen Li didn't seem to be inside, and he received no response even after knocking repeatedly on Chen Lin's door.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he made his way to Toxic Dragon's room instead.

This time, the door was quickly opened for him.

"Can I help you with something, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"I have some things that I want to ask you, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon," Han Li replied in a calm manner.

Toxic Dragon invited Han Li into his room, then brewed two cups of tea.

Han Li left the tea untouched as he cut straight to the point and asked, "Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon, are you aware of true spirit bloodlines?"

"True spirit bloodlines? Of course. True spirits are special beasts born from heaven and earth, and they're far more powerful than normal beasts. Those who possess true spirit bloodlines can use some of the abilities of true spirits, and all of them possess immense potential.

“Unfortunately, there are very few true spirits in our Holy Realm, so true spirit bloodlines are extremely rare. Having said that, I've heard that true spirits are more common over in the Immortal Region. Why do you ask about this, Fellow Daoist Li?" Toxic Dragon asked with a perplexed expression.

"I heard someone mention true spirit bloodlines recently, and I was rather intrigued, so I came to ask you about it, seeing as you're just about the most knowledgeable person I can think of," Han Li replied with a smile.

Over the course of their time together, Han Li had developed a decent grasp on Toxic Dragon's personality. Toxic Dragon was a very capable man who possessed a sharp eye, but he also possessed flaws in that he was boastful and susceptible to praise and sycophantry.

Sure enough, a pleased smile appeared on Toxic Dragon's face in response to Han Li's compliment, and he continued, "True spirit bloodlines are extremely precious, particularly to us bodily refinement cultivators."

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"Those who possess true spirit bloodlines generally possess far more formidable physical bodies than the average person, and adopting true spirit transformations can enhance their physical prowess even further. On top of that, there's always a way to use true spirit bloodlines that very few people are aware of," Toxic Dragon replied with a mysterious expression.

This was exactly what Han Li was hoping to hear, but he continued to act only mildly interested as he asked, "Oh? How else can true spirit bloodlines be used?"

"I only heard about this in passing, but apparently, the power of true spirit bloodlines can assist one in opening profound acupoints," Toxic Dragon replied.

"Is that true?" Han Li asked.

"Like I said, I only heard this in passing, but I've never seen it for myself. There are far too few people in our Holy Realm who possess true spirit bloodlines, and even for those who fit that bill, they require corresponding cultivation arts to truly maximize their true spirit bloodlines," Toxic Dragon said.

"I see. Thank you for telling me all of this, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon. I still have some matters to attend to, so I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he rose to his feet.

Before Toxic Dragon had a chance to respond, he had already departed, and Toxic Dragon was rather taken aback by this, but didn't think anything of it.

After leaving Toxic Dragon's room, Han Li immediately returned to his own room with a complex look on his face.

Up to this point, he had finally received an explanation on why he was able to open profound acupoints far faster than others.

If true spirit bloodlines really could allow one to open profound acupoints faster than others, then it did make sense for the Green Goat City Lord to pursue his bloodline powers.

However, if that were the case, then why did the Green Goat City Lord send him to the arena instead of making a move on him right away?

Chapter 879: Unconventional Means

At this point, Han Li was already mostly convinced about the validity of the message on the letter, not just because of what he had just heard from Toxic Dragon and the peculiar reaction that Chen Yang had displayed in response to seeing his true spirit bloodline, but more so because of an instinctive feeling.

His intuition was telling him that the message on the letter was genuine.

This sense of intuition when it came to danger had saved on countless occasions during his cultivation journey up to this point, and with that in mind, a grim look appeared on his face.

If the Green Goat City really were plotting against him, then he was in a terrible situation. The Black Tribulation Centipede was still in his body, so not only could he not run away, he was also completely powerless to resist against the Green Goat City Lord.

However, he certainly wasn't just going to roll over and surrender.

After pacing back and forth in his room for a while, Han Li stopped in his tracks, then inspected the small red vial momentarily before opening his mouth to expel the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Instead of drinking the liquid in the red vial, he tipped all of it into the Heaven Controlling Vial, then replaced the stopper before swallowing the vial again.

Even though Han Li now mostly believed what was written on the letter, he definitely wasn't just going to blindly drink this strange liquid.

However, throwing it away would also be inappropriate, so this was the best middle ground.

After doing all of that, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed and closed his eyes to consider what he was going to do from here.

During these past few years, he had considered trying to get away, and he had gathered a lot of information in secret.

The entire arena was constructed in a completely sealed-off area in Green Goat City, and the only point of connection that it had with the outside world was its entrance.

The star pond and several other special areas in the arena were also connected to the outside world, but all of those areas had restrictions placed upon them, and they were also overseen by powerful cultivators to prevent people from attempting escape.

At this point, Han Li had already established a plan for what he was going to do if he were to attempt an escape someday.

However, figuring out the escape route was the easy part, dealing with the Black Tribulation Centipede was still the main concern.

Information on these creatures was extremely limited in Green Goat City, so unless he was to resort to some unconventional means, it didn't seem like he was going to make any progress on this matter.

Given the urgency of the situation, there was no longer any time for him to waste.

With that in mind, his eyes sprang open, and a decisive look appeared on his face as he made his way out of his room.

As usual, the gladiators of the ninth area greeted him as he passed them by.

Thanks to the concealment methods that Han Li had employed, his cultivation base didn't appear to have improved by much, but everyone had witnessed his powers in battle, and he was also quite close with Toxic Dragon, so there were many people trying to suck up to him.

Han Li nodded in response to all of the greetings, then quickly made his way to the exchange hall.

After wandering around in the hall for some time, he made his way down the passageway leading to the fourth area.

After staying in there for a short while, he traveled to the eighth area, then the first.

Some time later, he returned to the exchange hall with a peculiar look in his eyes.

He had been covertly observing his surroundings this entire time, thinking that if the Green Goat City Lord were planning to make a move soon, then perhaps he would send people to monitor him.

However, he didn't discover any signs that he was being followed, and that was both reassuring and confusing to him.

Having said that, he had already made up his mind, and he had no intention of turning back now.

Thus, he took a deep breath, then made his way to a place similar to the ninth area before knocking on a certain door.

The door slowly swung open, revealing a gray-robed young man, namely the man who had first brought Han Li into the arena, Zhu Jieshan.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Zhu," Han Li greeted with a smile.

"Li Feiyu? What are you doing here?" Zhu Jieshan asked with a surprised expression.

"There's no need to be so apprehensive of me, Fellow Daoist Zhu. You were the one who first indoctrinated me into the arena, and for that, I'm very grateful, so I thought I'd pay you a visit to show my appreciation. On top of that, there's also a small favor that I'd like to ask of you," Han Li said with a smile as he stuffed a small cloth pouch into Zhu Jieshan's hand.

The pouch contained several C tier beast cores, and Zhu Jieshan's expression eased slightly as he stepped to the side to allow Han Li into his room.

The layout of Zhu Jieshan's room was quite similar to that of Han Li's, but it was much larger and better furnished.

Zhu Jieshan brought out a tea set, then began brewing a pot of tea as he smiled and said, "Given how limited the resources in the arena are, I'm afraid I don't have any good tea to treat you with."

"This tea is very fragrant, Fellow Daoist Zhu. If this doesn't count as good tea, then I don't know what does," Han Li replied with a smile.

"You can take some tea leaves back with you if you like. By the way, why have you come to see me, Fellow Daoist Li?" Zhu Jieshan asked with a smile.

"Just now, as I returned to my room from an outing, I discovered that someone had snuck into my room and left this letter behind. Its contents were quite shocking to me, so I came to see you about it," Han Li replied with a serious expression as he pulled out the envelope and handed it over.

Zhu Jieshan accepted the letter before taking a look, upon which his expression instantly changed drastically.

Taking advantage of his momentary distraction, Han Li immediately reached out with his right hand, thrusting his index and middle fingers toward Zhu Jieshan's dantian like lightning.

At the same time, a translucent chain flew out of his glabella before piercing through the air en route to Zhu Jieshan's head.

Two crisp clangs rang out as a white bone sword appeared in front of Zhu Jieshan's lower abdomen to intercept Han Li's fingers, while a translucent rune had taken shape on his forehead, forming a glowing shield to keep out Han Li's spiritual sense chain.

Han Li's expression instantly darkened significantly upon seeing this.

"I knew you came here with bad intentions! Did you really think you could fool me?" Zhu Jieshan sneered.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he slashed the bone sword in his hand through the air, sending a streak of white sword qi that was around ten feet in length sweeping viciously toward Han Li.

Han Li's pupils contracted drastically upon seeing this. Devilish qi and immortal spiritual power were both inaccessible in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so how had he unleashed this streak of sword qi?

Despite his surprise, Han Li's reactions weren't slow at all, and he abruptly vanished from the spot, causing the streak of white sword qi to miss its target entirely.

Zhu Jieshan faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which he abruptly swung around and slashed his bone sword through the air.

However, before his sword was able to strike its target, a hand had already appeared before him, plunging toward his chest like a sharp dagger.

A loud thump rang out as Zhu Jieshan was sent flying by a burst of tremendous force before crashing heavily into a nearby wall.

A huge gash had been torn into his chest, and he threw up a mouthful of blood.

His bone sword had flown out of his grasp, and an astonished look had appeared on his face. Before he had a chance to say anything, Han Li appeared before him once again in a wraith-like manner, then threw a punch directly at him.

Having been disarmed, he could only attempt to raise his arms to defend himself.

However, given the injuries that he had just suffered, his movements were very slow, so he was already struck on the forehead before he could fully raise his arms.

A dull thump rang out as Zhu Jieshan slammed into the ground before throwing up another mouthful of blood. A dazed look had appeared in his eyes, clearly indicating that his consciousness had been rocked by Han Li's punch, but the glowing translucent shield in front of his forehead remained as bright as ever.

Han Li looked down at Zhu Jieshan from above, following which a Spiritual Sense Sword shot out of his glabella before instantly swelling to several feet in length.

The Spiritual Sense Sword was giving off tremendous spiritual sense fluctuations as it struck the light shield in front of Zhu Jieshan's forehead, and the light shield was instantly torn apart, while the rune on his forehead faded away.

After destroying the light shield, the Spiritual Sense Sword instantly stopped in its tracks.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li released several spiritual sense chains out of his hand, all of which burrowed their way into Zhu Jieshan's head before wrapping themselves in layers around Zhu Jieshan's soul.

As a result, Zhu Jieshan spasmed momentarily before falling completely still.

After doing all of that, Han Li made his way over to the door, then opened it a tiny bit to take a peek outside.

The walls of Zhu Jieshan's room were constructed from the same material as Han Li's room, and it had exceptional soundproofing properties and could also ward off spiritual sense, which was why Han Li dared to make such a violent move here.

After verifying that no one had noticed the scuffle that had just taken place, Han Li's expression eased slightly, and he closed the door again, then strode over to Zhu Jieshan's side before tapping a finger onto his glabella.

Zhu Jieshan slowly opened his eyes, and as soon as they regained focus, he immediately roared in a furious voice, "How dare you attack me, Li Feiyu? Are you not afraid of having your heart devoured by your Black Tribulation Centipede?!"

Chapter 880: Black Tribulation Stone

Han Li clenched his right hand into a fist and delivered a vicious blow to Zhu Jieshan's lower abdomen, instantly causing him to curl up into a ball, and his complexion turned deathly pale as a sheen of cold sweat appeared on his forehead.

"That was for the punch from back then," Han Li said in an expressionless manner, while Zhu Jieshan was too busy coughing and dry heaving to say anything.

"I don't have much time to waste. Is it true that the city lord is after my true spirit bloodline? Answer my question or I'm going to chop off all of your limbs with this sword of yours!" Han Li demanded in a cold voice as he picked up the bone sword.

"You wouldn't dare! You're just a lowly slave, if you dare to rebel, then your Black Tribulation Centipede will eat you alive!" Zhu Jieshan roared in a furious voice.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he slashed the sword through the air, slicing off Zhu Jieshan's left hand cleanly at the wrist.

Blood immediately began to spurt out of the wound, and Zhu Jieshan stared at his own left wrist in shock and horror for a moment, then opened his mouth to scream, only for Han Li to chop off his tongue as well, rendering him only able to make some unintelligible, gargled sounds.

"My patience is limited. The next time, it'll be your right hand! Answer my question!" Han Li demanded in a cold and forceful voice.

Zhu Jieshan shuddered as he turned to stare blankly at Han Li, who raised his sword once again as he turned a menacing gaze to Zhu Jieshan's right hand.

Upon realizing that verbal threats weren't going to work, Zhu Jieshan immediately changed tact, hurriedly imploring through voice transmission, "No, don't do it! I'll tell you! It's true, the city lord really is after your true spirit bloodline. I've heard that he can use the power of true spirit bloodlines to open profound acupoints or something like that, but I don't know the exact details. I'm telling the truth!"

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Up to this point, the contents of the letter had been confirmed to be true. It was a good thing that he had been so decisive and acted in advance. Otherwise, if he had waited until the city lord made his move, then it would've most likely already been too late.

"I never meant to cause any offense to you, Fellow Daoist Li. I was only following orders from my higher-ups, so please spare my life out of the kindness of your heart," Zhu Jieshan implored.

Han Li's expression eased slightly as he said, "Rest assured, I won't kill you as long as you tell me everything that you know."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Li," Zhu Jieshan hurriedly replied.

"If the city lord wants my true spirit bloodline, then why did he wait until now instead of making a move on me right away?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know, I only followed orders to guide you into the arena. Everything else is completely out of my hands," Zhu Jieshan replied.

"When exactly is the city lord planning to make his move?" Han Li asked.

"I haven't been told that, I've only received some orders recently to keep a close eye on you . Aside from that, I haven't received any other instructions," Zhu Jieshan replied.

"You were probably also instructed to detain me right away if I displayed any suspicious activity, right? I know that there's something wrong with the tea that you gave me just now. Don't try to stall for time, I haven't actually drunk the tea at all, so it's not going to take effect," Han Li said with a cold sneer, then spat out a small mouthful of tea.

An astonished look appeared on Zhu Jieshan's face upon seeing this, following which he lowered his head in a panicked manner, not daring to look at Han Li.

"Alright, I have one final question for you, and I'll spare your life if you give me a satisfactory answer," Han Li said.

Zhu Jieshan's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "What do you want to know?"

"How can I extract the Black Tribulation Centipede from my body without being caught?" Han Li asked.

"Black Tribulation Centipede are insects that are personally refined by the city lord, and he's the only one who knows how to remove them. I've heard stories of others trying to get rid of them, but all of those attempts have ended very badly," Zhu Jieshan replied with a grim expression.

Han Li had already anticipated that this would most likely be the response, but his expression still darkened slightly upon hearing this.

Zhu Jieshan's face instantly turned deathly pale at the sight of Han Li's displeased expression, and he hurriedly continued, "I'm telling the truth, Fellow Daoist Li! I can swear a vow on it! There's no way that the city lord would tell someone as insignificant as me the method to remove Black Tribulation Centipedes!"

At this moment, Zhu Jieshan's soul was still bound by Han Li's spiritual sense chains, so Han Li was able to detect Zhu Jieshan's spiritual fluctuations, and through them, he could tell that Zhu Jieshan didn't seem to be lying.

Unfortunately, he was unable to draw upon any immortal spiritual power. Otherwise, he could simply use a soul search technique and spare himself a lot of trouble.

"As an arena administrator, there's no way that you don't know anything about Black Tribulation Centipedes. I recall you telling me that Black Tribulation Centipedes will turn on someone if they try to run away. Why is that?" Han Li asked.

Zhu Jieshan shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and a hesitant look appeared on his face.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he swept the bone sword through the air, and a deep gash instantly appeared on Zhu Jie's right wrist, almost slicing his hand off cleanly.

He immediately let loose a strangled cry of agony, and his entire body began trembling uncontrollably.

"I already told you that I don't have much patience. If you try to test me again, then I'll chop off all of your limbs, and I have many ways to ensure that you won't be able to regrow them," Han Li threatened as he raised the bone sword again.

"I'll talk!" Zhu Jieshan hurriedly yelled.

"Hurry up!" Han Li coerced as he pressed the edge of the bone sword against Zhu Jieshan's skin.

"There's a Black Tribulation Stone in the city lord's manor that releases a special type of soul power fluctuations across the entirety of Green Goat City. All Black Tribulation Centipedes will fall into a deep sleep under the effects of these soul power fluctuations, but if someone strays too far away from the Black Tribulation Stone, then the Black Tribulation Centipede in their body will immediately awaken," Zhu Jieshan replied.

"Does that mean that if I obtain this stone and carry it with me, then the Black Tribulation Centipede in my body will never awaken?" Han Li asked as his eyes lit up slightly.

"That seems feasible theoretically, but I don't know if it'll work in practice. After all, there's no guarantee that the city lord won't have any other tricks up his sleeve," Zhu Jieshan replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he fell into deep thought, but he then raised his head again as he asked in a cold voice, "What else do you know about Black Tribulation Centipedes? Tell me everything!"

"That's all I know, I swear!" Zhu Jieshan insisted as tears began to well up in his eyes.

"Alright, I'm going to capture another administrator and interrogate them. If he corroborates your answers, then I'll spare you. If not, then I'll slice you up and feed you to the scaled beasts in the arena!" Han Li said in a cold voice.

In the face of Han Li's threats, not only did Zhu Jieshan not appear terrified, he seemed to be quite relieved instead.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this. Judging from his reaction, it seemed that Zhu Jieshan wasn't lying.

He slammed the flat side of the bone sword into the back of Zhu Jieshan's head, instantly causing him to fall to the ground in an unconscious state.

After that, he cast a seal onto Zhu Jieshan's soul, and only then was he satisfied.

This seal would ensure that Zhu Jieshan would remain unconscious for three days and three nights, so he wouldn't be able to interfere with Han Li's escape plans.

He hadn't spared Zhu Jieshan out of kindness or anything like that. Instead, he was worried that perhaps there were certain restrictions placed on him, so killing him could alert some other parties to what he had done.

After stuffing Zhu Jieshan under his bed and cleaning the blood from the room, Han Li emerged from the room in a calm manner.

After leaving the area, Han Li returned to the exchange hall and looked down at the arena below.

On the other side of the arena, almost facing directly across from the exchange hall, was a wide passageway that led outward. That was the entrance of the arena, through which he could enter Green Goat City, which was where the city lord's manor was situated.

In order to obtain the Black Tribulation Stone, he would have to enter Green Goat City.

According to the rules, gladiators were not permitted to leave the arena, and there were also many guards at the entrance to prevent gladiators from getting away, so it wasn't going to be easy to escape.

With these thoughts running through his mind, Han Li began to make his way back to his room.

Now that he had become aware of the fact that he had to obtain the Black Tribulation Stone, he had to change his escape plan a little.

After returning to the ninth area, Han Li opened the door to his room, then immediately stopped cold in his tracks.

Daoist Xie was standing inside, waiting for him, and an elated look appeared on his face as he opened his mouth to speak, but his expression then abruptly changed as he shot back in retreat.

At the same time, a figure appeared up above in a wraith-like manner, then slammed a palm into his chest with tremendous force.